Hotel Del Luna Blu-ray Disc 5
Subtitle re-timing by Jharel
It's not that wonderful
to be in hell together.
What I have is hell.
Goodbye.
Chan-sung.
She's gone.
Hey.
Can you see that?
-I'm sorry.
Let's go.
I didn't know a place like this
existed in Myeong-dong.
-Me neither.
-Let's go.
Mr. Koo must feel very flustered.
He worked with us for quite some time.
Shouldn't you at least leave him a text?
I gave him something else instead.
I gave him a severance pay
and a dismissal notice.
I guess you just think of him
as the 99th human who worked for you.
No, Chan-sung is special.
I don't want to become weak-hearted.
I'm trying to be stronger.
I haven't heard
such sentimental words from you in...
No, this is the first time in 500 years.
Five hundred years?
Has it been that long since you died?
What are you still doing here
for 500 years?
I shouldn't be hearing that from a ghost
who's been here twice as long.
I can't leave
because I'm tied to the Moon Tree.
I can't leave because I still have
shame to clear up in this world.
I can't face my ancestors
in the afterlife like this.
Even if you go to the afterlife,
you won't meet your ancestors.
They must have reincarnated
several times already.
You're worrying for nothing.
I can just remain at the hotel
and continue to worry for nothing.
But will you be all right like this?
Will you be all right
giving up your chance
to go to the afterlife peacefully
through Mr. Koo?
They won't let me go peacefully.
In the future, try to speed up
and take care of your shame
left in this life.
There won't be much time.
If you can't solve it, take the bus
to the afterlife without regrets.
What about the guests?
Did you send them off properly?
We moved them with the help
of the Grim Reapers.
Although there was some confusion
due to the sudden move.
Those of you who have no regrets
and can leave right now.
Please take this bus.
Those of you who can't leave
because of your resentments.
Please standby here.
TO THIS LIFE, TO THE AFTERLIFE
You must not get confused.
Once you get on the bus,
you can't turn back.
Are you going to the afterlife?
My older child went to college
and is doing well now.
It's time to leave.
You went to wake up your son
in his dreams every morning.
I'm glad he finally went to college.
Have a good trip.
TO THIS LIFE, TO THE AFTERLIFE
You must choose a line.
I can't decide whether to go
to the afterlife or stay here.
Did you finish the novel
you were working on?
No. I couldn't finish it when I was alive.
I guess I can't finish it when I'm dead.
I had better go.
Should I stay and write it?
This guest can't make up his mind.
He won't be able to leave.
Finishing the novel is not the problem.
He can only leave when he gives up
what he can't do.
This bus goes to the afterlife.
You must be careful to choose
the right line.
You can't go back.
A few of the employees
went on the bus to the afterlife.
We will be shorthanded for a while.
Encourage the employees
to go to the afterlife.
Why are you acting
like you're closing down the hotel?
We've moved to a new place,
so we need to find a human manager.
No need.
We have Yu-na.
Did they move all my things?
Ms. Fourth Choice called a moving company
and took care of all your things.
Hey. You have to drive.
I've ridden a horse,
but I have yet to drive a car.
You haven't even learned to drive
a car for 500 years?
You're the weird ghost
who drives around a car.
Unbelievable.
Darn.
Why are you laughing?
I find it funny
that a ghost wears a seat belt.
I like that this is an open car.
This is my first time
after riding in your Pony 2.
It seems you like this pretentious thing.
Get in, and let's take this for a spin.
Giddy-up!
"Giddy-up"? What a fool.
The new place is in country side?
This is nice. It's like going on a picnic.
What?
I'm talking on the phone.
Just follow the navigation.
Okay.
I'd better get the driver license
to get to work.
Just concentrate on your school.
Summer break has started, stupid.
And I will graduate soon.
Her parents said they'll get me
a car if I go to college.
I have an apartment under my name too.
I'll get my own place
as soon as I graduate.
It's difficult to live
with her parents, right?
I'm just paying a very high price.
This is strong. Do you want a sip?
What?
Would you?
I'm fine.
What's wrong?
There's a woman in the car in front of us.
Don't look. She can be dangerous for you.
Help me...
Help me. Please...
There are many ghosts in this world.
Don't be too concerned about them.
I'm meant to be the manager
of Hotel del Luna.
Let's take that ghost as our guest.
What?
Sir.
A grey car just passed by us.
Can you go after it?
-What?
-I'll pay you extra money.
-Can you go faster?
-Okay.
You'll get in trouble.
You're not even a hotel manager.
Faster, please.
PHARMACY
Are you looking for Hotel del Luna?
Did you know that the hotel moved?
You must know where it moved.
If I tell you, will you go find it again?
You nearly died because of Man-wol.
I heard you embraced that potent curse.
If you haven't lifted that curse,
your soul is probably seriously hurt now.
Chan-sung, let her go.
Jang Man-wol protected me.
I'm fine.
Man-wol is fine thanks to you.
You are the one who protected her.
My sister chose the right person.
So keep up the good work.
Was I sent to that hotel for that purpose?
When the terrible fate comes to her
from the past,
am I supposed to block her from it?
You successfully carried out your mission.
Why are you angry?
Do you feel pity for Man-wol
you saw in your dreams?
Yes, I do.
I feel angry that you praise me
for not taking her side.
She abandoned me because I got in her way.
Are you telling me
to keep on getting in her way?
It's cool to take someone's side
while getting in the way is not.
Everyone wants
the role of embracing and consoling her.
The shabby role of getting in the way,
holding on, and begging
can only be done by a good person.
Don't overestimate me.
I don't want to take the role
that nobody wants.
I'm not such a good person.
Really? Then you can quit.
Just eat this.
What is this?
That medicine will take away
your ability to see ghosts.
You won't be able to see ghosts
and Hotel del Luna anymore.
I won't be able to see all of them?
She abandoned you too.
I have to give you the chance
to discard her too.
Sometimes, we can be very fair.
I came here for a way to find her.
But you give the way to never go back.
The results are not given by the deities.
It's made by humans.
It's always the same.
Thank you for giving me this chance.
Wait. Are you taking it now?
Without thinking about it?
Did you think I wouldn't take it?
Because I was a good person?
I told you.
I'm not good enough to volunteer
to take shabby roles.
I still hesitate...
only because she is in my heart.
Hugging and comforting her
is nowhere enough for her.
She's an awful woman.
She abandoned me because I got in her way.
Even if I went back,
she wouldn't welcome me.
And you never know
when she'll do something dangerous again.
I'll need to figure out
if I want to run back to her
despite all that.
If it's old,
it should at least look antique.
If it's tiny, it should at least be cute.
No matter how much I look at this,
it looks absolutely hideous.
This was the only piece of land
we could buy with little money.
But there is a cemetery
over the hills over there.
The land is dark and damp, so it's great.
And this place has great water,
so it's famous for makgeolli too.
Back when you were poor and starving
as you ran Man-wol Hostel,
you always had makgeolli
with radish kimchi, remember?
That rice wine was made here.
Stop talking about that time.
The building looks awfully ugly enough.
I feel like I'm as poor
as I was back then.
Anyway, the air is really fresh.
There's no fine dust here.
Fine dust? If it was around,
could you breathe it in?
I can't believe a ghost is
talking about fresh water and air.
Fine, I can just ignore the outside.
It's all the same once I'm inside.
Hurry up!
The lobby looks a bit smaller,
don't you think?
It's just your imagination.
It looks the same.
The guests complained a lot
when we sent them off in a hurry.
We couldn't bloom
enough flowers in the garden,
so of course, we became poorer.
It'll be the middle of the month,
so we'll have more guests.
We have a great location.
I'm thirsty.
I'll be in the garden
looking at the Moon Tree. Bring champagne.
Your stuff isn't here yet,
so we have no champagne.
What?
Why aren't they here yet?
Are they slacking off somewhere else?
Why don't we grab some makgeolli
for a change?
Just like the old times.
I just said I didn't want
to talk about that time.
You forgot what I just said.
Mr. Kim.
You couldn't resolve your grudges
for 500 years
maybe because you forgot what they are,
like a goldfish.
"A goldfish"?
I'm a scholar who passed
the National State Exam.
I could be an elegant crane,
not a goldfish.
A crane?
Both a crane and a goldfish are stupid.
What? "Stupid"?
I can't believe that mean and crude woman.
Calm down.
The outside of this hotel looks ugly,
so she's a bit ticked off.
Man-wol only looks okay on the outside.
She's definitely evil on the inside.
She fired Mr. Koo,
and she even called in a human
to do something suspicious.
Don't you think she sacked Mr. Koo
because of what happened that day?
She said she cut him off because she was
afraid she'd become weaker.
I'm afraid she might do
something dangerous again.
There is no human to stop her anymore.
So Mr. Koo can't see ghosts anymore?
Ms. Jang said so.
I guess she threw
a huge crude fit at Mago.
A goldfish?
Hey, I thought they would
all fall off after the move,
but they're still there.
Did you make sure that Koo Chan-sung
can't see ghosts anymore?
I gave him the medicine.
If he takes it,
he won't see ghosts any longer.
Okay.
Good.
You asked politely for the first time,
so I let you have your way.
But it's up to him to decide
to take the medicine or not.
What would he do?
Are you having fun?
I might as well ask for another favor.
Can you turn back these blue things?
I can't do anything about those.
That's how you feel.
It's up to you to bloom these flowers.
The buds look so pretty.
I will feel so bad for them
if they can't bloom the flowers.
Don't get your hopes up.
You won't see any flowers.
Don't even dream
about seeing any flower here.
Nothing changes at night either.
If you take the medicine,
you won't have to see
any ghosts or Hotel del Luna anymore.
You can't stand it?
Then run away from me, Chan-sung.
Are you looking for a hotel?
Hotel del Luna is not here anymore.
I'd love to take you there,
but I am not...
going there anymore.
I'm sorry.
Are you a human?
Do I look like a ghost?
Who are you?
What about you?
I'm with the real estate office.
This place is up for sale, so I came
to take pictures for our ads.
For sale?
They're selling this place?
Yes, is there a problem?
Yes, there are a lot of problems
in this place.
-Yes.
-Let's see.
-I have nothing to wear.
All right.
Ms. Jang, I got a call
from the real estate agent.
He asked if you paid the inheritance tax.
What tax?
If you didn't pay that,
there could be a problem
with the transfer tax.
I'm not really sure what he's saying.
How would I know?
Should I call Mr. Koo?
No. You can't call him.
God...
Is there any ghost
who would know a thing about this?
He used to work for the biggest law firm
in Korea, Jang and Yeong.
Then he died from overwork.
He said he used to be
a very competent lawyer.
Really?
Mr. Jang and Yeong. So what's the problem?
What's the deal with the inheritance tax?
The late Mr. No Jun-seok
left the building to you, Ms. Jang.
And he prepared all the paperwork
for you to pay the inheritance tax.
You can just pay it now.
With what?
Didn't you prepare the money?
No idea.
The guy who prepared that isn't here.
I have no idea if he prepared it at all.
If you sell your land to pay the taxes...
The inheritance tax,
the mortgage,
and the transfer tax...
There won't be much money left.
Why not? That's impossible.
I was told that land is very expensive.
Why wouldn't there be much money left?
That's how it works with taxes.
You should just pay the inheritance tax
and hold onto the land.
Mr. Jang and Yeong.
What are you doing?
You have to take care of this.
Mr. Jang and Yeong.
Because he died from overwork,
he faints if he reads anything
for more than five minutes.
What kind of ridiculous situation is this?
Darn it.
Sure thing. Please give me a call, then.
By the way, how did you know
about the inheritance tax?
I came to see the building,
and I ran into someone
by the name of Koo Chan-sung.
He's here with me right now.
He's there?
Could I speak to him?
God, it's all Greek to me.
Damn it!
Ms. Jang,
why don't you speak to him directly?
I have no clue what he's talking about.
And do you think I'd know?
Hey, Mr. Realtor.
Tell me, and make it easy and simple.
How much will I get out of it?
Don't try to swindle me.
I have a talented employee
who got his MBA from Harvard.
But you fired him.
Koo Chan-sung?
You don't know a thing about the taxes,
inheritance or transfer one, do you?
Why did you fire your talented employee?
Why are you over there?
Did you get hired by a realtor?
I came here because I was flustered
after getting fired overnight.
You must be regretting firing me.
If you just ask me to come back,
I can be there immediately.
Tell this to the realtor.
He should kick out anyone
that's unrelated,
and lock up the place well.
Okay. I got it.
Was Mr. Koo over there?
He must have been searching for us
all night long.
MANAGER KOO CHAN-SUNG
If he calls back,
tell him to call us when he's dead.
Right, Hyeon-jung and Yu-na!
Check if they're on their way.
Yes, ma'am.
If you don't like those, wear these.
No, they're not my type.
Wear your tacky poop colored shoes...
and go work at a normal hotel.
Okay, Chan-sung?
I have to lock up, so please leave.
Hey, where are we?
We got lost while chasing the other car.
Even the GPS can't find this road.
Where on earth are we?
What's the matter?
I saw someone on the road.
I don't see anyone.
There.
Gosh.
I'm sorry.
The car is not cooperating.
No.
I think we came to the right place.
I'll go out to a bigger road
to meet with the insurance agent.
See you later.
Darn it.
It was a man just now, wasn't it?
The ghost in the car earlier was a woman.
Let's go and see.
Yu-na.
I think it'll be too dangerous.
You're a ghost too.
I used to be one as well.
It's not that. Did you see the driver
of that car?
It was a young man wearing sunglasses.
There was a ghost in that man's car,
and when we chased after the car,
we found another ghost.
It feels a little...
Do you think they were killed by that man?
Humans can be more dangerous than ghosts.
If they died wrongfully,
I can't just leave.
I died wrongfully too.
I'll be careful.
Then promise me. You have to run back
to our car if you see a human.
-Okay?
-Okay.
By the way, it's usually people
who fear ghosts.
But we ghosts are scared of humans.
You're right.
He looked like an ordinary person.
This is our signature cocktail
the guests at the bar like the most.
Did you make this?
I did.
They dream of life here while being drunk.
These might be
the last drops of their tears
while they dream their lives away.
Why would you name it in English
when you were a Confucian scholar?
You're trying too hard to look cool.
I don't think someone who named this hotel
with a pretentious name
like "Hotel del Luna" can criticize.
As I expected, cocktails made by ghosts
are so disgusting.
I heard makgeolli is famous
in this village.
Don't you have any?
You're the one who told me
to never bring it up.
Did you forget?
Since when were you so obedient
to my orders?
I lost my appetite
because of this cocktail.
I know she's bored but can't go shopping.
But why is she taking it out on me?
It's delicious to me.
MAIN BUILDING
BORAM MAKGEOLLI
It's good.
What's this?
Who drank all this?
This village makes amazing makgeolli.
I wonder if there's anything to snack on.
Is there a radish field around here?
This will taste great with some radish.
Let's see
Where's the radish field?
No wonder the makgeolli tasted so nice.
Are you the big tree
beyond the hill over there?
Yes.
You've built a very nice house.
That place must be
the Guest House of the Moon,
where souls come to rest.
Yes.
And I'm the owner.
I'm the Guardian of the Well
of this village.
This village has a deity
who protects its well.
No wonder the water tasted so nice here.
I got to taste great makgeolli
thanks to you.
You got fired?
Did you get fired because of me?
What in the world did you do
to cause so much trouble
at Chan-sung's hotel?
I can't remember.
I remember feeling happy
because the hotel was so nice.
But I can't remember
anything else after that.
And when I woke up,
I was drunk in a cab.
I can't remember if I drank.
You probably did. You love alcohol.
You probably got drunk and caused trouble.
That's your thing.
I saw it a couple times.
It wasn't because of Mi-ra.
I just got fired
because she thought I was a nuisance.
I should find a way to go back.
I guess Man-wol dumped Chan-sung.
But it's not like
they went out with each other.
Chan-sung liked her.
Man-wol left him with an expensive
painting, so he'd leave her alone.
I've seen my yacht club members
do the same thing.
I never thought she would do that.
She's so mean.
Are you saying that huge painting
of the mountain
is worth a lot of money?
Did she really have to give him
a painting of Baekdu Mountain?
He's going to feel sad every time
he listens to the national anthem.
Sir.
As I thought, you have the ability
to see dead people.
I saw on the news that you passed away.
I'm sorry I didn't get to visit you.
I wanted to see this painting
one last time before I leave.
Is the tiger inside this painting?
The tiger rested well
at the hotel I used to work at,
and left for the afterlife.
A hotel?
Only dead people like you
can visit that hotel.
You're working
at a very interesting hotel.
I'd like to go there too.
You can go there.
You'll be able to see it very well.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, I'm going to the hotel.
I thought you can't go there anymore.
I found a way.
Let's go.
Chan-sung has a lot of pride.
I wonder if he's going there to beg her.
That's not like him.
You're really weird too.
Why aren't you stopping him?
You came all the way here
because of Chan-sung.
You kept interrupting their date.
Why are you just letting him go?
I just
decided to give up.
What?
I wanted to make
Chan-sung come back to me,
but I figured I should just give up
once I met Jang Man-wol.
Why? Because she's rich?
Or because she's pretty?
I make good money, and I'm pretty too.
But I have a feeling
that I'm no match for her.
I wonder what's wrong with me.
Do I owe her something
in my previous life?
That's possible.
You owe a lot of money
in this life as well.
I'm going to pay everything back.
Plus, I hold our alumni reunion
at your restaurant.
I should check the group chat.
I'm also a member of that group chat,
and I'm the one who gathers everyone.
Why is she acting like
she does all the work?
Are you coming back from somewhere?
Yes.
Where's all my stuff?
They're not here yet?
Hyeon-jung and the intern
ran into ghosts on their way here.
They wish to bring them here as a guest.
I knew it.
They got sidetracked.
Hyeon-jung must've learned that
from Mr. Koo.
After what happened
to our guest in Room 13,
Mr. Koo could never be indifferent
to wandering ghosts.
Yes, you're right.
I brought her from the public restroom.
Do you want the red toilet paper
or the blue toilet paper?
Gosh, how long have you been saying that?
I think I heard it when I was young.
Come with me. You should take some rest.
Do you want the red toilet paper
or the blue toilet paper?
He was hovering by the crosswalk,
so I brought him here.
It's not that way. It's this way.
He's a coward
with such a soft heart.
Chan-sung?
The late chairman came to my house.
So I brought him here.
He told me that this hotel is
much more magnificent than mine.
So I thought I'd pay a visit.
This place is amazing.
You're here as our guest, so we'll do
our best to make you feel comfortable.
Ms. Choe.
Let me take you to your room.
Please follow me.
Chan-sung.
You really played it smart.
You coaxed him to find our hotel
and followed him here?
I did follow him here.
But I didn't coax him to find here.
I met him for another reason.
What reason?
Mr. Koo.
Call my secretary to settle things
regarding the painting.
They're planning to make
a memorial hall for me.
They'll pay you a good price for it.
Yes, sir.
What painting?
The painting of the Baekdu Mountain
that you gave me
because you thought it took up space.
You told me
that you couldn't sell it
for even a quarter of the price.
I just didn't sell it,
since the price of it would get higher
after the Chairman dies.
You should've told me then!
Then I wouldn't have--
No, you wouldn't.
Thanks for the severance pay.
You fraud.
I didn't lie to you.
I didn't expect you to abandon
both the painting...
and me.
-Let's split the money.
-I won't.
You greedy fraud from Harvard!
Okay, give me a quarter of the price.
No.
I'm not selling it
unless I get the full price to myself.
You had no idea how expensive it was
when you gave it to me.
You must have gone broke.
You're drinking makgeolli.
Whatever. Get out!
I'll sell the painting
and bring some cash.
Money is the best way to get her.
Welcome.
May I come in?
Of course.
Please come in.
What a friendly man.
Thank you.
Rich families must have
secret funds that nobody knows about.
Since they're filthy rich,
they often have money
that they forget to tell people about
before they die.
Perhaps it could be a Swiss bank account,
a secret account in Virgin Islands,
or maybe just a safe filled with money
buried in a sunflower field
or something. You got any?
Well, I don't know.
Take your time, and think carefully.
This is water.
Ms. Jang, we're in trouble.
Something that shouldn't be
inside the hotel is in here now.
The hotel is flooded with water.
What's come in here?
It passed by me when it came in.
It wasn't a soul of a human.
It was a deity disguised in the body
of a young man.
A deity?
I know what it is.
How did it get in here?
This area is controlled by Mago.
Other deities can't get inside
without permission.
Perhaps someone let it in.
I honestly thought it was
just a regular guest.
Who is it anyway?
It's the deity that takes care
of the well in this village.
A deity?
You mean like the mountain deity
in the folktale about golden axes?
Exactly. He is the Guardian of the Well.
How could you let such a thing in?
I had no idea.
I've never seen someone like that,
how was I supposed to know the difference?
It's because our hotel has just moved
and because Hyeon-jung is absent.
It's all your fault!
Yes, let's just say
that everything is my fault.
What should we do now?
Do I just tell him to get out?
You can't chase a deity away.
We can't tell him to get out
since we're the ones that let him in.
We have no choice but to serve him.
Why did the deity leave his well
and come all the way here?
Something must've bothered him.
It must be a disaster out there,
without the deity in his place.
Goodness.
It's going to get busy from next month.
Keep up the good work.
-Yes, sir.
It's quite hot outside today.
Boss, the water taps aren't working.
What? What do you mean?
-Why isn't water coming out?
-Exactly.
This is bad.
The well is dry.
What do we do?
-What's happened?
-How can this happen?
What's going on?
-It's all dry.
-How can this happen?
The well is the main water source
of the area,
so if it dries up, so will the makgeolli.
Why is my hotel flooded with the water
that should've been used to make
the makgeolli?
My beautifully-painted walls
will all get wet.
My walls are going to get mold.
They might even rot.
Ms. Choe is checking to see
what room he's staying in.
We can't kick him out,
but maybe we can convince him
to walk out on his own.
I'll go talk to him when we find him.
Do you have any idea
how scary angry deities are?
Back in the days, we even had to give
human sacrifices to calm them.
Maybe deities didn't ask humans
to do that,
but people just did that in fear.
Mr. Koo, why are you back here?
Didn't you meet Mago?
I found him.
He's staying in a room
on the eighth floor.
Prepare drinks and some food
to make him feel better.
He said that he doesn't need anything
except for one.
He wants Mr. Koo to come up to his room.
Why does he want Chan-sung?
I'm the owner. I'm going up.
No, he wants a living human.
Is he actually expecting
a human sacrifice?
Where are you going?
To catch humans.
What?
He's probably angry
because of the humans in this village.
I'll catch a few of them
and make them apologize to him.
-It's too dangerous.
-I don't care.
I won't send you in there.
I opened the door for him.
He thanked me.
I'm sure he wouldn't harm me.
I'll go see him.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
I'll just ask.
Don't people usually ask, "May I ask?"
Who's the old woman
that we saw at the hospital the other day?
You knew her, didn't you?
Yes, she's my younger sister.
What? Younger sister? That old woman?
She may have grown old,
but she's still my cute sister
who always smiled when she called me.
"Your cute sister"?
What's her name?
Hyeon-mi.
Ji Hyeon-jung's sister, Ji Hyeon-mi.
I should visit her
and ask if she remembers Hyeon-jung.
No.
Don't do it.
Don't visit her. I mean it.
Hey, do you think I'm someone
who would say something bad to a sister
of someone I like?
Darn it, this is awful.
Why did I say that
in this mountain full of ghosts?
I'm so stupid!
Be careful.
Are you okay?
Hyeon-jung.
I found him.
-Yu-na.
-Yes?
I don't think he's alone.
Look.
The fog is really thick.
Just in case you just wanted
to look bold earlier,
I'll stop you this once.
Chan-sung, do not go inside. Go back.
I look kind of cool
now that you're trying to stop me.
Forget it. You're a coward.
You can hardly look cool.
Just run away.
I did you a favor and let you go.
Why did you come back?
You gave me your time again.
It was one, two, three.
Three seconds.
If you just ask me to come back,
I can be there immediately.
For a short moment,
you wanted me to return.
This time, for three seconds.
How could I not come?
Do not smile. You're making me angry.
You aren't angry. You're worried.
Don't worry.
In my experience, I could tell
that the deities like me.
It must be because I'm weak-hearted.
Chan-sung!
Chan-sung.
Answer me. Chan-sung!
Goodness, what is this?
Are you here?
Guardian of the Well, are you in here?
Yes, you let me in here,
so I am very delighted.
I'm sorry, but this place isn't for you.
Please return to your place.
I do not wish to return.
What made you so furious?
If you tell me,
I will try my best to resolve it.
I do not wish to go back.
I do not wish to go.
What did you say?
I ran away from there.
I am scared.
I am scared of getting abandoned.
I've never dried up
and have given the people fresh water.
No matter how much they took,
I was filled up again.
I gave them water to make alcohol
and let them make money.
Please let our makgeolli business
become a success.
However, I can no longer fill up
as much water as they want.
I am continuously getting dried up.
I ran away before I dry up completely
and get abandoned
like an empty pond.
I chose to abandon them first
while they could still miss me.
What is it like to be
at the ugly bottom of my soul?
I am saddened.
I am sorry that I'm in a place
where I am not welcomed.
But I have nowhere else to go.
Please help me.
I'm a lowly diety, but I'll return
the favor for your help.
Since you saw my fears already,
I'll show you yours.
This will help you resolve your concerns.
Is that the moon?
Chan-sung.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I found a way.
We found another one, sir!
Move out of the way.
Today, five bodies that were buried
in secret
were found on a hill.
The police believe there might be
more bodies buried,
and are continuing their search.
According to the police, it'll take
-a few more days
-Here.
to identify the bodies,
and it'll take over a week
to find the causes of deaths.
There were serial murders.
They found five bodies.
Really? Gosh.
Bye.
Wait a minute. How did they find out?
We brought some guests.
-Drink up, guys.
-Here.
-Dig in.
-It's been a while.
It's delicious.
-This is expensive.
-You didn't change at all.
-Do you think so?
-Here.
You don't know Mi-ra, right?
I know I look young.
-Right?
-It's nice.
-Mi-ra, you can drink soda.
-Why?
-It's directly from the factory.
-Watch it.
Hey, guys.
Hello, Ji-won.
Hey, Ji-won!
-It's been a while.
-Hey.
-It's been so long.
-Hello.
-Hey, Ji-won!
-What is going on?
-You're still the same.
How did he come here?
What? I called him
since he wasn't on the invitee list.
Ji-won, sit here.
It's nice to see you.
Long time no see, Sanchez.
Yes.
I didn't know you'd show up here.
There's someone I wanted to see.
I heard Chan-sung is back in Korea too.
Yes, he's back.
I didn't know
you and Chan-sung were close.
Of course we are. I know him well.
He's a smart guy who's good at everything.
Is he still the same? I want to see him.
A chairman I was close to was
nice enough to provide
a small spring in his villa.
You'll be at peace here.
The makgeolli from that village
will taste different now.
They'll find a different source of water.
Even if the water's taste changes,
not many will notice it
as long as the label doesn't change.
Their makgeolli used to be so good.
It's upsetting and sad to think
I won't ever get to taste it again.
He was sad too.
He dried up the well as a punishment
because he was cross.
Now he's sad?
He told me he wasn't cross.
If he wanted to punish them,
he would've called on you
since you're stronger.
Why would he call on a weak human like me?
What did you see
at the bottom of the well?
Fear.
"Fear"?
For seeing his weakness,
he showed me
what I fear,
what I want to avoid
and run away from right now.
It was...
very scary.
Like how I could look into your dreams,
you were able
to see my fears, weren't you?
Just like how I helped the Guardian
of the Well move to a safe place,
you were
only trying to put me in a safe place.
You know what this is, don't you?
It looks like a medicine.
I thought it was strange
why Mago would suddenly give this to me.
You asked her to give it to me, right?
Think what you want.
Chan-sung.
I'll pray for your safety.
No.
I will get in danger
to make you feel uncomfortable.
What?
Chan-sung!
Do you know how precious that is?
Do you know
how much I had to beg to get that?
Jang Man-wol!
No place is safe for me anymore.
I will keep getting on your nerves
and get in danger.
You must...
keep protecting me.
But in fact, I was hoping you'd return.
I won't let you vanish.
Trust me.
You brought both that woman
and Yeon-u to me.
Thank you, Chan-sung.
If Chan-sung didn't take the medicine,
then he can probably see
the connections that were cut off.
It's the past I have been hiding.
Please get rid of it.
I brought a connection
from your past again.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu
You know what this is, don't you?
It looks like a medicine.
I thought it was strange
why Mago would suddenly give this to me.
You asked her to give it to me, right?
Think what you want.
Chan-sung.
I'll pray for your safety.
No.
I will get in danger
to make you feel uncomfortable.
What?
Chan-sung!
Do you know how precious that is?
Do you know
how much I had to beg to get that?
Jang Man-wol!
No place is safe for me anymore.
I will keep getting on your nerves
and get in danger.
You must...
keep protecting me.
Does this medicine belong to you?
It's yours, isn't it?
Why would you pick it up
and give it back to me now?
I thought you dropped it,
so I brought it back as a thank-you.
Thank you.
You brought back something
that's very precious.
You may go ahead and rest.
Isn't this something
that will help you get rid of your fears?
Well, yes.
Then, I hope you take it and feel at ease.
See?
Even the deity says
you should take the medicine.
He's very slow-witted.
He's giving you advice as someone
who ran away and found peace.
Eat it.
You must've forgotten something.
If you get attacked by a ghost that holds
a deep grudge, you could even die.
You almost died recently because of me.
Don't get yourself in trouble.
Just live peacefully.
Eat it.
If I eat that,
I won't be able to see you anymore.
You also must've forgotten something.
I can see through you.
If I don't take care of you,
you'll only end up becoming more spiteful.
I'd rather get myself in trouble
and stop you from ending up that way.
I...
I can't let that...
happen to you.
So,
I'm going to stay beside you
and keep an eye on you.
Mr. Koo Chan-sung?
What is it this time?
What brings you to my father's villa?
You asked my father for a favor
back when he was alive?
Yes, he let me borrow the pond
in his botanical garden.
Did you set free a pet fish or something?
It's something very special.
It'll give out a lot of good energy.
My father told me about you
a couple of times before he passed away.
That you helped him out a lot.
We're here to take care of his belongings.
I see.
BAEKGU
This is mine.
I spent a lot of time with him here
when I was a kid.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Look what I found in this book.
My goodness, when was this?
Father looks so young in this photo.
I miss him so much.
If you want,
you can write a letter and give it to me.
The hotel I work at provides
a special service where you can send
letters to the ones you miss.
I thought you would've already left,
but I guess you waited for me.
Because I don't like driving.
If you don't like driving,
why did you buy so many cars?
Because they're pretty.
I'm going to buy
every single car you sold.
With what money?
You said you're willing
to go through trouble,
so let me be a little cheap
while I'm at it.
Give me the painting of Baekdu Mountain.
Do you think I'll give that to you?
That was my severance pay.
I just dropped it at your place.
It's mine, so give it back.
There's a famous restaurant nearby
that once aired on TV.
Let's go there.
A famous restaurant?
It must be baffling to hear me
talk about food in this situation.
You must be feeling furious.
That's exactly how I felt.
Let's go.
If we don't get to the restaurant
before it closes because of you,
that painting of Baekdu Mountain
will never be yours.
Your favorite celebrity,
Kim Jun-hyun, came here as well.
Oh, right. You should take a photo.
THE GUYS WHO DIED AFTER EATING
I'LL VISIT EVERY FAMOUS RESTAURANT
IN THIS COUNTRY
There aren't any naengmyeon restaurants
or any shopping malls around here.
Why don't you just
come back to Myeong-dong?
This place is too far away from my house.
Just work at the hotel
you used to work at.
The owner of that hotel
seemed very fond of you earlier.
I'm just interested in being liked
by my current boss.
And to make that happen,
I'm going to challenge myself.
Promise that you'll reinstate me
if I eat this in one bite.
Are you serious?
Kim Jun-hyun can eat
the entire thing in one bite.
You're no match for him.
You'll never be able to do it.
Just give me my job back if I succeed.
Don't even bother.
I don't watch his shows anymore.
You used to like him so much.
You abandoned him as well?
Yes.
So if you succeed,
you should become a comedian
instead of coming back to my hotel.
Is it that easy to give up?
No, not really.
He's on almost every TV channel.
I hope the food here
tastes really horrible
so that I'll never think of it again.
THE GUYS WHO DIED AFTER EATING
I told you to park the car and go.
Why are you following me?
To make it hard for you
to give up on me.
But right now,
I'm here to meet the chairman.
His granddaughter asked me
to give this to him.
I'll give it to him.
No, how can I trust you?
I'll give it to him myself.
I'm the owner of this hotel,
and you recently got fired.
Ms. Jang.
Mr. Koo, I see you also came to work.
He's not the manager here.
He's just visiting.
Go ahead and meet the chairman.
I have something urgent to tell you.
Are you saying the guests
you guys brought were all murdered?
Yes, we saw them buried in the woods.
And there were no graves.
I called the police from a payphone.
It was on the news.
A number of corpses have been found.
Everyone says it's serial killing.
Judging from what the guests are saying,
it seems to be true that they were
all killed by the same person.
They all said it was a stranger to them,
but they all agreed
that it was a young man.
It's that guy.
I'm sure
the owner of that car is the killer.
I jotted down the license plate number.
-Let's find him and--
-Don't get involved.
Hyeon-jung already called the police,
and the fact that the bodies were found
was on the news.
Since the killer is alive,
the police can catch him.
All we have to do is take good care of
the dead victims until they can see that
and leave at peace.
Make sure to install a television
if they want to watch the news.
Give them access to our Wi-Fi network
so that they can search the web.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you okay?
The police will catch him.
Hyeon-jung, you called the police,
so the cops must be so confused now.
The call was made from this payphone,
but no one was caught
on the security camera over there.
Was it a ghost?
It's so odd.
Ghosts don't exist.
What's odder to me is
how payphones like this still exist.
Do you have any change?
Oh, yes. Just a second.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'll give you this in return.
It's all right.
Gosh, no. If you lose this,
you'll stay a bachelor.
For the rest of your life.
Forever.
You won't even be able to date anyone.
Don't ever lose it.
Hey.
Right, yes.
Wait, ma'am.
What was that about?
For the rest of your life.
Forever.
DEAR GRANDFATHER WHOM I MISS DEARLY
I'M SO HAPPY I CAN WRITE YOU A LETTER
Your granddaughter is
very sad about not being by your side
in your final moments.
She was studying abroad at the time.
I get to see her like this.
I owe it all to you.
I guess you rode your motorcycle earlier.
That suits you.
You think so?
I never got to do this when I was alive,
thinking it'd be frowned upon.
Thanks to you,
I get to enjoy this as well.
I'm glad to see you happy.
Isn't my granddaughter so pretty?
Yes, she is.
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-Pardon?
My granddaughter doesn't have
a boyfriend yet.
Her name is Jeong Ji-eun. She's 25.
She's just been studying,
so she can't pick out good guys.
I always wanted to find
a nice, reliable guy for her.
Oh, I see.
I'm sure she'll meet
a wonderful man. Don't worry.
I'll be off, then.
Chan-sung doesn't have a girlfriend.
You seemed curious
about that nice, reliable guy.
Is that so?
Then shall I tell you more
about Chan-sung?
Shall I tell Chan-sung
to take care of this since he's here?
Forget it.
Ms. Jang, there you are.
What is it?
I curried favor with Chairman Wang
as per your order.
Good. So have you found out anything?
He entrusted me
with taking care of something
that is still bothering him very much.
Look at you. Well done, Seon-bi.
You sure are a capable man.
Once again, you proved
to be such a useful asset.
Chairman Wang
has a granddaughter
that he absolutely adores.
He's still upset
that he couldn't find a nice guy for her,
so I promised him
I'll hook her up with a nice guy.
You'll find a guy for her!
Great. If all goes well,
he'll buy you a nice suit.
He's a chairman. He won't stop there.
You're absolutely right.
You'll find a nice guy
for his granddaughter.
He'll have to take care of this
for us at the very least.
You have nothing to worry about now.
I knew it.
You're the ace of our hotel,
without a doubt.
And Chairman Wang really likes
the guy I recommended.
My gosh, Mr. Kim.
I'm sure all the work at the bar
keeps you busy enough.
When did you have time to go out,
meet people, and recommend someone?
I don't have time to meet new people.
I only know one guy.
What?
I recommended Koo Chan-sung.
You mean the manager of our hotel,
Koo Chan-sung?
He's no longer our manager.
I know it's been bothering you as well.
Let's marry him off to the granddaughter.
He won't ignore us if he marries
into that rich family thanks to us.
We'll get money from Chairman Wang
and Chan-sung.
We'll kill two birds with one stone.
Did he leave already?
I have to give him
the granddaughter's number.
Just trust me.
Where did he go?
That dunderhead.
Did Mr. Koo leave?
No, I didn't see him leaving.
That means he's still here.
All right, catch you later.
TO MS. JANG MAN-WOL, I LOVE YOU
She still has this.
-You're still here.
-I will leave soon.
Mr. Koo?
What is going on?
Is he in Ms. Jang's office?
Mr. Koo!
He's not here.
What's the matter?
I have to...
My gosh.
Would he be in the garden?
What's with him? Goodness.
Do we have to stay like this?
Why do we have to do this?
You don't like money, right?
You prefer plain things
over fancy things.
You love that tacky poop...
I mean, you like dull colors like brown.
Right?
Is this your way of pressuring me to
give you the painting of Baekdu Mountain?
Now I see.
You are greedy for money.
Yes, I am. I want to make a lot of money.
Is being money-grubbing
something to brag about?
Is that what they taught you at Harvard?
Yes, MBA programs teach you
how you can earn money.
Okay, you show-off.
You greedy fraud from Harvard.
-What--
-I hope you become filthy rich.
Then own a hotel!
Get out!
Why...
She's so mad at me
for not giving her the painting.
Jang Man-wol.
I'll give you back
the painting of Baekdu Mountain.
And as for the medicine,
you should keep it.
It'll be the last way
for me to run away
and for you to abandon me.
I'll wait for your call
to reinstate me back at the hotel.
And the meal we had today.
I enjoyed it.
Let's...
go and have another meal there.
My wife hasn't been home
for several days now.
That's why I'm calling you.
If she calls you,
please tell her that I'm sorry.
Please tell her to come back home.
Thank you.
Gosh.
No!
Honey!
Oh, no!
What happened to you? What is this? Honey.
What happened to you? Honey.
What...
What is this? Why...
Wait. Why...
It's just like the tip.
There's a body here.
You're under arrest for murdering
your wife, Lee Do-yeon.
-I didn't kill her.
-You have the right to remain silent.
And you have the right to an attorney.
What about the shovel?
Get the shovel. The one with dirt on it.
There you go. That's it.
You ought to arrest a serial killer.
Bye.
Darn it.
Why do you hate Seol Ji-won so much?
Did something happen
between you and him in the States?
Not between just the two of us.
Among three people.
Chan-sung was involved too?
It was after you went back to Korea.
A Korean international student
committed suicide in Boston.
But there was a ridiculous rumor
she killed herself because of me.
What? Because of you?
No way. Who would believe that?
People did.
That ridiculous rumor snowballed.
Later, people said that
I was a rich piece of trash
who toyed with the poor
International student and made her
do something nasty with foreign friends.
Afterward, on an online forum,
people started to bet
on whether I'd kill myself or not.
And the guy who set up the whole thing...
Seol Ji-won?
It's you, isn't it?
You're the one who spread
the rumor about Jae-in.
I just said
that I saw you invite her to the party
you had with rich European friends.
She...
She came to work as a waitress.
She said she needed money for her tuition,
-so I got her a job--
-She could have done something else.
Don't get so worked up
because no one will believe you.
Actually, everyone was fed up
with your righteous acts as a rich guy.
Keep your chin up.
I made a bet that you'd live.
What are you doing here?
I've been looking all over for you.
Let's go eat.
When I was in misery
and almost thought about dying,
Chan-sung came to me.
That day, he took the box with the gun
and went to see Seol Ji-won.
After that, Seol Ji-won went back
to Korea all of a sudden.
What did Chan-sung do that day?
I don't know that either.
Well, anyway, after that,
he always found me to have a meal with me
until the rumor died down.
That's how you two got so close.
Who threw these out?
Today's not the day. It's tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
Chan-sung, I brought
some pizza for you. Go wash up.
Thank you.
The recycling trash goes out on Saturdays.
Don't tell Chan-sung that we met
Seol Ji-won at the gathering today.
I don't want Chan-sung to have
anything to do with that jerk.
Okay. I won't tell him.
It's my loss. There's no guy
better than Chan-sung.
I think Chan-sung would make
the best grandson-in-law.
I understand that you like Chan-sung,
but you have already passed away.
How can you pass on your message
to your granddaughter?
That brings me to my next point.
I'd like to make
a special request to your hotel.
The bartender told me all about it.
I heard that your hotel provides
a dream call service
where the dead can talk
to the living in their dreams.
I heard that I could pay you
with the money from this world.
I just remembered an asset
I forgot to take care of.
Grandpa.
You received my photo?
The guy who gave me this photo is
really my cup of tea.
Mr. Koo Chan-sung?
That's right.
I really hope that young man
can be your husband.
Let me tell you about the guy.
Your time is up.
It was very expensive to make this call.
Is it supposed to be this short?
Then, why don't you make another call?
The rule says
you can only make a call a day.
You must think about other guests too.
But I think you told her
all the important parts.
Ms. Jang, will Mr. Koo really
marry into the wealthy family?
Kids these days
rarely listen to old people.
She never listened to her grandfather.
Why would she now?
My grandfather came to me
in my dream last night.
He told me that he received my photo.
Really? You must've been happy.
Also,
he told me something else.
I really hope that young man
can be your husband.
Use this.
Could you please clean this for us?
Thank you.
Mr. Koo?
Have you eaten?
I'd like to talk more
about my grandfather with you.
Sure, let's grab a bite to eat.
What do you like?
Here he comes!
Did you really murder your wife?
Why did you kill the others
that were buried?
Are there any more victims?
What was the reason behind these murders?
-Is there an accomplice?
-Are there any more victims?
-Please say a few words.
-Any words?
-Over here!
-Sir!
MAN ARRESTED FOR MURDERING HIS WIFE
That's not right.
The guy had a smaller build.
What guy?
I don't think this man is the killer.
All we have to do is find the car 0963.
What? 0963?
Did you memorize the license plate number?
Yes.
Forget it like you forget English words.
Darn.
My friend owns the place,
and the food is quite tasty.
-It's Mr. Koo.
-Sanchez!
-How have you been?
-And you?
-Do you know Sanchez?
-We're in the same yacht club.
-It's been a while.
-Really?
What a coincidence.
-I should visit there sometime.
-You won't be allowed in.
That's not true.
You could if you had a hotel of your own.
I was going to talk
about the car with Mr. Koo,
but he seems busy.
Actually, he doesn't
work at the hotel anymore.
What?
-He'll marry into a rich family.
-I can use my experience
as a hotel manager
to greet the members
and help with their baggage.
-That's nice.
-And see them off later.
KOO CHAN-SUNG
I'll wait for your call
to reinstate me back at the hotel.
Ms. Jang!
They met!
The blind date happened.
What? They met?
I saw Mr. Koo meeting
Chairman Wang's granddaughter.
I haven't seen him smile so widely before.
Of course.
Who knew he had such an ambition?
I'm not sure about that.
He's always been the friendly type.
You should see for yourself then.
They agreed to meet tomorrow as well.
Mr. Koo invited her over to his house.
That means
she's going to meet Mr. Koo's parents.
Mr. Koo's father passed away, remember?
I'm not sure about his mother.
Is his mother still alive?
How should I know?
You're always bitter when this comes up.
Anyway, wouldn't it be great
if this leads to Koo Chan-sung
getting his own family?
You know how warm he's been to our guests.
This must be the work of good karma.
And I'm so happy for him.
Is that so?
May he be full of luck then.
Are you cleaning
because Ji-eun is coming tomorrow?
Yes, it should be clean.
Dating someone else
will help him forget about Man-wol.
Still, he plays it big.
He only goes for a woman
who has a hotel of her own.
There's a book here
that's haunted by a ghost.
That's ridiculous.
My cousin's a librarian here,
and she told me.
The ghost that donated it
comes along whenever you pull it out.
Sounds like fun.
Where's the book?
Let's post it on social media.
-This way?
-Yes.
Okay, I'm filming.
-Pull it out.
-Got it.
It won't come out. I'm not kidding!
-Come on already.
-It really must be haunted.
What's wrong?
Seol? Are you all right?
Seol?
Hey! Are you all right?
EXISTENCE AND TIME
Are you all right? Seol, wake up!
Come on. Please.
Wake up.
If Chan-sung hasn't taken the medicine,
then he can probably see
the connections that were cut off.
It's the side effect of
being able to see ghosts.
I hear you made two incompatible souls
cross their paths.
It's always fun to make enemies
of previous lives meet again.
They're drawn to each other
because of leftover feelings.
My goodness.
How pretty!
-Are you getting in?
-Yes.
Excuse me.
Is this yours?
Thank you.
Look.
Just look at this.
This is all because of your pen.
This is brand new, you know.
I'm terribly sorry. What can I do?
You can pay for the dry-cleaning.
I'm busy today,
so give me your number instead.
Sorry?
Hold on.
This ink is black.
You're right. It's very black
even though it's pink on the outside.
Forget it then.
Excuse me.
This pen is important to me,
so let me pay for the cleaning
for getting it back to me.
May I have your number?
Sure thing.
So this is the library
the chairman established.
Yes, this must be
why my grandfather came to me
in my dream.
I wanted this would happen
the moment I met you too.
I'm sure my grandfather
will be very happy.
Shall we go?
Are you happy now?
They make a nice couple.
Then, as you promised,
I will keep that money.
You can keep watching them here.
You are so pretty.
You are like a princess.
Really?
-I hardly recognized you.
-Thanks.
How is your mother?
She is healthy and doing well.
-Good. I need to visit her.
-Yes.
This is Koo Chan-sung.
Hello.
Nice to meet you. I am Koo Chan-sung.
Jang Man-wol.
Why are you here?
Chairman Wang wanted to see
his granddaughter.
He paid a high price for the dream call,
so this is a special service.
You can ignore this and go.
Since you are here,
why don't you look around the library?
There are many good books
and nice paintings here.
Forget it.
I'm going back.
Come on. Take a look around the library.
There's a nice painting here.
I sold this.
If we waited for the memorial hall
to be built,
you'd probably collapse first.
So his granddaughter and I decided
to hang it here.
I came here to sell this.
What did you come to sell?
What kind of a deal did you make
with the chairman without me?
And the "high price for the dream call"?
You don't need to know.
There are many good paintings here?
Why don't we look at them?
How much did you rip off
from the chairman?
Just a little. Very little.
Actually,
that's the chairman's painting as well.
I feel a bit like committing fraud.
You are a greedy fraud
from Harvard anyway.
A fraud?
You keep calling me that. Take it back.
-I don't want to.
-You don't want to?
That's not what matters.
Take back what you said.
That guy called Chan-sung
seemed nice.
Are you seeing him?
I wanted to.
He told me there is someone else.
The cafeteria of this library
is not bad at all.
Isn't it?
I came here often with my father
when I was young.
The food was also good then.
Did you live around here back then?
Father wanted to send me
to an elementary school around here.
The rent in this neighborhood was so high
that we couldn't get a room.
But we came here often.
Because the food was cheap and tasty.
Did you only live with your father
from the start?
Yes. The reason my name is Chan-sung is
that the only person who wanted
me to be born was my father.
He felt bad about that
so he named me Chan-sung.
But he didn't know
Chinese characters very well.
So my name means a brilliant star.
The reason your father sold you
was not to save himself.
It was because of you.
Because you would be alone without him.
Of course I know that.
He was my only family.
If you are finished,
let's go and read some books.
Books?
I can't do that in this condition.
-Why?
-My clothes don't suit books.
What's that got to do with books?
It has everything to do with them.
Look.
I have to take a photo at the library
to post it on my social media.
What I'm wearing isn't appropriate.
God...
Have some coffee and wait for me.
I'll get changed and come right back.
There's no need for that. Sit down.
I didn't mean to go to read books.
I want us to find the ghost
attached to a book.
There is a rumor
that there is a ghost around here.
The director of the library
is very worried.
If there really is a ghost,
we should take it to the hotel.
There is a book with a ghost?
Yes.
The rumor is that the ghost
donated the book before.
She was an elementary school principal
and she died not long ago.
Her family donated her books.
The book must have been precious to her.
I don't know.
Most people easily throw away
things they used to care about.
They protect things they want
to hide with their life.
That ghost must have got nervous
when so many people came
to pull the book out because of the rumor.
What's there to hide in the book?
It's probably her emergency money.
Gosh.
She speeds up only when it's about money.
You're the human, so you pull it out.
The ghost won't come out if I do.
Existence and Time.
Nobody would want to read a book
with that title and look.
I read it.
I'm sure you did.
Since you're such a smarty-pants,
Koo Chan-sung.
You're so great.
Right. I read it to show off.
But it was difficult to understand.
I've been alive for over 1,000 years,
trying to kill time.
Even I don't know
what is existence or time.
You've only lived for about 30 years,
so how could you know?
Let's see what this book tells
about the time.
The ghost might not appear if I'm here.
I'll be near the bookshelf in the back.
You can see me?
Yes, I can see you.
What are you doing here?
I don't want anyone to read this book.
Is there something you cherish
in this book?
Or is it something you want to hide?
Can you get rid of something
inside the book?
I will help you.
To do that, I have to take out the book.
It's the past I have been hiding.
My family must not find out about it.
Please get rid of it.
The lady we just saw...
I think she's my mother.
I have never seen her.
I didn't even know she passed away.
I didn't know
my father sent these photos to her.
CHAN-SUNG AND I ARE GOING TO THE US
It wasn't something she cherished.
It was something she wanted to hide.
I guess...
she really didn't want me to be born.
You volunteered to go through trouble.
That's why you ended up
finding out about this.
It's just useless and upsetting.
What? Am I wrong?
Are you going to say you felt happy
to see your mother?
Do you want to take her to the hotel,
so you could be a filial son?
Do you think I'd want to do that?
Good.
Give me that. Let me put it back.
We'll just let that ghost
stay there forever.
That's not...
what I want either.
Then what do you want?
You ended up going through this
because I made you see ghosts,
-I should at least do something for you.
-I'm just sad...
that I wasn't able to feel happy
when I got to meet my mom...
for the first time.
Just let me grieve for now.
Never mind. Just go.
Did something happen?
Why do you look so upset?
Well...
I just feel a little sad.
I'm glad you're here. I'll cheer you up.
Let's go. I'll buy you a drink.
Hey, you lost a button.
Where did you lose it?
You're making me feel sorry for you.
Was she trying to console me?
Sanchez.
Hey, Mi-ra. I was just about
to leave with Chan-sung.
What? Chan-sung's here?
I don't think you can join us today.
You'll have to eat alone.
I have company.
Someone will be here to eat with me.
-Really?
-Yes.
Gosh, this place is nice.
What's going on?
Chan-sung, say hello. He's Park Yeong-su.
I helped him find something
that means a lot to him.
So he's treating me to a meal.
He died...
because of you.
What?
I know, right? His looks are to die for.
My gosh, Mi-ra.
He's a cop.
I heard you're going to leave
with Sanchez.
See you later.
What's wrong? Do you know him?
No, I don't know him.
But Jang Man-wol does.
Man-wol?
Does he know her too?
No, he probably doesn't.
Sanchez, I don't think
I can drink today. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Tell me if Chan-sung ever told you
anything personal about his life.
Does he have any relatives
that he keeps in touch with?
What about his friends? Who else is
he friends with other than Sanchez?
No one knows anything? Seriously?
Mr. Koo always stuck by your side...
I mean, he always spent time with you.
Don't you know anything?
It's natural that I don't know since I'm
his boss, but his colleagues should.
How can you be so indifferent
to your colleague?
Seon-bi.
You even recommended him to the chairman,
and yet you know nothing?
I only recommended him
because he has a kind heart--
Hyeon-jung,
weren't you pretty close to him?
Well, from what I remember,
Mr. Koo
likes the color brown.
Even I know that.
The Grim Reaper's here.
Will you stop nagging at them?
You don't seem to know anything either.
What about you then? Do you know anything?
You saw him very often.
I get that you guys are ghosts,
but you're all so cold-hearted.
Ms. Jang,
why don't you just ask him yourself?
He's here.
I thought you'd be sad for a long time.
I guess you're okay already.
I'm not okay yet.
But I came because of you.
Because of me?
I think...
I stirred up your existence and time
this time.
I met someone from your painful memory.
BEOMCHEON CENTRAL POLICE STATION
He used to be a thief.
But now, he's a cop.
You're living a good life again.
I'm glad.
What a relief.
Do you want to go
and talk to him?
No.
I'm nobody to him.
He was like a family to you.
Will you be okay?
I won't be okay.
It's a bit sad.
I brought a connection
from your past again.
Thank you.
Chan-sung.
-Let me see.
-Gosh. No.
The serial murder case.
You got the analysis report
on the dirt from the shovel, right?
Pardon?
Yes, the dirt is the same as that of
the hill where the bodies were found.
Right?
But why does that suspect keep denying
that he killed them?
This is giving me a headache.
But the thing is
he doesn't have any motives
other than his wife's murder.
He's a typical psychopath.
A murder fanatic.
The end.
So there's a problem with the stuff
the truck was carrying that day.
Everything arrived without a problem.
Check the name
of the reservation one more time.
The reservation with the truck, 3465,
was made
under Koo Chan-sung.
-Who?
-Isn't this Mr. Koo Chan-sung?
Koo Chan-sung?
No way.
Koo Chan-sung.
Why am I running into you here?
Chan-sung.
Are you staying home today again?
-Yes.
-You're not going to the hotel?
You kept going there
and said you'd be reinstated.
I have unfinished business here.
I don't think
I can take care of the hotel guests
if I go in this state.
EXISTENCE AND TIME
Will I find an answer
once I'm done with this difficult book?
A way to console a guy
whose existence
and time he spent with his mom
have completely been denied.
Are you worried that the secret
you've been hiding would be exposed?
Don't worry.
Your son doesn't want that.
He's sad.
And I want to console him.
I need you.
I will
escort you to my hotel.
Reinstated.
Come to the hotel. Take Line Four.
A guest you must send off is waiting.
A guest I must send off?
Mr. Koo, congratulations
on your reinstatement.
You came back to Myeong-dong.
I like this place
way more than the other place.
I look forward to working with you again.
I thought he would marry
into the rich family.
He came back to this hotel of ghosts.
How could a man have no ambition?
Ms. Jang needs Mr. Koo.
Ambitious men aren't popular among ladies.
You're so behind the times.
Besides, I told you to stop
talking like a dinosaur.
I did change the way I talk.
Right? Gosh.
I'm sorry for having kept you waiting.
Thank you for coming.
May I keep
the photos from the book?
Could you do that?
I'm very...
sorry.
Goodbye.
Mother.
Did you see her off?
Yes.
I'm sorry I took the liberty
of bringing her here.
Thank you for bringing her here.
Also
for telling me to return.
It's embarrassing for me to say this,
but let's get things straight.
You didn't return because I told you to.
You did it for me.
I could've forced you to eat the medicine
so you could never return,
but I didn't do that.
I thought you returned as you pleased
every time I gave you a chance
to run away.
But in fact,
I was hoping you'd return.
I'm glad to hear you admit
that I wasn't the only clingy one,
wanting to return.
Chan-sung.
I'm going to use you.
You brought both that woman and Yeon-u
to me.
Which means
you'll bring him too.
Yes, probably.
I'm certain that you will.
And
I will never let him
pass by unscathed.
That's why you'll use me?
That's right. I'll be vicious and cunning.
And you may end up
being used, abused, and wrecked
because of me.
Are you...
-threatening me again to make me run--
-No.
Don't run away.
You've already made up your mind
to get on my nerves and get in danger.
Knowing that such danger
could lead to death,
stay by my side.
Even if I...
go berserk, do crazy things,
and vanish one day...
please stay by my side.
No.
I won't let you vanish.
Trust me.
It must be pretty hard
to miss something you can't see.
You, I'm going easy on you
because you have a soft heart.
You probably saw the flowers.
Why aren't you saying anything?
We have to go before Ms. Jang does,
so let's prepare ourselves for that day.
They look so pretty now.
Why must they fall?
It's sad.
Flowers bloom
only to fall.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu