Hotel Del Luna Blu-ray Disc 7
Subtitle re-timing by Jharel
My gosh, are you that sleepy?
-Is it the intern?
-Yes.
Yu-na needs to get her homework done,
but she was so sleepy.
So I was trying to keep her awake.
Hyeon-jung.
Does Yu-na know
that you're planning to leave
with your younger sister after she dies?
No, she doesn't know that yet.
I only told her that
I was waiting for her.
I see.
-Welcome.
-Welcome, sir.
Do you remember
how long it's been since you died?
I can't remember for sure.
Maybe about two days.
-Then--
-Sir.
Let me escort you.
Come this way.
Sir.
Are you Yun Seung-beom,
the eldest grandson
of the Yeongju Yun family
who used to live in Beomcheon City?
And you're 42 years old.
Yes, that's right.
You're still single, aren't you?
Yes.
I wasn't able to get married.
I see.
Your family must be devastated
since the succeeding grandson
of the family died
without even having any children.
Ms. Choe.
I thought you were Ms. Jang for a second.
Why are you all dressed up?
Mr. Kim, I think
I'll be able to leave here soon.
I'm on my way to relieve
my 200-year-long resentment.
Are you saying...
He's dead.
The very last son of that family died
and came here as a guest.
The family tree
of that darn family
has finally come to an end.
I'm on my way to his funeral
so I can witness the Yeongju Yun family
shed tears of blood.
Ms. Choe.
You can't cause an incident
like 42 years ago.
I went there because I was furious.
But now, I'm going there
because I'm happy.
Sanchez is still at the restaurant.
So all I need to do is face Sanchez
and say that I'm sorry, right?
I can be so much more apologetic
with a shot of alcohol.
This is sparkling water.
Think of it as champagne, and drink it.
It's quite bubbly. Do you have soju?
Mix some soju in it.
Let's see if it's any good.
If it's good, you will drink this
instead of champagne.
Taking away champagne and caviar
from me is the same thing
as taking away the hot sauce and pickles
from pizza.
And pizza reminds me of Sanchez.
I wonder if he's doing okay.
All right. Fine. Let's go shopping
before the department store closes.
Why is this conversation ending
with shopping?
I'm supposed to apologize to him.
Instead of going there empty-handed
and saying, "I'm sorry, Sanchez,"
buying something beautiful
and saying, "I'm sorry, Sanchez"
would be much better.
You just want to go shopping.
All you need to tell Sanchez is
that Veronica left this world
and you saw her off
at the bridge to the afterlife.
"The bridge to the afterlife"?
How could I see her off at the bridge
that I haven't been to myself?
You've never been to the bridge
over the Samdo River?
I wouldn't be here if I had been there.
The moment you step foot on the bridge,
it's impossible to return from it.
Well,
I can tell him that his girlfriend is
crossing that bridge about now.
She's still on the bridge?
Is the bridge that long?
Time runs at a different speed there.
It doesn't take very long
to cross the bridge to the afterlife,
but it's equivalent
to 49 days in this world.
While the deceased cross the bridge,
they forget their memories of this world
one by one.
It's not that they are forced
to stay in the afterlife.
They don't come back
because all of their memories are gone.
I'm pretty sure Sanchez's girlfriend is
crossing the bridge right now,
and her memories about him are
getting erased one by one.
It's a bitter story
for those left behind.
Chan-sung.
I can promise you one thing.
I'm 1,300 years old.
And when I end up crossing that bridge,
a lot of my memories will disappear.
But I'll keep the memories of you
to the end.
Well, I can't promise
that I'll remember you in the afterlife.
But until I take my last step
on the bridge,
I'll remember you.
Okay.
I'm sure you can do it,
given your experience of 1,300 years.
I'll believe in you.
But what will you remember me by?
You were worried many times
that I might reincarnate
as a dog or a pig.
You sold off all of my cars,
stopped me from buying yachts,
and took away my credit cards.
You suggested that I should drink
sparkling water instead of champagne.
My gosh, I only remember
these absurd things.
I've done a lot for you.
And especially, I won't be able to forget
about your bragging.
I might remember the word Harvard
instead of your name,
Koo Chan-sung, in my last moment.
This is mine.
Yes, I was going to order it again
since you liked the fragrance.
But the seller disappeared.
I brought it, so I can look into it.
All right. I thought you stole it
from the hotel.
That might be the case.
Just in case, look around to see
if any of this stuff is yours.
Did you really steal from my hotel?
Look thoroughly
if you see your stuff here.
It's right here. It's yours.
I'm stamping this into your memory.
I like it when you remember me
by Harvard, a nasty manager, and such,
but...
don't forget a man
who's smiling at you now.
Yes.
Remember these moments.
It looks like
Sanchez will be coming home late.
We should go to him.
This is Hyeon-jung.
After some man came into the hotel
as our guest,
Ms. Choe didn't look so good.
I found out that the guest was
the last son of the family
that Ms. Choe loathes so much.
She went to that man's funeral?
Yes.
Mr. Kim is really worried about her too.
Ms. Jang.
The incident that happened 42 years ago
won't happen again, right?
What happened 42 years ago?
The room service manager, Choe Seo-hui,
left the hotel and almost became
an evil ghost that had to be eliminated.
That level-headed Ms. Choe?
Her daughter was the reason why
she loathes that family so much.
And that darn family
messed with her daughter's grave.
This is the site.
The grave of a girl who passed away
on the 25th of this month
is harming your family and your child.
You must dig it out and get rid of it
for your daughter-in-law
to give birth to a healthy baby
who is in an inverted position now.
You're not supposed to mess
with an old grave of a girl.
My family line is about to run dry.
Dig out the grave.
Stop it.
Don't you dare touch my daughter's grave.
I curse all of your family
to die. All of you.
I will make sure
your family line ends here.
Die!
If she had faced Mago
before the Grim Reaper got a hold of her,
Ms. Choe would have ceased to exist.
That day, the Grim Reaper
and Ms. Jang worked out a nice deal,
so Ms. Choe didn't get dragged
to the afterlife
and could continue to work at the hotel.
We made an offering of flowers
for ten months, right?
It was for twelve months.
Right.
The flowers in the garden all wilted then.
The manager before Ms. Hwang
lost all of Ms. Jang's money.
We were the poorest then.
You know what Ms. Jang did?
Whenever I think about Ms. Jang
digging up arrowroots with a hoe...
Hey.
Don't think about it.
Yes, ma'am.
The son who was born 42 years ago
died without having a son.
Nothing will happen even if she meets
the people from that family
at the funeral, right?
What she's been wishing for
for 200 years is happening.
I doubt anything will happen.
Then, that means Ms. Choe will leave soon.
Are you finished?
The end has come to this family.
I'll be able to leave without any regrets.
You're here.
Yes, he's the father of my baby.
I thought I should at least
come to say goodbye.
Didn't you say he was a bachelor?
I guess
he left an offspring.
If the child in that woman's belly
is a boy,
the Yeongju Yun family line
will be carried on.
I'm sorry I left my post unattended
without informing you.
What happened?
There's still one more child
in that family.
Ms. Choe...
Is there anyone inside?
A baby is dying. Please open the door!
Please open this door.
Please open the door.
No doctors will open their doors for you.
That baby must not live.
My baby...
Please save my child.
I asked the guest from the family
and he said that a lover he broke up with
because of his parents
is pregnant.
That's why he couldn't go straight
to the afterlife.
Ms. Choe must be disappointed.
I feel sorry for that man,
but no one can compare to Ms. Choe
who remained here for 200 years
because of the sorrow of losing her child.
I know the flower is withering.
Can't it be stopped?
I think Ms. Choe is more anxious
than anyone.
I was really worried.
Did you think I'd harm someone?
I was worried you might get hurt.
That's no concern of yours.
Where did you get that strange suit?
It's a tiger.
Where did you find such a thing?
I got it as a gift,
so I tried it on today.
What do you think?
You look funny. What on earth is that?
Take it off already.
I hear it's a brand name suit.
Who cares if it's a brand name suit?
You look like you are from the Serengeti.
Does it look that strange?
I guess I shouldn't wear it outside.
Of course not.
Even our dead guests will laugh at you.
Should I wear it
when I see our guests off?
They can laugh on their way out.
Mr. Koo, you're bringing down
our hotel's class.
Right. Did the guest
in Room 403 leave yet?
I should see him out.
He said he should see you before leaving.
Let's head to the platform.
You're not really going to wear that,
are you?
Let's go together, Ms. Choe.
Stay away from me.
I think Mr. Koo decided to look funny
to divert Ms. Choe from that family
and help her relax.
He said he'd never wear it,
but he's using it like this.
Ms. Jang.
I looked into why my matchmaking
for Mr. Koo didn't work out,
and it turned out
his heart belonged to someone else.
Someone who won the heart
of such a man must be happy.
Yes. I'm happy.
Why are you happy?
Now that you know,
don't do something a crane would do.
I'm calling you a crane because you hate
being called a birdbrain.
Don't act like a crane.
This must be a crane-like question,
but do you also feel...
You asked me
if we can't stop the flowers from falling.
That's not possible.
I wonder if it's because
I like him too much.
I just can't seem to stop it.
I feel sorry for you too, Mr. Kim.
The flowers are falling because of love...
Should I give you a glass of Tears?
No.
I don't like it.
It tastes really bad.
She's been consistently rude.
How did he change her?
Chan-sung.
What is this?
Why did you get changed already?
I was going to take a picture
of you in that suit.
Thanks to you, I was able to use it well.
But I don't want to leave a picture of it.
Why not? It was totally my cup of tea.
I'll buy you a zebra-print suit next time.
Suit yourself. You can turn me
into a tiger or a zebra.
You were really cool.
The tiger in front of Ms. Choe
was cooler than the Siberian tiger.
Koo Chan-sung,
you're an excellent hotelier.
I forgot
that Ms. Choe was also a guest
who needed to be consoled
in order for her to leave here.
She's a long-term guest
with a deep-rooted resentment.
Her resentment which is making her wait
to see the end of the Yun family
might turn into a curse?
Just as she wanted,
that family is facing a problem.
I told you everything comes
with a price, right?
For making her feel so much sorrow,
they received a curse.
But it's been 200 years already.
Time doesn't mean anything to the dead.
With such resentment,
one could spend 200 years,
or 500 years,
or even 1,000 years.
They wait for a long time
not knowing when their hearts
will open up again.
I guess it could be considered
a curse too.
Are you...
still waiting for him to come?
Chan-sung.
If he comes,
will you do what you did
for Ms. Choe for me too?
Will you become a tiger?
I told you to trust me.
Anything is possible.
Since I'm yours.
Right.
Then you wear that.
And we will go to eat beef short rib soup
that tigers love.
You said tigers like red bean porridge.
Who said that?
You did.
That tigers love red bean porridge.
No tigers like red bean porridge.
You think they're vegetarians?
You have to get them some beef at least.
All right. Let's go and have some soup.
Let's put this on.
I will not.
If you don't wear this,
I will take all your clothes off.
Do as you please.
But will you be able to handle it?
I don't think so.
Let's have the soup tomorrow.
I have to go home and see Sanchez.
What are you doing?
You don't have to know.
They are flowers that fall
because of love.
There are still so many flowers.
It took more than 1,000 years
for them to bloom.
I don't think they'll fall that easily.
Look, it's a firefly.
I saw it from time to time
after the tree changed.
See? Even a firefly comes
now that the flowers have bloomed.
But can something like that come in here?
I don't know.
Since it's inside the hotel,
it can't be alive.
Is that what Mr. Koo was talking about?
What?
He asked me once
if there could be a soul
that looks like a firefly.
Why is there only one? It must be lonely.
He's spent all those years,
unable to show himself.
He's always been with her like a dust.
Now finally, he will be seen.
The flowers have finally bloomed.
I wonder if she'll be willing to listen
to his side of the story.
When things in one's heart are entangled,
it's so hard to untangle them.
I will weave them properly this time.
I ate too much soup.
I feel so bloated.
I know that's just an excuse
to come here to see her.
The baby she is carrying
is the child of the family
Ms. Choe hates, right?
Right. She thought the family line
finally ended.
But it continues persistently.
And that's the baby
who disappointed Ms. Choe.
If only that child disappears,
Ms. Choe's deep grudge will be resolved.
Do you really think so?
If the child disappears,
will that solve everything?
Shall I get rid of that baby right now?
The baby doesn't seem to be
in good condition anyway.
Are you all right?
My stomach was tightening.
You should be careful. I will help you.
She is Ms. Choe's enemy.
Why is he helping her?
What is this?
This is a nice car. I wanted to buy this.
Just because you have an expensive car,
doesn't mean you can park it anywhere.
Isn't she also Mago?
Oh, my! Mago!
-Mago!
-Man-wol!
It's been such a long time.
You used to come to my hotel often
when Mun-suk was there.
Why don't you come anymore?
We don't get a lot of money
because you don't come.
-Come more often.
-Where are you poking me?
I'm very busy these days.
I'm going to an opening now.
I don't know where the place is,
but it will be a success
thanks to your help.
Some young people have started
a computer business
in a small office here.
-Computer business?
-Yes, computer business.
I think it's praiseworthy
so I'm cheering them on.
They are very lucky.
And who are you?
Is he the new manager?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Take her hand quickly.
She'll bring you money.
My name is Koo Chan-sung.
You're holding it so hard.
You seem very nice.
I think we'll be meeting often.
Take good care of your guests.
Especially,
your first guest.
"My first guest"?
One's first guest is very important.
That's why I'm going as their first guest
to support them.
Man-wol.
Goodbye.
Have a good day. I've opened
lots of champagne bottles thanks to you.
Right.
By the way, you're so pretty nowadays.
You will be rich.
She's a deity of wealth.
She shook your hand and said nice things.
Was that why you were
so excited to see her?
Of course. I get excited whenever I meet
good-looking guys and rich women.
Then you should treat me differently now.
Since you'll be rich,
I'll treat you as a woman.
Let's go, sister.
First guest...
There is a guest that even Ms. Jang
and the staff don't know about.
Those who don't show their existence
also have the meaning of their existence.
Letting them exist
in the way they want to exist
is my answer to "the existence."
Just say you don't know.
By the way,
do you know where that murderer ghost is?
It is not easy to find a vengeful ghost.
You don't know that either.
The seven guests who were murdered by him
think we will bring him in soon.
They're waiting for him,
refusing to get on the bus.
Tell them
that they'll get to ride
a limousine if things get delayed.
I guess that means
it's going to take some time.
Vengeful ghosts...
always hide themselves in darkness.
If something's dark
even when it's no place for a shadow,
that's where they'll be.
Don't be late for the movie.
If you're going to be late again,
don't come. Let's just break up.
If you think you're being watched
by someone from a dark space,
it's one of them.
Hello, Sanchez.
VERONICA
I was so close to catching him.
He doesn't approach Koo Chan-sung
because you're always with him.
It seems like he's aiming
for people around Chan-sung.
I'm sure I'll catch him soon,
but he should warn them
just in case.
Mr. Kim, does Yu-na still
hang around with Hyeon-jung?
She's with him even right now.
-That's good.
-Okay.
-I did well, didn't I?
-Yes, you did well.
I know, right?
My goodness.
Man-wol.
I heard you got hurt.
I brought you some medicine.
Thanks.
How did you know I got hurt?
I didn't even tell Chan-sung.
I have an informant.
Who?
The Grim Reaper.
I guess you also have connections
with the Grim Reaper.
I didn't know I was friends
with such an incredible being.
Light this up at home.
Keep it nice and bright,
and don't go anywhere dark for a while.
I guess I didn't get hurt
merely because of bad luck.
I've been to your hotel.
There's nothing I can't believe now.
I'll do as you say.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I should've been nice to you then
instead of being so sarcastic.
I didn't really think
you'd be able to give that pizza
to Veronica.
I just wanted to believe
that it's possible.
Sanchez, you're Chan-sung's best friend,
aren't you?
If...
Chan-sung
also goes through the same thing someday,
I hope you'll be there to console him.
I'll be off now.
There are a lot of guests at the hotel.
You should light up the incense
in every room.
In every single room?
I guess I should tell Mi-ra
to light one up in her room as well.
I forgot she lived here.
Sanchez, is Mi-ra also acquainted
with Seol Ji-won?
Yes, they met in the States.
Why do you ask?
Where is she right now?
Mi-ra has a boyfriend.
She went to the movie theater
with her boyfriend.
The movie theater?
She's just friends with Chan-sung now.
Mi-ra's boyfriend is really good-looking.
Would you like to see a photo?
Wait a second.
Movie theaters are really dark.
Why should I care?
Man-wol, look...
She's gone already.
I guess she doesn't walk
like normal people.
Mi-ra would've been in big trouble
if she didn't have a boyfriend.
Yeong-su, when are you coming?
The movie's going to start soon.
Stop making excuses.
Okay, hurry up.
I guess that vengeful ghost
will take care of her for me.
What are you doing?
Where have you been?
What?
I went to apologize to Sanchez.
You went by yourself?
You should've taken me with you.
I just wanted to get it over with.
You've become a nice person.
Not really.
Thank you for caring about my friend.
You really did become a nice person.
Chan-sung.
You made me bloom flowers.
You've changed me a lot.
But you can't change my roots.
Don't even dream of it.
Do I need to get in your way again?
No, I didn't do anything.
I'm not lying.
So if anything happens,
it's not because of me.
We have a lot of guests today,
so I'm quite busy.
I'll drop by after I'm done with work.
See you then.
Darn.
Su-jin!
Sir, I noticed that you went outside.
-You can't just go outside--
-Please help me.
I heard this hotel has a human manager
who helps out with human affairs.
What's going on?
My girlfriend's sick right now,
but no one's there to help her.
If no one helps her,
my child will be in danger.
You should go back to your room.
I will
take the manager there and help her out.
Thank you.
I'm not going to call Mr. Koo.
I'm going to do nothing
and watch their family line end.
You can do whatever you want.
I don't intend to stop you.
I guess it's finally going
to come to an end.
How about you witness
how their family line ends?
I know where she is.
You just need to go there and watch.
You don't need to do anything.
Someone once told me
that seeing it
won't resolve my resentment.
I want you to prove
that they're wrong.
My baby...
Please tell Mr. Koo
that this woman is in danger.
911 EMERGENCY SERVICE
Ms. Choe, the woman was taken
to a hospital quickly by ambulance.
The mother and baby
are both okay.
I was
married to the eldest son
of the Yun family.
I wasn't able to bear a child
until I was quite old.
The child I finally gave birth to...
was a girl.
No.
My husband had to use
someone else's stomach
to bear a son who would
carry on the family name.
I had to leave my newborn daughter behind
to go pray at a famous temple
for the child in that woman's stomach
to be a son.
But...
To make sure
the child in her belly is a boy,
you need to get rid of the girl
that was born earlier.
According to my fortune-telling,
that girl is getting in the way
of all the men in this family.
If a family has a girl
with such a bad fortune,
that family will never give birth
to any boys.
My baby didn't get any water for days.
They didn't even change her diapers.
She was neglected like that.
By the time I ran over to her
after hearing about that,
the child was close to death.
Please open the door.
My baby is dying.
Is there anyone inside?
Please open the door!
No doctors will open their doors for you.
That baby must not live.
My baby...
My child died,
but there was nothing I could do.
There, there.
I started to lose my mind.
Their family will dry up.
She used to be clean and tidy.
What happened to her?
That Yun family was too harsh on her.
How could they turn someone like that?
Don't touch her!
Don't touch my baby!
The Yun family
will die out.
Even after I die,
I'll watch that happen.
I'll make sure...
That's how I swore I'd get my revenge.
But earlier, I couldn't bear to watch
that baby die until the end.
If the child disappears,
will that solve everything?
Do you really think so?
YEONG-SU
I'm running a little late.
Go ahead and watch it. I'll go in later.
POWER OFF
What you said was right.
I was wrong, so I'll tell you something.
Your friend...
Lee Mi-ra might be in danger.
Her phone is turned off.
This has to be the closest theater
to our house.
Don't be so dramatic.
That vengeful ghost won't be
strong enough to kill someone.
At most, she'll get a burn or a cut.
Did you keep this to yourself
so you could see Mi-ra get hurt?
Then why are you telling me now?
Did you change your mind
after watching Ms. Choe?
Yes. My heart is shaking.
Chan-sung.
Mi-ra.
What is this? Are you two here
to watch a movie?
What about you?
How darn lucky.
I got stood up.
I felt too offended
to sit there alone, so I left.
I guess he didn't come here.
Thank goodness.
What are you saying?
I was mad
because my boyfriend didn't show up,
then a pervert behind me went, "Hello."
I guess he did come after all.
What about Yeong-su?
Are you sure he didn't come here?
Are you looking for me?
This is interesting.
Keep looking for me.
Yeon-u.
Yeong-su!
Yeong-su, are you okay? Get up.
Yeong-su.
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Yeong-su?
I'm fine.
I work out on a regular basis,
so this is not a problem.
I'm glad nothing broke.
I got a good rest thanks to you.
I'll get going now.
No.
You can rest a little longer. Relax.
This is Chan-sung's room.
This is the cleanest room in our house.
Mi-ra, this is not "our" house.
That would mean your room is
extremely dirty.
Yeong-su, how are your teeth?
What about your tongue?
Did you not bite it?
I'm fine, Mi-ra.
Sanchez, go get some more ice water.
Okay.
Should I check your face?
-Let me see.
-I told you, I'm fine.
What about your back?
What is it? What's wrong?
That part hurts the most.
-Really? What about the other side?
-That side too.
How are Yeon-u and Song-hwa
together?
He's not Yeon-u. He's Park Yeong-su.
And she's not Song-hwa. She's Lee Mi-ra.
The two of them are dating.
I met Yeong-su through Mi-ra.
I thought it might make things
complicated for you,
so I didn't tell you about them.
Because they're the people you despise
and care dearly for.
To you, she may be an object
of an unresolved grudge.
To her,
you're a piece of her previous lives
that she doesn't even remember.
Just let her pass by.
Are you feeling confused?
The person I cared dearly for and
the person I hated the most are dating.
Killing a person I wish to kill
won't relieve my resentment.
Were you not able
to kill him then?
He died.
He died that day.
You survived.
I survived
to keep my promise to kill you.
I'm proud of you,
Man-wol.
FULL MOON
You memorized the letters well.
Did Yeon-u engrave it for you?
He was dexterous indeed.
I guess the blade of this sword...
carries Yeon-u's grudges too.
There are many who have grudges
against you.
You need to learn of them all,
and die in pain and misery.
What about ours?
I'm just happy to see you again.
As a beautiful bride,
you would welcome me,
and I'd say that I missed you
while stroking your face.
Shut your mouth.
FULL MOON
This is...
the end for us.
I won't let your people survive.
I'm going to burn down this castle.
Our last moment together
is this.
You have to die after seeing all of that.
Man-wol.
I'll keep you in my heart
and become the moon that never falls...
to watch you from afar.
After he died that day,
I was blinded by my desire to get revenge
and killed a lot of people.
Then I put my people's belongings
in a coffin and searched everywhere
to find the Guest House of the Moon.
I killed whoever got in my way.
When I finally arrived
at the Guest House of the Moon,
what I faced
was myself covered in blood.
My sins are heavy,
and my grudges are deep.
That's the real me.
I have...
waited for the man for so long,
planning to vanish
after bringing him down with me
to the rock bottom.
I came to you instead.
I...
cannot make you
forget your painful memories,
but I want to lift you out of them.
Does this bus go to Myeong-dong, sir?
Yes, it does.
Are you alone? Where's your mom?
I'm going to meet my mom.
Do you know about Hotel del Luna
in Myeong-dong?
That's where my mom is.
Ms. Choe!
Are you leaving now?
How could you not even say goodbye?
We've been working together
for the last 200 years!
I'm hurt.
I'm not leaving.
I was only cleaning the car
because the Grim Reaper asked me to.
Is that right?
Why does he always ask you
to clean the car? It's not our job.
I'm done.
Are you not leaving then?
I don't even know
if the child is a boy or a girl.
I have to see that first.
I ran all the way over here for nothing.
Mr. Kim,
please make me the Tears.
A strong one, please.
Sure. Let's go.
-Did you cry?
-No.
-That's a tear.
-I told you I didn't.
-I think it is.
-No.
Be good to me while you have the chance.
I will.
I hid a present for you in here.
Find it. You have one chance.
How can I do that in one try?
I'll give you a hint.
Sure.
The room number is the same
as the day we first met.
-The day we first met?
-Yes.
How am I supposed to remember that?
How can you not?
Do you not remember the date
of our first kiss either?
Don't say it out too loud.
Only ghosts will hear us anyway.
Think harder. When did we first meet?
It was when flowers were blooming,
-so maybe June?
-June?
-No, that's not right.
-Maybe May?
-Which day in May?
-May...
-Which day? Tell me.
-It's not May 5th, is it?
-May 5th?
I know that's wrong.
It's a child.
We rarely see a child come here alone.
Are you here alone?
Yes. I'm here to see my mom.
Did you follow your mom here?
You are not dead...
He's alive.
You saw this place in your dream, you say?
Mom said that she was all good here.
It's a side effect of a dream call.
There's a living child in here,
looking for his dead mom.
Please take him home safely.
Is his mom still here?
She already left for the afterlife
yesterday.
Please talk to the child
and get him out of here.
Where did he go?
Where's the child?
You were the one watching him.
I went to bring some ice cream for him.
We have to find him. Let's split.
My goodness.
Hey, kid.
Where could he have gone?
Hello, have you seen
a little child around here?
The kid? I saw him heading
to the platform.
What?
Hold on!
THE SAMDO RIVER
THIS WORLD, THE AFTERLIFE
What? A living kid came in here?
Yes. He disappeared,
so we're looking for him right now.
How could the front desk not catch him?
Was this tunnel always so long?
Am I trapped?
I found him!
I found him.
He was in front of the platform.
We could've been in serious trouble.
Bring Hyeon-jung here
and tell Chan-sung to take him home.
This isn't a place for you.
You could've ended up
in a very scary place.
But I saw a man walking in there.
What? What did you just say?
Who did you see?
A man in a suit walked in.
I was waiting to see if he was coming out,
but he didn't.
I think Mr. Koo went in there.
If he did, he'll get lost in there
and never--
Chan-sung...
Chan-sung?
Chan-sung!
I was so scared you might never come back.
Who...
are you?
If he had come, I was going to throw him
into the hell that you made
and make both of you vanish.
I can't do that anymore.
I ended up falling in love again.
How ridiculous.
Eat this.
Eat it and become an evil ghost.
Just die.
I told you that she will protect me.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu
Stop.
What are you doing?
These are the belongings
of the executed men.
We were told to keep what's useful
and burn the rest.
Don't burn the belongings of the dead.
Gather all of them.
Give these to the men who survived
so that they can hold a proper funeral.
Wait.
I will kill you.
I will kill you
at all costs.
Chan-sung!
I was so scared you might never come back.
Who...
are you?
Mr. Koo!
-Mr. Koo!
Thank goodness you're okay.
We were really worried.
My heart dropped again.
Ms. Jang, you must've been
really startled.
Do you feel unwell?
No, I'm fine.
I'm okay. I must've startled you a lot.
Ms. Jang must be angry.
She's probably just embarrassed
that she ran over here all startled.
Anyway, I'm relieved
that you managed to find your way out.
This is...
the end for us.
Who is that man?
Why do you ask? You think it might be you?
That thought did occur to me.
What I saw could be a memory
from my past life that I don't remember.
Koo Chan-sung will eventually
bring him to you.
This is absurd.
Chan-sung can't be him.
It seems Man-wol will get seriously swayed
by this
small and green light.
You've become
very weak because you had to come back
from the afterlife.
And now, you're so dim.
This alcohol is for the living.
You almost crossed the threshold
of the afterlife,
so hurry up and drink something
from this world.
Thank you.
I'm so relieved that you didn't get lost
and found your way out.
Yes, I heard
that time runs at a different speed there
and that I could lose my memory.
"A man was gone for a moment
and came back,
and 30 years had passed."
Such a folktale wasn't a joke.
I heard this from the Grim Reaper.
Someone remembered his past life
on his way back from the afterlife,
which completely ruined his life
in the living realm.
His past life?
Did you see anything odd
when you were there?
I think I remember seeing
something twinkling in the dark.
I see.
What was that?
We don't know. We've never gone in there.
You got to go in there
even before we dead ones do.
By the way, how did you manage
to return right away?
I heard it's not easy.
Frankly, I have no recollection
whatsoever.
I was out of there
when I came to my senses.
You lost your memory.
Here, drink some more.
Ms. Jang.
I thought the kid got on the car
to the afterlife.
I ended up going in there,
trying to stop that.
Both the kid and I are fine,
so don't be mad.
I'm really fine.
You are just Chan-sung.
Do you still...
see me in your dreams?
No, I haven't seen you in my dreams
since the day I had a very long dream.
Then, did you see someone else?
I haven't told you
because I wasn't sure whether it was
a dream or just my imagination,
but I saw that man.
The man named Cheong-myeong.
He was waiting for you
by the lake all by himself.
He was holding an ornament
with your moon-shaped symbol
in his hands.
Have you
received such a gift?
No.
If I wasn't looking into your past,
what was that dream about?
You told me before
that perhaps you were seeing
memories from your past life
that you don't remember.
But you said that was impossible.
Yes.
It's impossible.
Are you anxious
because of how Song-hwa and Yeon-u
ended up together?
Are you worried he might return like that?
I won't end up like them.
They were...
Fine. It happened in their past lives,
so let's say it's possible for them.
But for me, it happened in this lifetime.
Seeing Yeon-u with that woman
made me think
some crazy thoughts for a moment.
-Dad.
-Hyeong-min! Yes, I'm here.
He fell asleep at a bus stop.
We brought him to the hospital
because he had a fever.
He took some medicine,
so the fever has gone down.
Thank you so much.
Where have you been?
I took the bus and went to the hotel.
He must've had a dream when he was asleep.
I went there to see Mom,
but they said she was not there.
When you're a little older,
I'll tell you where your mom is
and why she had to leave.
I'll tell you everything, okay?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
If he finds out later,
will it make him less sad?
That he will never see her again.
Does Yu-na know
that you're planning to leave
with your younger sister after she dies?
Yu-na.
-There's--
-Hey, Ms. Jang will yell at you
if you go back now,
so let's hang out a little.
-Well--
-I learned
that you get scolded less
if you wait it out a little.
Wait here. I need to use the ladies' room.
I should tell her today.
Ma'am, listen to this for a moment.
Do you like this piano melody?
Well...
Yes.
My friend's sister...
I mean, you look a lot
like my friend's grandmother.
May I take a photo of you
listening to music to show my friend?
Sure.
Thank you.
Well... Do you remember
your brother's name by any chance?
Yes, I do.
My brother's name is Ji Hyeon-jung.
You remember him?
Yes.
Hello, can I help you?
Hyeon-jung.
Yes, Hyeon-mi.
Were you listening to music?
Let's see.
Sir, are you the founder of this hospital,
Mr. Ji Hyeon-jung?
Yes. You must be Mr. Kim's daughter
who was hospitalized here.
Hold on.
You're
her brother?
Yes, I am. What's the matter?
But her brother, Ji Hyeon-jung,
died many years ago.
What?
Hyeon-jung?
-Where are you?
-Yes, I'm here.
Gosh.
There is someone who knows
that Ji Hyeon-jung is dead.
I told you not to bother Hyeon-mi.
Does that man have something
to do with your death?
Did he steal everything you had?
And he's living as you now?
-It's none of your business.
-That's why you couldn't leave.
You couldn't stand him living
a good life using your name.
-Just leave him be.
-How could I?
He stole your life.
Who cares? I'm already dead.
Look at yourself living a good life.
Right.
I stole someone's life too.
I was being too nosy.
Yu-na, that's not what I meant.
I'll mind my own business.
Hey, Sanchez.
Everything's going well, right?
-Yes.
-Give me that!
-Hey!
-What's up with all the noise?
Is someone else home?
Mi-ra had Detective Park
sleep in your room last night
because his leg was swollen.
I think he's fine now,
but Mi-ra kept saying
he must eat well as he's injured.
So we were eating.
But when we were having a meal,
Detective Park's colleagues
came over since it's their day off.
And then, they said I had a nice yard,
so they're having the watermelon
they brought.
Gosh, you guys look great together.
It's Mi-ra who invited them, right?
Chan-sung, it's very safe
since they're here.
And thanks to the incense Man-wol gave me,
it's spiritually safe too.
Since the detectives are here,
I don't need to worry
about being in danger.
Sanchez, put Mi-ra on the phone.
I'll talk to her.
Don't.
I'm sure she's bringing people over
in case I get depressed if I'm all alone.
It's nice and noisy here.
Chan-sung, all I could think about is
making sure
that they don't ruin the grass.
Chan-sung, you don't need
to worry about me.
-This is good.
-It is, right? I bought it.
-No, you didn't.
-I didn't?
I'll eat it myself.
Come on, you're injured.
My arm is fine.
Should I break your arm,
so you will let me feed you?
Here.
It's good, right?
-You can eat it yourself now.
-It's good.
Isn't it sweet?
I thought Mi-ra and Detective Park were
always fighting like enemies.
Now that I see them together,
they seem fine.
You don't need to worry.
I think she'll move out soon.
Chan-sung, I'll go eat
some watermelon now. Bye.
Sanchez.
Eat the melon the detectives bought.
-Come and join us.
-It's delicious.
Mi-ra.
That melon came from my fridge.
Is that so?
-Let's eat it.
-Things happen, you know.
-The melon did feel cool.
-Bring the cutting board.
What does it matter?
Come in.
Do you remember
that Ms. Jang invited a woman
to our hotel a while ago?
This is an amazing hotel.
And from what I've heard,
she's your friend.
That's right.
Did she cross paths with Ms. Jang
in her past lives?
I'm sure their connection was ill-fated.
We have never
tried to figure out Ms. Jang's story
because we always assumed
that she had no intention
of leaving after resolving her grudges.
But now, the tree that tied her down here
has changed.
And I think the changes have been brought
by you and the connections
you have brought.
Your assumption...
is correct.
Will Ms. Jang face
more connections from her past,
not just that lady?
He's already here.
And I'm sure
more will come shortly.
I'll probably end up bringing
the man to Ms. Jang like the others.
That must be why Mago brought you
to our hotel.
Then, you must have crossed paths
with Ms. Jang in your past life as well.
No, I have not.
Is that so?
That's odd.
If you have never met her
in your past life,
why did Mago choose you of all people?
I'm sure the deity must have
a reason for bringing you to her.
Anyway, it resulted in love.
I will continue
to stay with her.
My heart breaks for Ms. Jang.
Soon,
she will have to face someone
who pains her the most.
Man-wol.
Why are you leaving?
I don't want to see you.
Just admire the flowers you like so much
as much as you want,
and leave.
Then,
will you let him just pass by,
pretending to be clueless?
You have met him.
You can't run away from it.
He's already
by your side.
I finally get to give this to you.
It's yours.
But I saw that man.
The man named Cheong-myeong.
He was holding an ornament
with your moon-shaped symbol
in his hands.
Is it Chan-sung?
If it is him,
will you be able to accept it?
Is Chan-sung
that man?
The man you've been waiting
for over 1,000 years has finally shown up,
but you don't seem happy.
You were sure
that once he came to you in this world,
you'd kill him and vanish yourself.
Are you second-guessing yourself now?
So I asked...
if that man is Chan-sung.
You have fed the hatred of yours
for a long time.
Why don't you let go of your hatred
with your love that took ages
to reach you?
I have hated the man for over 1,000 years.
But you make me see him
as a man I fell in love with?
I'm curious to find out which man
you'll see him as.
Will you see him as Go Cheong-myeong
and vanish yourself?
Or will you see him as Koo Chan-sung
and be saved?
That is...
up to you.
Jang Man-wol.
Every sight you see with me
will look different.
The view is much better
now that I'm with you.
I'm proud of you,
Man-wol.
I told you
to trust me.
Chan-sung.
Ms. Jang.
Are you all right?
You look very pale.
A moment ago,
I killed Chan-sung in my thoughts.
He could be...
the reincarnation of the man
I hate the most.
I'm sure it isn't him.
Mr. Koo also said it wasn't him.
Right.
It might not be him.
But as long as there's the slightest
possibility that it could be him,
I will never be able
to see Chan-sung properly.
Now
what will you do?
I can never kill Chan-sung.
Mago says I have to empty out everything.
Now I have to think hard...
about how to do that.
I bought them at the shop you like.
You will feel better
if you eat something sweet.
Come and sit down.
What do you have in your hand?
It's the ornament I saw in my dreams.
I guess this came from your dream.
Mago gave it to me.
In my dreams,
it didn't have any blood on it.
I told you he died on my sword.
This blood
must be filled with the hatred of me.
Why did Mago give you
such an ominous thing?
Give it to me. I'll keep it for you.
I'll get rid of this myself.
The moon covered in blood
must be destroyed.
Mago always tells me
to empty the moon
that is filled with hatred.
Can you do that?
I have to.
I want to call in
the moon covered in blood.
Mr. Koo.
You were here.
The Grim Reaper is looking for you.
Go on.
I have found the vengeful ghost
that cursed you.
You've found Seol Ji-won.
Has he become more powerful as he wanted?
Do you think a vengeful ghost
that holds unjustifiable resentment
can become powerful as he wishes?
He is only hiding in the dark
like a gutter rat.
It's good to know
that he hasn't become
as stronger as his evil mind.
He's just hiding in the dark
like a coward.
Can you help me?
I heard you were good at acting as bait.
I won't reveal who recommended you.
I'm sure it's Mr. Kim.
I'll take it that one of my colleagues
thinks highly of my skills.
Many human managers worked here.
Among them, you are...
This is my assessment.
Thank you.
Were you there when the Guest House
of the Moon first opened?
Yes.
I guided a number of souls
from this place to the other world.
Take good care of your guests.
Especially,
your first guest.
Who was the first guest of this place?
Mago said that the first guest was
the most important.
I have not yet guided...
the first guest of this place.
Nobody in this place
has seen the faint light of his existence.
How is that possible?
I do not give answers.
I only guide them to the end.
For now,
let's go catch that vengeful ghost.
Since it has the moon-shaped symbol,
he must have made it for you.
And you would've been so happy
if you received it.
That's the most
disgusting thing about you.
If he would come,
I was going to throw him
into the hell that you made
and make both of you vanish.
But because of the scheming
of the deities,
I can't do that anymore.
I...
ended up falling in love again.
How ridiculous.
Leaning on that love,
I tried to ignore you.
But you just had to
drag me down again.
I will
put you in here
and dump it in a trash bin around here.
You will go berserk.
And we will vanish together.
Seol Ji-won.
Come out.
I know you're hiding in here.
The Grim Reaper is on his way to take you.
There you are.
So you went from being a smug jerk
to a loser.
I have something for you.
Eat this.
Eat it...
and become an evil ghost.
So he ended up hiding in a place
he was familiar with.
He's in the darkness, but he will reveal
himself once he sees you.
Jang Man-wol, you're here too?
Yes, I came earlier.
Did you catch him?
I let him go.
You'll be in danger soon
because I gave him
a very special gift.
And you'll have to take him
more seriously than before.
He might go crazy
with his new-found powers.
What are you doing?
Chan-sung.
Mago said that you're him.
I need to kill you,
but I won't be able to.
I just like you too much.
I won't protect you though.
I've waited
for over 1,000 years to kill you.
So if I protect you now,
I'll be making a mockery of my grudges.
If he becomes an evil ghost,
you'll vanish
because you helped him become stronger.
Whatever.
You're a human adored by Mago,
so they'll interfere
before the evil ghost gets to you.
And...
you'll vanish.
So I ended up using you.
It's pathetic I called it love.
Jang Man-wol!
What's with the hotel?
I don't know.
All the lights in the building
have gone out.
Mr. Koo, what happened to Ms. Jang?
I think there was a misunderstanding.
Do you know where she is?
She went into the garden
where the Moon Tree stands
and barricaded the door.
No one can enter.
We should check on our guests first.
I don't understand
why we're in trouble now.
Ms. Jang,
what on earth are you up to?
Is it true?
Am I truly that man from her past
who Ms. Jang loathes?
I doubt that's what she said
since he is
right here.
You've met him before, you know.
How...
is this him?
He is
the first guest who stayed
at Man-wol's Guest House of the Moon.
I should take him to her.
Actually,
shouldn't you stop her
from vanishing first?
Find the thing Man-wol handed over
to the evil ghost.
Once the evil ghost makes his move,
it will be irreversible.
Since we got the overtime pay,
let's grab a drink.
-Sure.
-Let's go.
I hear he cursed his wife,
wishing her dead.
What a piece of garbage.
Does he have no shame?
Who are you?
You should get out of here. Hurry.
Hi, my friend.
I was going to visit you
after I had some fun.
But I guess you were in a hurry.
How did you find me?
I found you thanks to the owner
of the thing you recently picked up.
This?
I came to take that back. Give it to me.
How are you going to do that?
You'll die before you can take it from me.
So this is
how you've come to face me.
I guess you're not going to give up.
Let's see how long you'll last.
I was just buying time.
The time has come.
The moon's showing itself.
Why do you think she gave that to you?
I told you that she will protect me.
You see that moon-shaped symbol?
Once the moon fully reveals itself,
you'll be doomed for having that with you.
Don't try to fool me.
I told you
that death isn't the end, didn't I?
I tried to stop you,
but you just chose to die.
Now, what awaits you is horrendous hell.
Goodbye, Seol Ji-won.
How dare you lie to me?
Just die.
I never lied to you.
You're really doomed.
I was also once
a vengeful ghost full of spite.
We've been dead for 770 years in total.
But you're nothing but a runt
that just died.
How dare you act up this way?
Take what you found,
and go back to the hotel.
Okay.
I caught him.
We did all the work.
You're just taking credit for it.
You gave yourself to the vengeful ghost
and tried to turn him into an evil one.
I cannot forgive you for that.
I took out the most horrid hell
that I had deep down inside me
and gave it to the evil spirit.
Then what does that make you now?
Are you just a heartbroken moon
that blooms and withers flowers
as time repeats itself?
Just make me vanish.
No!
I brought it back.
There's no reason she must vanish now.
Please leave.
Just make me vanish!
Fine.
Go ahead and have what you want.
If you must torment yourself like that,
I'll become the guy you hate so much.
Kill me.
I promised I'd stay by your side
even if I have to die
for getting in your way.
The man you've been waiting for...
is actually here.
You came all the way here.
So you should listen to
what happened to the moon...
covered in blood.
That way, you'll be able
to empty your grudges.
Is this the afterlife?
The afterlife that you'll encounter
won't be so magnificent.
But there are some people
who wish to see you before you leave.
Me?
Our hotel guests are waiting for you.
This is a special service for them.
This number is such a cliché.
What is this? Is it the hell?
You'll find out once you go inside.
Do you remember what you said to all of us
right before you killed us?
Seol Ji-won.
We should soundproof the hotel rooms.
YOU'RE INVITED TO HOTEL DEL LUNA
JANG MAN-WOL
PRESIDENT JANG MAN-WOL
"Hotel del Luna"?
Mr. Koo Chan-sung works here?
Yes, the owner of the hotel invited you.
She invited the doctor too.
You two should come together.
DEAR MR. PARK YEONG-SU
Jang Man-wol?
DEAR MS. LEE MI-RA
What's that?
An invitation to a hotel.
I've already been there once
as my friend works there.
It's such a nice hotel.
Where is it?
Not everyone can go.
You can't go there without an invitation.
It's a special hotel.
Very special.
Welcome.
I'll take you to our Sky Lounge,
the pride of our hotel.
Wow.
You came to this fancy place
all by yourself?
Welcome.
We have a table ready for you inside.
This way, please.
Here, everyone gets drunk
and has a dream about their past lives.
And I'm the bartender here.
Today, the deities made an exception
for the two of you
and gave me permission
to let you have a taste
of one of your past lives.
The deities?
He means he'll impress us
with super delicious drinks.
I blacked out last time,
so I don't remember much.
This time, I should drink slowly.
Give us our drinks.
This is a petal.
It's a petal from the Moon Tree.
The Moon Tree?
There is such a tree?
I'm sure there is.
This is so pretty.
They're here in this hotel now.
You'll be able to find out...
more about him through them.
Cheong-myeong.
My father is looking for you.
Why is he looking for me?
We received a tip that you are in league
with the rebels from Dongmo Mountain.
You will die if you go see my father now.
So I sent some soldiers
to capture everyone in that woman's gang.
What do you mean?
Those bandits are
the remnants of Goguryeo.
If you capture all of them
and take them to my father,
he will no longer suspect you.
They're just wandering thieves
that steal from peddlers.
If you are executed as a traitor,
all your subordinates
as well as everyone
who is related to you will die.
Even if there are hundreds of people,
my father will kill them all
as he is afraid of a coup.
Go and capture them all.
Why are you taking the innocent villagers?
You should just capture us thieves.
I'm not here to catch you thieves.
I came to quell the rebels.
What?
I'll try to save them even if that means
they must become slaves.
But for me to do that,
all of you thieves must be killed
as rebels.
Why...
Why are you doing this?
I wanted to find a way
to join hands with you.
I wished to go to the new country
in Dongmo Mountain
with you.
But I got busted.
And now, I must take your lives
to cover it up.
After I bury all of it,
I will pay for what I did
with my own life.
No, don't.
Just save Man-wol.
And to do that,
you must live as a traitor
instead of telling her all the excuses
that you told me.
Then Man-wol will live.
He made a promise to Yeon-u.
He's always been here.
He was the first guest
of the Guest House of the Moon.
You're not the only one
who's been paying for the past sins here
all these years.
Thanks to you,
I made a great contribution.
I will kill you.
I will kill you...
at all costs.
If you wish to kill me,
you will have to stay alive.
You must live as a traitor.
Then Man-wol will live.
I've been waiting for you.
I hope there won't be any hesitation
when you swing your sword at me.
If so,
I won't hesitate
to throw myself at the sword.
You have never
uttered his name. Not even once.
If you call his name,
he will show himself.
Have you been here the whole time?
If so, show yourself to me.
Go Cheong-myeong.
Tell me if there's anything else
you wish to tell me.
I'll listen to it.
There's no more excuse to tell you.
Man-wol.
You told me in your last moment
that you would watch me from afar.
While I was tied down to the Moon Tree
and filled with grudges,
my words tied you down here...
and stopped you from leaving.
I...
have emptied everything now.
So you should stop now.
This is really...
the end for us.
Yes.
It's the end.
His soul doesn't have the energy
to go to the afterlife.
If we leave him here, he will vanish.
He won't be able to have another life.
To avoid that,
you should
send him off.
That is the last punishment
you will get here.
Yeong-su.
Are you up?
You two got really drunk,
so Mr. Koo told me to escort you home.
So I called a cab.
Well, you two can go home
on your own, right?
-Yes.
-Goodbye then.
Gosh, this again?
When I came to the hotel last time,
she was the one who sent me home in a cab.
But this time,
I remember up to drinking the cocktail.
Yeong-su, why are you crying?
I don't know. I just feel sad.
Seeing you cry like this is
making me sad too.
This is so weird.
I'm right here. Why are you crying?
Don't cry.
Is he really not going to make up with me?
We met for the first time
on May 2nd.
I found it.
This watch looks pretty old.
It's over 70 years old.
Time on that watch
has been flowing since you were alive.
It must be really rare.
It must've been hard to find it.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry.
I wanted to remind you
that you're 70 years older than me.
It wasn't easy to get that watch.
So from now on,
even if I get to look older than you
like your sister,
don't forget
that you are way older than I am.
Put it on your wrist.
I'm sure it'll look great on you.
Yu-na.
I will leave soon.
I told you that I was waiting
for my sister, Hyeon-mi.
Right now, Hyeon-mi is very sick.
When she leaves,
I must go with her.
Yu-na,
when this watch was made,
I had already been dead.
Time can't run
for the dead and for the living together.
I died too early.
It's so upsetting.
I'll see him off.
You'll be back soon, right?
Of course.
I'll be back soon.
You are coming back, right?
Wait for me.
THE SAMDO RIVER.
THIS WORLD, THE AFTERLIFE.
A MONTH LATER
Ma'am, let me help you.
Once you go out to the beach,
you can rent any kinds of beach supplies.
Let's go.
-Thank you.
It looks like you've made progress.
Could you read it for me?
It's been a month since Ms. Jang left.
Ms. Jang isn't here.
But how come
the hotel hasn't vanished yet?
It means that Ms. Jang is no longer
the owner of the Guest House of the Moon.
That's my guess.
Mr. Koo.
I think you should go see the garden.
Yesterday,
I saw a few leaves and flowers.
But the tree is completely lifeless now.
I guess
that means Ms. Jang can't come back
for good now.
Wait for me.
Jang Man-wol.
Please hurry.
I'm getting...
anxious now.
All of us are against having a new owner.
Help Ms. Jang return.
I'm with them.
It took me 500 years
to get used to Ms. Jang.
Having another boss? I'm against it.
It is up to her
whether she returns to this place or not.
There's no way she won't come back
when Mr. Koo is waiting for her.
If she set foot on the bridge,
she might have forgotten him.
She might have let go
of all her memories of this world
and crossed the bridge,
following her most distant memories.
Is that why all the flowers fell?
Then I guess the tree is really dead now.
Right.
All the flowers fall down and disappeared.
I suppose Man-wol is
really dead now.
Should we be expecting a new owner
of the Guest House of the Moon?
The Moon Tree is the owner
of the guest house.
But all the flowers and leaves are gone.
It's dead now.
THE GUYS WHO DIED AFTER EATING
This is so hot.
How did Kim Jun-hyun
eat five of these at once?
He amazed me.
That's where Kim Jun-hyun sat.
Eat before it gets cold.
KIM JUN-HYUN SAT HERE
"To Ms. Jang man-wol, I love you"?
-Doesn't it make you happy?
-Are you confessing your love to me?
This is Kim Jun-hyun's autograph.
Here, "Kim Jun-hyun."
It's too heartbreaking
if I remain only as a flower petal
that's bound to vanish.
I'LL VISIT EVERY FAMOUS RESTAURANT
IN THIS COUNTRY
Not all of the flowers vanished.
There are still some flowers left.
I put the flowers dreaming of the moon
in his heart.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu