Hotel Del Luna Blu-ray Disc 6
Subtitle re-timing by Jharel
Was...
Go Cheong-myeong
there to meet her?
Chan-sung, come here!
This came for you.
HOTEL DEL LUNA
It's from Man-wol.
-It's from Jang Man-wol?
-Yes.
THANK YOU
"Thank you"?
Don't run away.
Even if I go berserk, do crazy things,
and vanish one day,
please stay by my side.
I won't let you vanish.
Trust me.
She fired a competent guy like you,
but she eventually
ended up reinstating you.
I guess she wants to be nice to you now.
My sincerity touched her heart.
My god, what's this?
Is this a tiger print suit?
Make sure you get a good price for this.
Then as a reward,
I'll get you a tiger print suit like this.
God, she's unbelievable.
This is a luxury brand. It's really sexy.
You should try it on. It'll look funny.
No, forget it.
Who wears tiger print suits?
But if you don't wear it,
Man-wol will feel upset.
It looks really expensive.
And it'll upset me as well.
I want to see how it looks on you.
I didn't give her the money I got
from selling the painting.
Where did she get the money to buy this?
She wouldn't go to a luxury brand store
just to get a suit for me.
Hey, this is actually really nice.
Veronica's coming to Korea next week.
How about I buy the same suit?
It might make me look
really wild and different.
No, don't do that.
You don't want to shock her.
You know nothing
about being in a relationship.
It's necessary to surprise
your partner once in a while.
Whatever.
Man-wol said she was going
to a department store the other day.
I guess that's when she got this.
You met Jang Man-wol?
Yes, a few days ago.
She asked me to help her sell something
she inherited from her grandfather.
What? "Something she inherited
from her grandfather"?
They're a couple of pure Arabian horses
on a farm in Qatar.
I heard even the royal family
wants to have those horses.
Do you think you can help me sell them?
Sanchez, are you close to Mansour
by any chance?
Mansour?
No, I'm not.
But purebred horses are very rare.
So someone in my equestrian club
will want to buy them.
That's great news.
If you help me sell those horses
at a high price,
I'll get you a white suit
just like this one.
But why are you asking me for help
instead of Chan-sung?
I can't trust him.
Why not?
He just got reinstated,
so he's really busy.
Please help me with this, Sanchez.
If you ever happen to come
to my hotel in the future,
I promise that I'll treat you well.
Oh, really?
Of course.
My gosh.
The chairman...
I sold the horses for your sake.
By the way,
those horses are really expensive.
She got those horses in return
for letting him make the dream call.
I should never be off my guard.
I should always make sure
to tighten the reins.
Mr. Koo. All the guests are
requesting the special service.
They heard of this
because of Chairman Wang,
so many of them wish to make
a dream call to the living people.
This is a service
that Ms. Jang has only offered in secret
to guests who pay special fees.
What should we do?
We should be fair
in providing our service.
I'll handle this.
Okay.
Hey.
What? Why didn't you put it on?
I was looking forward to seeing you
dressed in tiger print.
This is my workplace.
If the owner says it's fine,
then it's fine.
See? I even bought this
to wear when you come dressed
like a tiger.
That's a horse print. A zebra.
What do you think? Pretty, isn't it?
It gets on my nerves.
You don't like it?
You're so picky.
Fine, if you don't like
tiger prints or zebra prints,
then let's go. I'll get you
something that's your cup of tea.
We have no time to do that.
We have a lot of special requests
from our guests.
You need to take care of them.
A dream call is only offered to those
who pay a special price.
You already got paid.
The horses. You took the horses.
Darn you, Sanchez.
I won't meddle with that money,
but you have to help the other guests.
REQUEST FOR SPECIAL SERVICE
Chan-sung, do you think
the dead will only say nice things
when they appear in a dream?
"I died because of you.
You have to die with me."
What if they resent and curse the living?
Resentment and cursing.
That's why I look into each and every one
of their cases
and take a special price
only when the circumstances look right.
It's not just about money!
You're right.
I had the wrong idea about you.
It wasn't because of money.
You were concerned.
Yes. It's all for my guests' sake.
I only do it for those
who can pull this off.
What do you take me for?
In that case,
I will make some rules
to single out those who can do this.
Seriously!
I'm the one who took the horses.
Why is he acting like that?
I'll tell you the secret
to our naengmyeon stock.
It's because you were
the most diligent one among my staff.
Listen up.
Naengmyeon?
I love naengmyeon too.
The secret is...
My gosh.
Is that you?
Thank you so much for everything.
Your band's music gave me
much comfort to my last breath.
-"Your band"?
-He must be in a band.
I knew your music and dance
would end up touching
the heart of the world.
That's not for someone she actually knew.
Look, it says...
I WISH TO TELL SOMEONE I LOVE...
I love you!
I'll love you forever!
Having fun?
Stay on top of everything, will you?
Yes.
He's leaving today,
and he wishes to talk to his wife
before he leaves.
Am I allowed to make only one call?
Yes, just one call.
In that case, I wish to call someone else.
I got into a car accident with my son.
I wish to talk to the man
who hit us with the truck.
You cannot make a call
to blame or curse someone.
Please leave.
It's not that I wish
to blame or curse him.
I wish to apologize to him.
I'm glad you were just put on probation.
Glad? Two people were
hit by my truck and died.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I can't do this job anymore.
If you quit this job,
how will you make a living?
You are the people I killed...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I can't be forgiven for what I have done.
We're sorry.
It's our fault for suddenly jumping
in front of your truck.
It was a mistake.
We had bad luck,
but we gave you too much pain.
I'm sorry.
I hope
your life doesn't get ruined
because of us.
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
I feel much better now.
Son, shall we go?
Thank you.
Should we call it a day?
We only have a few guests left.
Let's finish up today.
Tell them to come in.
The flowers are in full bloom.
Let's not be too worried.
The flowers have finally bloomed.
They might stay pretty like this
for a long time.
Mago is trying to take Ms. Jang.
Flowers bloom only to fall.
We have to go before Ms. Jang does,
so let's prepare ourselves for that day.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
Do you know how tiring it is
to let ghosts talk to the living?
But thanks to you, many people will smile
when they wake up from their dreams today.
You've done well,
so I'll make you smile too.
What?
How?
Are you going to put on
the tiger print suit?
I knew it. You sent that to me
to make me look ridiculous.
Hey, if I put in that much money
to have a good laugh,
it means I tried very hard.
I tried very hard to make you laugh too.
I made a reservation
at the rice cake soup place
where you failed to eat
and came back angry many times.
Let's go.
What?
They don't take reservations. It takes
at least two hours to get a table.
I used my connection from Harvard.
Can you major in rice cake soup
at Harvard?
The son of that restaurant is an alumnus.
I reserved the entire place
at the closing time.
Let us hurry.
Hey, wait.
You should change into an outfit
that fits the soup.
This isn't an ordinary rice cake soup.
It's made with bead-shaped cakes.
I'll wear something special.
Look here.
I'm okay.
Sanchez is only three years older than me.
If I eat three bowls
of rice cake soup today,
can I talk casually to you
like Sanchez does?
What?
Sanchez calls you by your first name.
You want to be on a first name basis
with me?
Okay, just eat 1,300 bowls
of rice cake soup.
Even Kim Jun-hyun can't eat that much.
Don't underestimate Kim Jun-hyun.
Okay, then.
One rice cake will be worth one year.
No, one rice cake for one hundred years.
You fraud from Harvard!
You think you could age that easily?
After I eat 13 rice cakes,
I'll start calling you Man-wol.
Do as you please.
When a human ages 1,300 years, he dies.
Challenge. I'll take 200 years first.
It tastes better
because it's worth 200 years.
Being on a roll, I add 300 years more.
They look so pretty now.
Why must they fall?
It's sad.
Now I have 300 years left.
Are you nervous?
Then, I just have to eat 500 years more.
Are you stupid?
I will eat faster.
No, I will eat faster.
I now have 100 years left.
Add 200 years for me.
I was famous for eating fast at Harvard.
I'm already 3,500 years old.
-Adding 600 years.
-I'm 3,600 years old now.
You can't beat me. Just acknowledge it.
I'll also eat those earrings after this.
Nonsense.
I've found the motive for the murders.
It's this website called Helllo.
Helllo? Is it some social club?
It's "Hell" and "lo," meaning "to Hell."
The name is a play on words.
Helllo. What is the website for?
It's an old community
with more than 100 thousand members.
At first, they just shared
their problems on it.
But it's gradually become a real hell.
Now, they post curses and slanders
about other people.
It's like an emotional trash can.
-So?
-The suspect posted
several slanders about his wife.
He wrote comments on slanders
about six others who were killed.
The slanders about the victims
had a high number of views and comments.
Now you're looking
at the post and comments
criticizing one of the victims.
KILL, KILL!
If one uploads a slandering post
about people he hates,
the others curse them together.
That's what they do on the website.
What about the suspect?
Did he carry out the curse?
He thinks he's some kind of demon?
Except for Lee Do-yeon,
the wife of the suspect,
the victims were killed by someone
who they had never met.
They didn't even know why.
So this man is not the killer, right?
I told you. I was right.
The owner of that car is the killer.
There was a ghost in that car too.
You saw it.
But you can't call the police
without any evidence.
There's the composite sketch.
That thing you always see
in criminal investigation dramas.
Let's do that.
I'm good at drawing.
You'll get into trouble
if Ms. Jang finds out about this.
Tell me everything you remember about him.
Tell me anything.
81GI 0963
I didn't meet the Koo Chan-sung guy.
I moved the stuff with a high school girl.
I really had a hard time
because my car broke down.
Do you know the girl's name
or her phone number?
I don't know her phone number.
She contacted us through the SNS account.
Do you really work
at an entertainment agency?
Are you a casting director?
I guess.
She is quite attractive,
so I wanted to meet her.
She can't be in show business.
She's really weird.
What's weird about her?
She's soft in the head.
No, she's not crazy. She sees ghosts.
That's right.
Ghosts?
Yes, she sees ghosts.
Everyone in our schools knows.
You shouldn't make up rumors
about your friend like that.
I'm telling the truth.
She talks to herself.
She follows someone when there is nobody.
She follows ghosts?
That's interesting.
Mr. Kim, I looked at the new menu.
You changed the name of
our signature cocktail, Tears,
to Tear Wine.
Ms. Jang said it was too pretentious.
Why? It was a good name.
Tears and cheers.
It has a nice ring to it.
A Harvard graduate like you
thinks it's not bad, right?
Ms. Jang's picking on me for no reason.
It's the signature cocktail of our bar,
so I think you should work on it
a bit more.
Something like Angel's Tears
or Devil's Tears.
You think so? Angel and Devil?
I will make a note and give it to you.
Harvard knows how to teach
their students properly.
What are the guests doing
in the middle of the day?
They are those who were killed
and buried secretly.
I heard we had those guests.
I heard the killer was caught.
That's what I heard too.
But Ms. Fourth Choice keeps saying
something is not right.
I don't think the man
the police caught is the culprit.
There was a ghost in this car too.
The owner of this car is suspicious.
81GI 0963
Yu-na, you're still too young.
You shouldn't get involved
in a violent crime like this.
I agree. You should concentrate on school.
Then, let me finish the sketch
I've been drawing.
I'll show it to you when I finish it.
I'll look into it if there's any problem.
So you have to tell me.
Okay.
REQUEST FOR SPECIAL SERVICE
They are the additional service requests
we have received today.
Oh, dear.
It's such a bother.
You probably saw the flowers.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Have you all decided to get on the bus
to the afterlife?
We are preparing ourselves for the worst.
And I...
will leave after I see
that family completely destroyed.
You told me your daughter had to die
for the family to carry on
their family line.
No matter how impatient you feel,
you must not do what you did 42 years ago.
If you become an evil ghost and vanish,
your 200 years
of hard work at this hotel
will go down the drain.
My grudge is so deep
that I don't care about those years.
There will be a lunar eclipse soon.
Yes.
I hear the moon will be covered
for quite a while this time.
I'll prepare for it.
Sir.
Do you need anything?
I'm thirsty.
I'll bring something to drink
to your room.
This way.
A long lunar eclipse...
Mr. Koo Chan-sung,
we need you to come with us.
We brought him.
Come closer.
Who are you, and why did you look for me?
Do you recognize me?
Of course.
I even saw you on today's morning paper.
I've been admiring you.
But why did you call for me?
I hear you're working at a hotel
that's registered
at the Jung-gu District Office.
Yes, that's right.
Will you take me to that hotel?
I'd like to meet with the owner.
Do you know...
my boss?
Hotel del Luna's Ms. Jang Man-wol.
I used to be
a manager who served Ms. Jang
at the hotel.
Didn't you get off work early today?
I brought a pleasant guest.
Ji Hyeon-jung,
do you still skip work
and leave the front desk unattended?
Ms. Hwang!
Goodness.
What brings you here?
You're not dead, are you?
You still can't tell the difference?
I'm alive.
You scared me.
By the way,
should I call you President Hwang now?
I'm only a candidate for now.
Mr. Kim. Ms. Choe.
Ms. Hwang is here.
My goodness. You two are still here.
Ms. Hwang.
It's been a long time.
It's been a while.
Has it been over 30 years
since we last met?
You've gotten old.
You still make
such straightforward comments.
Do you have a lot of guests
at the hotel right now?
I can't see anyone else
other than the hotel's employees now.
There are a few.
There's Ms. Jang.
Your hotel has become so big.
It's all thanks to you, Mun-suk.
Thanks to the money you made back then,
we were able to move to Myeong-dong
and got big.
It seems you've become a big shot too.
I saw you a lot on the phone.
I hear you'll become a president
of somewhere big soon.
I'm just a candidate for now.
I'm thankful you let me free.
Do you think I let you go
because I wanted to?
Mago thought someone talented like you
shouldn't be tied up to a place like this.
She gave you the medicine behind my back,
and you couldn't see ghosts anymore.
So I had no choice but to let you go.
I wish you had stayed
for a few more years back then
and made more money for me.
I'd have quite a lot of land
in Gangnam right now.
Thanks to the experience here,
the way I see the world
and the things I value
have changed greatly.
Sure. It seems like
you are doing a lot of good work.
Why are you here anyway?
I have a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
Of course.
I know there's nothing
you would miss here.
You must be here
because you want something.
Oh, right.
I brought a present
that might suit you well.
Gosh.
You shouldn't have brought such a thing.
Oh, my god.
Okay. What's the favor you want?
It's something trivial,
but very important.
We're getting
another big lunar eclipse after 39 years.
This country was seeing
an economic revival at that time.
And thanks to Mun-suk's appearance,
Ms. Jang was able to turn the poor
business into a successful one,
laying the groundwork for the wealth
and luxury she's enjoying now.
She worked here
for about seven to eight years.
I never imagined such a person
would've worked here as a manager.
Because Ms. Jang doesn't leave
any traces of the human managers
who used to work here.
However,
I wonder why she came here when she has
such a big event happening soon.
We're going to take human guests?
Is that possible?
Yes, because a lunar eclipse is coming.
Are things different with a lunar eclipse?
When the moon's covered during an eclipse,
the Guest House of the Moon's presence
is exposed.
That's why we get quite a few human guests
during eclipses.
Even humans are able to see our ghost
guests when they come into our hotel.
So, do we accept human guests
on the day of the lunar eclipse?
The front desk turns them away, of course.
But...
Did that happen in 1981?
When Mun-suk was here
during a lunar eclipse,
some newlyweds stayed at our hotel.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
it's past the curfew.
-I'm sorry.
-Is it this way?
Yes. That way.
HOTEL DEL LUNA
I think this is a hotel.
The lunar eclipse better end soon.
-Excuse me.
-Do you have a room?
Newlyweds?
They came to Seoul for their honeymoon,
and now it's past curfew.
If we turn them away now,
they'll have to spend
their first night at the police station.
I feel bad for them.
Let them in, then.
This is your room.
Please go in.
-Thank you.
Thank you so much.
The couple spent
their first night at our hotel.
At that night, a human baby was conceived
for the first time
at this ghost hotel.
And that baby grew up to be
Korea's most talented soccer player.
Really?
He got conceived here?
Yes, apparently. I was shocked too
when I heard about it earlier.
Anyway, he's going to become
Mun-suk's son-in-law.
-Really?
-She went to meet her future in-laws
and met the newlywed couple.
They were all so surprised.
What an interesting coincidence.
But then again,
this place is full of unimaginable things.
I guess it's natural that the baby
turned out to be someone special.
She wants us to let her daughter
and future son-in-law
stay here for one night so they can
also experience the same thing.
Then, are we going to let them stay
in the room that the King stayed in?
No, they're humans.
They should stay in Room 404.
Room 404?
But no one can check out of that room.
The only way you can check out
of our hotel is head for the afterlife.
Then how are they supposed to check out
of Room 404?
Are you worried about them?
Then why don't you go in there
and check for yourself?
On the night of this year's lunar eclipse,
we'll be welcoming human guests.
They're newlyweds.
It'll be their honeymoon.
They made an official reservation
this time,
so get ready to treat them well.
-Yes, ma'am.
We need to get food and decorations
that are fit for humans.
I'm excited to hear
that we'll be getting human guests.
But where's our manager?
He went inside Room 404.
Then I guess he won't be
returning tonight.
Whatever the case, I'm really excited.
Veronica.
Are you in Wai Tan in Shanghai?
Yes, I was in a meeting,
but I came out to eat lunch now.
-Sanchez, I'm so upset at you.
-Why? Why are you upset?
I miss you so much.
You really make it hard
for me to focus on work.
I'm going to scold you.
Veronica, I can't wait to meet you
so you can scold me.
Veronica.
I found a way to get scolded by you
forever. You can look forward to it.
Gosh, what are you
going to surprise me with this time?
I can't tell you. You can come here
and check for yourself.
Chan-sung's here.
Say hello.
Hey, Chan-sung.
Hi, Veronica.
Veronica, I'll call you later.
I love you. Goodbye, my love.
Bye.
-Is Veronica coming to Korea?
-Yes.
She's in Shanghai right now.
She's going to come in two days.
So I've been thinking...
I'm planning to do
something really important.
And I'm thinking about doing it
at your hotel.
My hotel?
Veronica's been to all kinds
of hotels all over the world.
When I told her that you work
at a really special hotel,
she wanted to take a look.
I'm also quite curious.
No, you can't do it at my hotel.
Chan-sung, you're not exactly working
at a decent hotel, are you?
-What?
-You had to invite someone
to our house to sell a painting.
And Man-wol even asked me
to sell her horses.
Are you guys struggling financially?
Yes, it's pretty bad.
My goodness.
Chan-sung, let me know
if you're having a hard time.
You can't just endure everything
with love.
Okay?
Okay.
Fine, let's break up.
My gosh.
Mi-ra's fighting all the time.
She and the cop must've been enemies
in their past lives.
They fight all the time.
But she always goes out to meet him.
What? You're not the only one who's busy.
I'm busy too.
You talk like your job is
to save the world.
You think you're a superhero or something?
What?
They were enemies in their past lives.
Sanchez, let's all eat together
when Veronica comes to Korea.
-She's coming in two days, right?
-Yes.
-That's the day of the lunar eclipse.
-Yes, I know.
I was planning on watching
the lunar eclipse at the rooftop bar
in your hotel that you bragged about.
Maybe next time.
I'm sorry.
They could get startled
if they run into other hotel guests.
So we should empty the adjacent rooms.
We already informed the guests
on the fourth floor.
We're moving them to other rooms.
You really are well prepared.
The dinner menu is great.
What kind of drink are you going to...
Are you going to serve them these drinks?
I took your advice
and created my own signature menu.
They're the Angel and Devil.
It's incredible.
But I'm not sure if humans will like them.
Could you try them?
Sure.
Put half of them on the dinner table
and the other half in their room.
Yes, sir.
It's a bee.
I guess the bee came along
since these are real flowers.
I guess we don't have
any bees or butterflies here
since the flowers here are not real.
By any chance,
are there also bug ghosts
that look like fireflies?
I've never heard of anything
called a bug ghost.
Oh, I see.
Then what was that?
Should I put this bouquet in their room?
Yes, sure.
That one looks more romantic.
Wait.
I'd like to put one in my office.
Please follow me.
God... I'm so tired.
You got a lot of special requests
again today, didn't you?
You're all so excited
about those human guests.
I'm the only one
who's taking care of our actual guests.
My gosh, the day feels so long.
My goodness, I'm so tired.
Then here's something to wake you up.
This is a real flower, so it smells nice.
We have tons of flowers in our garden.
None of them are real.
No, wait. Your flowers are real.
That tree of yours is
filled with beautiful flowers.
What's with you?
Are you showing off?
I'm entitled to show off.
The flowers bloomed
the moment I hugged you.
If I knew this was going to happen,
I should've hugged you
instead of buying you champagne.
What are you doing?
I never asked you to hug me.
Are you crazy?
I was asking for the phone.
Okay, here. I'll let you hug me.
Forget it.
You arrogant, greedy fraud from Harvard--
You look so pretty.
I put the additional special requests
on your desk.
You should get back to work
after you get some rest.
Darn it.
I won't let you vanish.
Trust me.
It's real.
You,
I'm going easy on you
because you have a soft heart.
The lunar eclipse has begun.
There will be special guests
coming tonight.
Please do your best
to get ready for the guests.
Everyone seems quite excited.
As the moon gets covered,
they can feel the hotel's presence
is shown to the world.
And human guests are coming as well.
That makes them
feel like they're alive again.
Welcome.
You made a reservation, right?
How long has it been
since you passed away--
I mean, how long has it been
since you got married?
Right, you got married today!
Congratulations.
Please follow me this way.
We'll take your luggage to your room.
You can enjoy your meals first.
These cocktails, Tears, are
our hotel's signature cocktails.
This beautiful one is called
the Angel's Tears.
And this one is called the Devil's Tears.
Why are you so happy?
I hated looking at the full moon.
But look, it's all gone now.
It feels so good watching that.
This is my favorite moment ever.
The whole moon is covered now.
The moon will be different
when it comes out again.
Perhaps it'll know how to be kind
and cut down on spending.
After our human guests
check out of the hotel,
would you like to go out
and see the new, kind moon?
You evil moon.
Do you want to die, Chan-sung?
I'll take that as a yes.
This is why I love my name.
I love how it means "yes."
It's like everyone agrees with me.
It's perfect.
Zero looks like a circle.
And "Koo" means a circle.
Koo Chan-sung.
Sure, Mr. Zeroth Choice,
your name is Mr. Okay Koo now.
What do you mean?
My English name is Andrew.
Chan-sung isn't just okay,
it means "agreement."
Agree, Andrew, whatever.
You're just Okay Koo to me.
Okay?
Okay Koo,
the lunar eclipse is finally complete.
You're right.
This sign means it's yours, right?
Yes.
I wonder if he was waiting for her.
Ms. Jang.
Our guests would like
to go into their room now.
Okay, the lunar eclipse is complete.
It's perfect. Take them to Room 404.
Yes.
Once you go inside,
please don't come out of the room
until you check out.
I already heard about this room
from my parents.
Have a good night then.
A world-famous soccer player
was conceived here.
Who do you think will be next?
You've been a kid for 70 years,
so you wouldn't know this.
But things like this
don't happen just overnight.
I know that it doesn't happen
just overnight.
Why are you laughing?
I know it all.
Really?
Don't just assume
that I don't know things.
We're talking about lives here.
It's not a conversation
a Grim Ripper could jump into.
I hope
that a great scholar will be conceived
this time.
I hope the child will receive
a Nobel Prize.
I hope that triplets will be conceived
so that they'd win three Nobel Prizes.
All the guests and employees at the hotel
are rooting for Room 404 right now.
Veronica hasn't arrived yet?
I waited for her,
thinking that her flight was delayed,
but the flight was never delayed.
She's not even picking up her phone.
Chan-sung,
do you think Veronica knew
I was going to propose
and is avoiding me
because she's feeling pressured?
Veronica loves you more than you love her.
No, I love her so much more.
Veronica has never broken
any promises with me.
I just got a text.
It must be from Veronica.
I'll call you later.
Sanchez.
Sanchez!
An accident? What happened?
Veronica got hurt.
I think she got into a car accident
in Shanghai.
I have to go now.
How badly is she hurt?
I have to go and see.
-I'm sure she'll be fine.
-Yes.
Hey, I have to stay there
until she gets better.
Okay.
Where's my car key?
I have to go.
Even if you go there,
you won't be able to see her.
Hey, don't say that.
You won't be able to see her.
It's too late.
What's with you?
It's not too late!
If I go now, I can see her.
Sanchez.
I'll let you see her.
What?
If you come to my hotel now,
you can meet her.
Hey. What the hell are you talking about?
Do you trust me? We don't have much time.
You won't be able to see her
if you're late.
Mr. Koo.
There is a lady guest
who'll come in right after us.
We'll be waiting for her
at the Sky Lounge.
Please bring her over
after the beauty service.
Sure.
Let go of me.
What are we going to do here?
You'll see once you go out there.
I'll tell you after you see this.
Hey, how are you working here?
This is a very special hotel.
It's a hotel for the dead.
What?
I have no time to explain.
You can see the dead
until the eclipse is over.
So,
you'll have only a little time
to say goodbye to Veronica.
What?
Stop joking around.
How could she come here?
Because she's dead.
She is here.
Sanchez, Veronica is dead.
I'm sorry...
I surprised you like this.
Don't cry too much...
for me.
I lived
a happy life thanks to you.
My awfully handsome love.
Goodbye.
Mr. Koo's friend
had to say goodbye to his love.
Such a sudden death leaves
those left behind
with great sorrow.
I only see the dead these days,
so it's been a while
since I saw the sorrow
of the living.
Yes, come in.
Did you have a great night?
Yes. We won't be able to forget
the time we spent
in this hotel.
Thank you. Take care then.
It's exactly like what my parents told me.
It's a hotel you can never find again.
When we have a baby later,
let's find the hotel and have the baby
go on their honeymoon there like we did.
I'd like that.
Veronica's funeral will be held in Italy.
Sanchez will stay there for a while.
I feel so sorry for Sanchez.
He couldn't even see
his girlfriend's last moments.
He didn't get to say goodbye.
He saw her. He got to say goodbye too.
He learned that death isn't the end,
so I'm sure Sanchez will be able
to get through it.
So he got to say goodbye.
But how did he see her?
Didn't she die in Shanghai?
Gosh, this coffee smells so good.
You should have another.
I'm sorry.
She's really tailing me.
Why would such a cute student follow me?
I better ask her.
I heard they really enjoyed their stay.
Thank you.
If you end up quitting your job
at Hotel del Luna, come look for me.
Ms. Jang told me
that you're quite competent
and recommended you to me.
I don't think I'll be quitting.
According to Ms. Jang,
you're going to quit soon.
There's a guest
Chan-sung will have to send off himself.
Once he sends off that guest,
he'll probably leave this place.
Did she say that?
Did they come up with a new rule
for the hotel manager?
Who is the last guest
you'll be sending off?
It's someone...
I like a lot.
It'll be difficult for you.
I think so.
It's too hard for me to console myself...
by saying I know it's coming.
What were you doing? Were you sleeping?
I'm awake.
I'm looking at the moon.
The moon?
How can you see the moon during the day?
I don't know.
It must be pretty hard
to miss something you can't see.
Where are you?
I'm on my way home.
Wait at home. I'll come to see you.
What is it, Yu-na?
81GI 0963
I've found that car.
Where are you right now? Where?
Don't move. Stay right there.
Why did she follow me all the way here?
Yu-na!
The man in the sketch
and the owner of that car look alike.
Could he be the culprit?
What's the matter?
He looks a lot like...
someone I know.
I'll look into it now. You should go home.
Okay.
I told him to wait,
but he's making me wait.
Anyone here?
Is anybody here?
The dreaded Mago has come
instead of the one I've been waiting for.
Why?
I'm the deity you've been waiting for
the most.
Am I wrong?
You didn't care about reincarnation,
healing, and connections.
You only wished to see me and vanish.
So? Are you here to do that for me?
I've heard the flowers have bloomed.
You finally have
something to lose too.
Do you think
I'm afraid to see the flowers fall?
What about the one
that helped you bloom the flowers?
What if you lose him?
Long time no see, Chan-sung.
Man-wol, you conceited and foolish thing.
Did you say you weren't afraid
to see the flowers fall?
No.
Your flowers will begin to fall
when you become afraid.
So the price Chan-sung needs to pay
in return
won't be fair nor reasonable.
You can stroke my hair in your room
to help me fall asleep.
What's with you? You're too naughty.
You were really scared.
I don't want you to pay the price,
so I'll do everything I can
to clean up after you.
Don't be afraid when you leave me behind.
This is how I, just a weak human,
love you with all my heart.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu
What about the one
that helped you bloom the flowers?
What if you lose him?
Man-wol, you conceited and foolish thing.
Did you say
you aren't afraid to see the flowers fall?
No.
Your flowers will begin to fall
when you become afraid.
Long time no see, Chan-sung.
Are you waiting for me to say,
"Why are you doing this to me?
I'm so scared."
And when I start shivering in fear
and the flowers slowly start to fall,
is that when you'll drag me
to my afterlife?
I'm not surprised.
I already know how cheap you guys can be.
There's no need to wait.
You should just bring him to me
right now.
We can end this once and for all,
and I'll finally vanish.
That's exactly what I've been wishing for
during the endless years I had to endure.
Koo Chan-sung
will eventually bring him to you.
Why do you keep
getting Chan-sung involved?
I'm not the one
who got him involved in this.
It's the one that wants you
to leave in peace.
You've been enduring
for the past 1,000 years,
and all you wish is to cease to exist.
So the price Chan-sung needs to pay
in return
won't be fair nor reasonable.
I tried to stop him.
He chose to stay by my side.
You wicked thing.
Yes, that's right.
I'm a wicked witch who made him stay
even when I knew
what he'd end up going through.
Yes, you're right. You are very wicked.
Because of you,
he even had to encounter the person
that hurt him the most.
What more do you think
he'll have to go through because of you?
You're shaking like a leaf.
It's very amusing to watch.
You're Chan-sung, right?
Don't you remember me?
I'm Seol Ji-won.
We used to study in Boston together.
Yes, Seol Ji-won.
It's you.
What brings you here?
Did Sanchez tell you about me?
Or was it Mi-ra?
No, it was someone else.
She told me she saw you on the street.
But I'm surprised that you're really here.
Oh, really?
I'm sure you didn't come here
because you missed me.
So, what brings you here?
I heard you came back to Korea
to get into law school.
Did you quit studying?
You told me your father was a judge.
Did he give up on you?
He didn't give up on me,
but he did pass away.
So I'm just doing what I like to do now.
And what exactly is that?
It must be wine.
Do you have a lot of good wine?
Can I have a glass?
Okay, sure.
Was it him?
Did he kill you?
What are you doing here?
What about you? What did you do here?
Is what you like to do...
murdering people?
Why won't he pick up his phone?
I need to go back to Chan-sung's place.
You've been there many times already.
He'll come.
He didn't show up or pick up the phone.
This is weird.
I need to know where he is to go find him.
I'm sure there's a reason.
Why are you so restless?
What about the one
that helped you bloom the flowers?
What if you lose him?
I heard something ominous.
I'm going to go find him.
Ms. Jang.
Why won't he pick up the phone?
-Hello?
-What am I going to do?
What's wrong, Yu-na?
I think Mr. Koo got hurt.
What if he died?
What?
Mr. Third Choice is dead?
I think he was killed when he went
to catch the murderer.
Ms. Jang.
This is bad.
Mr. Koo is dead.
What?
Yu-na followed some car
to find the murderer of the guests,
but Mr. Koo said
it was too dangerous for her
and went over himself.
Stop talking nonsense.
Why would Chan-sung die?
Yu-na saw him carried into an ambulance.
Explain the situation.
What happened?
Stop crying!
Mr. Koo?
Ji Hyeon-jung, you little... Come here.
-Ms. Jang! Goodness, Ms. Jang!
-You jerk!
Ms. Jang!
-You said he--
-My goodness.
You didn't die. I'm so relieved.
Goodness.
You're alive.
I thought you came as a guest.
What? A guest...
You went there to meet the murderer alone.
We couldn't get a hold of you
and heard someone got badly hurt.
I thought it was you.
I knew it could be dangerous.
I didn't go in there without any plan.
I had already called
a police officer I knew.
Freeze.
Great job. Then who got hurt?
The culprit.
Seol Ji-won,
you are under arrest for murder.
Put that down.
He's not in critical condition now,
so he will live to pay for what he did.
Gosh, I'm so relieved.
I was really shocked
because I thought you came as a guest.
I knew he wasn't a guest
as soon as I saw him.
No, you didn't. You cried.
I saw you wiping your tears.
I had a runny nose.
Ms. Choe, I saw your legs shaking.
I'm sorry that I made everyone worried.
And thank you for worrying about me.
Our dead hearts skipped a beat
thanks to you.
That was thrilling.
Ms. Jang will begin
to throw a huge fit soon,
so let's survive that too.
Okay.
-We can do it!
Jang Man-wol.
Where did she go?
I brought an extra one because I knew
a few bottles wouldn't cut it.
Jang Man-wol, where have you been?
Did you go shopping?
Chan-sung, sit down.
Did you go to the pharmacy?
Yes, we don't have anything
that can treat the living.
Did you clean the entire pharmacy out?
Just sit down, will you?
Let me see.
You're all wounded.
What do I have to put on you?
Let's put on the most expensive one.
-That stings.
-It hurts?
Darn it. I guess
this ointment isn't a good one.
Let me see.
Wait, this is the ointment
for hemorrhoids.
What?
Sorry. I applied the ointment
for buttholes on your face.
Come here.
No, that's okay.
If this heals buttholes,
I'm sure it'll heal my face too.
Buttholes and faces aren't the same.
Give it back. I'll apply another one.
Were you scared
that I died
and came to the hotel as a guest?
How could you of all people
be confused and scared?
Because I was afraid.
Just like the world turned pitch-dark,
I was scared.
No matter how desperately I wanted money,
I never made that kind of mistake.
You made me look like a fool.
All of my employees were watching too.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
What is this? Darn it.
Wait here.
I'll go look for a guest
who was a pharmacist.
You seem pretty shook up yourself.
Shouldn't you take some medicine?
Why? Do you have any pills for that?
You were really scared.
Are you a pharmacist or what?
I'm supposed to take care of you.
Your flowers will begin to fall
when you become afraid.
I have good news too.
Your Yeon-u...
Right. Detective Park Yeong-su
caught the culprit.
He'll probably get promoted.
I found all the drugs and syringes
he used to kill the victims.
I think he illegally smuggled in
the drugs while importing wine.
It's the symbol of
the website Helllo, right?
Did you find Seol Ji-won in the website?
Actually,
I received a tip.
Who?
You're the dead woman, Lee Do-yeon?
My husband isn't the culprit.
The murderer is right here.
You shouldn't make a prank call.
Blood. There's blood.
He collected samples of blood
from his victims.
Please come here. It's dangerous here.
The lead that there were traces
that the victims' blood was drawn
was never disclosed to the public.
I came here because that bothered me.
I really found their blood here.
He's really like a demon.
He displayed the victims' blood
among his wine bottles.
But who do you think gave me that call?
There's no way a dead woman
could have called me.
That's really strange.
You can't let a ghost
take over your body like that.
Promise me. Don't you ever do
something like that without me.
The ghost just helped me call it in
and gather evidence.
Take them with you.
And go home and rest for the day.
Now I have a lot to take home.
-What's this?
-A massager.
Put it on your neck
before going to sleep. It'll be nice.
There are an sleep mask
and a bottle of champagne.
Right. Caviar. This is really expensive,
just so you know.
Take your time with it.
You gave me things
that are very valuable to you.
Take one of my cars
since you have a lot...
Forget it.
You should just keep driving one.
Really?
The red one. Can I take the red one?
What?
Why? Do you like the color red?
You don't like it.
I do.
Is that so?
Really?
Sure.
There's only one red car,
but you can drive it.
You can keep it.
Thank you.
This isn't the right key.
It's that one. Over there.
Here.
It's nice to have a near-death experience.
I'll just drive this one.
Are you kidding me?
I was testing you.
The red car versus me. I won.
You would've lost
if it was a new poop colored car.
I know that your favorite is the red one.
I beat the red car.
It means I beat them all.
I had no idea you were such a sly snake.
I think I need to go
to the police station a few times.
To explain what happened
without involving the ghost,
I really have to be a sly snake this time.
Anyway, Yeon-u must be flustered.
He received two tips from ghosts.
He may have a fine figure,
but he got scared easily
and found ghosts really scary.
Yeon-u did?
You must've grown up with him
since you were young.
Yeon-u's mother raised me.
When I was very young,
I was dying in the wilds.
A merchant who was passing by
saved me, apparently.
And Yeon-u's mom was the one
who took me in.
But she passed away not long after.
Yeon-u and I were
practically brother and sister.
That's how we lived.
He was dexterous,
so he'd make clothes for me too.
I think he's living
a good life as a cop now.
I don't think
I've told you about my past before.
You haven't.
-Perhaps, the flowers are the reason.
-Maybe it's time for them to fall.
I should go.
Hey.
Maybe it's time for them to fall.
I hope you keep it up
and take good care of me
and then...
see me off.
That's what Mago wants.
You must be doing a good job.
I think the flower will bloom.
You should look after it well
so you can send her off.
Who is the last guest
you'll be sending off?
I'll become your last customer.
When you see me off,
don't feel lonely.
When will he wake up?
Probably in a couple of hours.
-Did he wake up?
-He will in a few hours.
-Where did he go?
-He was here a second ago.
Don't just stand there. Find him!
I'm sorry, sir!
Is what you like to do...
murdering people?
What are you talking about?
You killed...
a person.
Says who?
The person you killed...
is here with us.
You're insane.
Do you think it's over once people die?
Our souls remain.
Your seventh victim is here
with us at the moment.
And this is...
her blood.
Must I find the other six for you
to believe me?
-Who are you?
-I didn't find them.
Your victim did.
Don't lie to me. That's impossible.
You may not know this,
but she's been next to you
this whole time.
She's also telling me what you are hiding
behind you.
So, ghosts exist?
Will you be here soon?
What time?
That's too late.
DETECTIVE PARK YEONG-SU
Yes, Detective.
Mr. Koo, we need you here
at the hospital now.
You're here.
As I said on the phone,
Seol Ji-won will only talk to you.
Would that be all right?
Yes.
You're here.
Look at where I am thanks to you.
No, this is on you.
What brought you here is
the victim you killed.
You said ghosts existed.
Is someone aiding you right now as well?
Yes, I have someone protecting me
even at this moment.
Is this the guy?
Should I just push him?
No, don't.
He must live and suffer,
paying for what he's done.
Sure.
I don't want to go through the trouble
because of some scumbag anyway.
-Of course.
-Hey!
What are you doing?
I was talking to my guardian about you.
Damn you, Chan-sung.
My life started to fall apart
because of you, you know.
No, it was because of what you had done.
Cute.
Do you have proof that I sent it?
Also, who will believe you?
You think you're something
just because you're smart, don't you?
You're so full of yourself.
No one has to believe me
except for one person.
The man who knew his youngest son so well
that he sent the son abroad.
I'm talking about your father, a judge.
How about we have a little bet?
Between his son who isn't reliable at all
and a straight-A student
of a prestigious US university,
who will your father believe?
Before I tell your father
about everything,
get lost.
I should've just pulled
the trigger back then.
Do you
know him personally?
Our ill-fated relationship goes way back.
I thought it had been severed,
but we met again.
Because of you,
he even had to encounter the person
that hurt him the most.
What more do you think
he'll have to go through because of you?
What you've done
won't end with your death.
The only way to save your soul is
to stay alive and pay for your sins.
How are they my sins?
I just did what other people
asked me to do.
Do you have any idea
how enthusiastic people become
when it comes to hating
and cursing others?
Soccer players score goals
because that's what people want.
And I killed those people
because that was what people wanted,
so how is that my responsibility?
That's probably where people go
to express their filthy emotions.
But no one actually wants someone
to put their filthy thoughts into action.
Get down here, Ji-won!
I uploaded a post
to express my hatred for you.
I hope it receives a lot of support.
I guess you're able to see me now.
He was right.
Death really isn't the end.
Yes.
You're a ghost now.
Chan-sung probably didn't want this
to happen,
but I couldn't wait for you
to fall down the building and die.
I'm not allowed to harm
a living human being.
But it's a vengeful ghost like you,
that's not the case.
"A vengeful ghost"?
You deserve to be thrown
in a garbage truck.
I'll destroy you and turn you to ashes.
I hope you turn into trash
and head to your afterlife.
What was that?
What's protecting you?
It must be my resentment.
My hatred and curse are
making people go wild.
I will sacrifice my life
to curse Koo Chan-sung,
the guy who ruined my life.
COMPLETE
YOUR POST HAS BEEN UPLOADED
I HOPE HE DIES
I CURSE HIM TOO
These people's ugly thoughts and emotions
must've given you
a hideous type of strength.
Who are you to protect Chan-sung?
Shut it, you piece of trash.
You stink.
I'll get rid of this hideous power
that's protecting you now
and rip you into pieces.
You just wait.
I'm going to become
even uglier and more powerful.
I requested the Helllo website to delete
the posts that Seol Ji-won uploaded.
But we couldn't do anything about the ones
that already went viral on the web.
I'm sorry.
There's no need for you to apologize.
Is it okay if I go now?
Sure.
Oh, wait.
When you were at the wine bar,
were you with a woman by any chance?
The thing is,
I got a call from the wine bar.
And the woman who called told me
that she was the late Lee Do-yeon.
I know it doesn't make sense,
but I was just wondering--
It could've been her.
I believe that souls exist.
I also believe in reincarnation.
Oh, reincarnation? I see.
You draw very well.
You must be quite dexterous.
Thank you.
Okay, then.
Seol Ji-won
died.
I know.
I met him as a ghost.
He has become a vengeful ghost,
and he holds resentment toward you.
Yes, I know. I read the post he uploaded.
I'm quite shocked
at how much support he got.
Darn it.
I should've turned him to ashes
the moment he died.
I should've brought a gun
instead of a folding fan.
Was he strong enough to escape from you?
I want to act like it's not a big deal,
but it is a big deal.
Chan-sung.
Don't go home until we catch him.
Stay right by my side.
Do you think Ms. Jang will ban me
from coming to this hotel?
She probably forgot about it already.
Mr. Koo turned out to be okay,
so everything will be fine.
-Really?
-Of course.
But thanks to you, our hotel guests
were able to reveal their wrongful deaths.
Good job, Yu-na.
Gosh, what a relief.
We got a new guest last night,
and she asked if she could meet you.
What?
You're that woman.
Thank you for following me
until the very end.
THE LATE JEONG SU-JEONG
This is where I actually am.
But I was too scared to come here.
This is my first time.
I got murdered as well.
And I feel like I consoled myself
by helping out with the murder case.
I secretly brought it
from the hotel garden.
Let's put this inside.
-Hyeon-jung.
-Yes?
Where are you buried?
Somewhere in the mountain.
I don't have a grave.
Then let's share this space together.
That's me.
I was just practicing drawing portraits.
This is our grave now.
Do you like it?
Don't you like it?
Well, then. Just forget it.
I already told you that I liked you,
but you ignored it.
I didn't ignore it.
Yu-na.
Your boyfriend
should be someone kind
and alive.
That's why...
I like you.
Can't you just like me too--
Chan-sung.
Wake up.
Why are you sleeping
in this uncomfortable couch?
The only rooms
I can sleep in at this hotel
is Room 404 and yours.
If I end up in Incheon
after sleeping in Room 404,
I'll have a hard time coming to work.
Who told you to sleep in Room 404?
I told you to sleep in my room.
You'll fall asleep in no time
with the massager and sleep mask.
Do you think I'll be able to fall asleep
in your room
even if I had that massager?
You're right.
After all, you are very healthy.
Gosh, humans need to sleep well.
Too bad for you.
Let's go, then.
Let me sleep comfortably in your room.
I don't need that massager.
I'd rather have your arm.
If you let me use your arm as a pillow,
I don't need that sleep mask.
You can stroke my hair
to help me
fall asleep.
What's with you? You're too naughty.
Cool it down.
You cool it down. You're blushing.
I feel so stiff.
Maybe I should try the massager.
Gosh.
I am not blushing...
Chan-sung.
Forget the massager.
Let's go get acupuncture.
-What?
-Let's get acupuncture
and cupping therapy to let some blood out.
I know a good oriental clinic.
There's a famous doctor
who can even bring a dead person back.
You did a great job, ma'am!
HYOSAENG ORIENTAL CLINIC
Be sure to come in daily
to get acupuncture.
Doctor, your herbal medicine
is too expensive.
It's only because it's really effective.
And I even gave you
some free samples as well!
Thank you.
You mean that doctor
brought back a dead person?
He's keeping someone who should have died
three years ago alive.
He must be an amazing doctor.
Take care, ma'am.
Is he a reincarnation of Hua Tuo?
I don't know.
Ma'am, don't hesitate.
Buy them for your family members.
I'll give you ten percent off.
I'll need to think about it.
All right, ma'am.
Take care.
Keep recommending it to her.
He seems
a bit greedy, though, like someone I know.
You have a guest, honey.
Thank you for coming.
Please follow me.
You don't look too good.
She must be his wife.
They look alike.
Anyway, we have to take the patient
he's been keeping alive
to our hotel.
But, isn't the patient still alive?
How are we supposed
to take them as a guest?
By killing, of course.
The Grim Reaper told me
to make sure to kill the patient.
You even run errands for the Grim Reaper?
It's not an errand!
It's a deal.
I need you to take care of someone for me.
I want your help.
If you couldn't handle him on your own,
he must be quite strong.
He holds a really deep grudge,
so one of my people could get hurt
if I'm not cautious.
Quietly bring him to me.
It's your request.
How can I reject it?
But you'll need to do me a favor as well.
Go on.
There's someone
who's been causing me trouble.
It's an unsolved case
that has disgraced me.
If you bring that person
to Hotel del Luna,
I'll bring that vengeful ghost...
to you.
Deal.
Is Seol Ji-won that dangerous?
The reason your ill-fated relationship
is haunting you
may be me.
Mago told me that.
You made the flowers bloom,
so you will have to pay the price for it.
The price I have to pay
for making the flowers bloom
is having a vengeful ghost haunt me?
I don't want you to pay the price,
so I'll do everything I can
to clean up after you.
Thank you for that.
EMERGENCY FUND
Mr. Koo Chan-sung?
Here.
Please come in.
Is my job to see
how good of a doctor he is?
Take this with you.
Tell him this is why you came.
The hepatization slowed down
your stomach contractions,
which is why you have indigestion
and a pressure on your chest.
It must be due to stress.
Yes. I do have a lot on my mind lately.
Is that so?
You can get the acupuncture treatment
and some medicine.
It's best if you take
my herbal medicine too.
I don't need acupuncture or medicine.
The reason for my stress is money.
That's why
I came here after seeing this.
I need the money.
EMERGENCY FUND
This is your number, right?
We were running short on time.
What a relief.
I need to check something.
Your palm lines look good.
You have a good lifeline, too.
Give me one centimeter of your lifeline.
If you sell me your lifeline,
I will give you 50 million won.
He buys other people's lifelines
and keeps a person
who should be dead alive?
I guess that doctor really is great.
Is it possible to buy
other people's lifelines with money?
Well, if it is a fair deal.
It's not a fraud. He pays well.
So that's why the Grim Reaper
couldn't do anything.
The person who sold it
wouldn't have thought it was for real.
They would've thought it was easy money.
Only the buyer is desperate.
I guess he uses it to make more money.
Do you think he sells it
to a wealthy person?
An important person, I suppose.
You'll be having surgery tonight,
so let's feed you some meat. Let's go.
You just want to have meat, don't you?
There's...
A restaurant Kim Jun-hyun visited
around here.
I know. Let's go.
I got someone to sell his lifeline.
I was very worried
since the one who promised me backed out.
What a relief.
That means you have to spend
all the money you've saved up so far.
Money isn't the problem.
As long as I can save him,
that's all right.
But you worked so hard to earn that money.
The surgery is today.
I must take a look.
Hyeon-jin is sleeping.
You can get surgery today.
It's a boy?
Yes.
The life we must take away
is the couple's son.
I didn't know
Man-wol could look so stunning.
Once the flowers fall,
will that be the end of the Moon Tree?
Yes.
That means the death of Man-wol...
who I have chained to this tree.
Man-wol will finally
be able to go to the afterlife.
It's been too long
for Man-wol
who has blossomed to the fullest
and for the guy who had to remain
as a small light.
He turned back when I was
accompanying him to the afterlife.
He's managed to stay here
for such a long time.
You should
get going too.
Live your life as a traitor.
That way, Man-wol can live.
I let him be
because you told me not to take him.
It is quite impressive
that a soul of a human can remain
for this long as a small light.
It's a curse he cast upon himself.
He's
staying here as a small light
because of the promise
he made to Man-wol.
Ms. Jang
took an assignment from me
in order to lessen the burden
on Koo Chan-sung
for making her flowers blossom.
It sounds like Man-wol doesn't know
the price Chan-sung has to pay yet.
Once she finds out,
she will be sad
and scared.
Are you nervous
that he might take your lifeline?
I guess you must want to live a long life.
Don't worry. You'll live a long life.
I was trying to figure it out.
How his parents must have felt
to buy someone else's lifelines
and attach them on their son.
That means I'll protect you,
so he can't take away yours.
I'm just protecting your lifeline.
They just don't want
to let go of their son.
They must be desperate to hold onto him.
You're here already.
Let's go to the treatment room.
It will neither hurt nor harm you.
I'll cut off exactly one centimeter.
Are you cutting my lifeline
to give it to your child?
Earlier today,
I heard that you have a sick son.
My son was severely ill.
After hearing about the lifeline surgery
overseas,
I tried it out
because I had nothing to lose.
Like a miracle, my son lived.
Both of you are still young.
It must've been quite an ordeal for you.
My son is young,
but my wife and I look quite old.
People think
we are his grandparents.
Hello?
DEMIAN
Were you reading a book?
That's a hard book.
It's not that hard.
I think it's all right
to show off how intelligent you are
if you're really that smart.
I like you.
Ma'am, are you the Grim Reaper too?
On the days I had surgery,
I always saw a man dressed
in a black suit in my dream.
He and I have totally different
themes for our black outfits.
He's just wearing black clothes.
And I'm wearing midnight black
with a hint of dark blue.
Midnight black and black are the same.
Really?
Whatever.
I am here to do something similar
to what he does.
I can't take you against your will.
You're a smart boy,
so you can hear me out,
think about it, and make a decision.
You do know
that your mom and dad
suddenly aged a lot, don't you?
Is it because of this?
Yes.
What they've attached there is
the lives of your mom and dad.
You paid the price,
so your desperation
to save your child was heard.
You didn't buy someone else's life.
You gave parts of your lives
to your child.
That's why you two
have aged a lot quicker.
I am not sure what you know,
but if my son lives,
I don't care what it takes.
Sadly, the child will
have to make the decision.
Once he makes the decision,
you must let him go.
Hyeon-jin!
-Wake up.
-Hyeon-jin.
What's wrong with him, honey?
Hyeon-jin.
Honey, what's wrong with him?
No, not yet, honey. What's wrong with him?
Honey...
No. Hyeon-jin, no.
No, wake up. Hyeon-jin!
I'm glad you resolved this.
If you had been any later,
I would've had to take away
all three of them.
His parents
may have wanted that.
If I go with you,
it'll be more painful for my mom and dad.
That's not for you to worry about.
It's for those who are left behind.
But...
I'm really afraid of that.
I'm afraid...
Do not be afraid.
I will find the evil ghost
just as I promised.
Okay.
Find that in a hurry
so that no one won't be scared anymore.
Even if it means I must give everything,
I still cannot let go.
After I, it's N, E, S, S, not Y.
-Isn't this right?
-Come.
-You did that on purpose, right?
-Blowing on it helps?
What does that look like to you?
The intern and the receptionist are
dating at work.
My goodness.
She just started here.
I can't believe they're dating already.
They're young.
A man and a woman are bound
to hit it off when they're together.
I guess it doesn't matter
if it's this life or the afterlife.
Goodness.
We've been together for 200 years,
but we're still very professional.
It wouldn't happen even after 2,000 years.
You aren't my type.
Not even in your dreams.
My dream? I didn't dream anything.
Hey, listen.
I don't like you either.
You're back already?
Yes.
Did Sanchez go crazy
after he went to the funeral?
What's with him?
Actually, I need to tell you something.
How did the funeral go?
You should have stayed longer.
I couldn't.
Veronica is still at your hotel.
Am I right, Chan-sung?
She's still there, isn't she?
He sounded so desperate,
so I couldn't tell him no.
He knows that he cannot come to the hotel
or see her even if he comes there.
But he thinks she's still at our hotel
even though he cannot see her.
I'll have a talk with him,
so please just play along.
Just until he gets better.
When will he get better?
Man-wol, thank you
for what you did last time.
I said goodbye to her thanks to you.
I'm making something that Veronica liked.
She loved it whenever I cooked it for her.
Can you bring it to her?
Sure, let's do that.
Chan-sung.
You're really bad at acting.
If you're going to do it, do it right.
Sanchez, do you have anything else
other than pizza for her?
You know, the shoes or jewelry
that Veronica used to like.
Oh, I can take a car too.
Can you really take it to her?
Of course, bring everything.
I'll take anything to her.
Oh, we have a sea in my hotel.
How about the yacht?
It would be great
if she plays on that yacht at the hotel.
Jang Man-wol!
What?
I'm comforting him.
If Sanchez doesn't get better soon,
he'll end up giving me everything he has.
Why are you doing this?
It's because you didn't tell him
the truth.
I'm trying to comfort him
because he's in pain.
Do you find that silly?
Yes, it's ridiculous to me.
Parents who buy lifelines
for their almost dead son,
and your friend who's making pizza
for his dead girlfriend.
They all look ridiculous to me.
They look pathetic and make me angry.
Don't you dare turn
into someone like them.
Why do you assume
that I won't be just like them?
I don't want to let you go.
I don't want to send you off.
The thought of not being able to see you
drives me crazy.
How...
How could you tell me to be okay?
You're the one who must send me off.
Tell me that you'll be okay.
If you don't tell me you'll be okay,
I'll be...
too scared.
A long time ago,
I told you that I was afraid
of paying the price
if I did stay by your side
and look into you.
I guess this is the price.
Becoming a nuisance...
that you despise.
Go.
I'll go to my friend.
She's not there anymore.
Veronica isn't there, is she?
Your flowers will begin to fall
when you become afraid.
When I first met you,
the flowers around here
blossomed beautifully.
Now, all of them are gone.
That day,
you were utterly scared
after seeing a ghost.
Today, I'm the scared one.
The flowers...
are falling off the tree.
I see.
The petals don't even remain
in this world.
They vanish
even before touching the ground.
I guess...
nothing will remain.
Maybe,
the flowers falling off your tree...
are falling onto me.
Just like the first leaf did.
And those petals have piled up.
So it's gotten heavier...
and painful to carry.
I'll consider shouldering the pile
as solely my responsibility.
So...
Don't be afraid when you leave me behind.
This is...
how I, just a weak human,
love you...
with all my heart.
It's too heartbreaking
if I remain only as a flower petal
that's bound to vanish.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu