Hotel Del Luna Blu-ray Disc 2
Subtitle re-timing by Jharel
Are you alive?
Or are you dead?
I'm just...
here.
I'm neither alive
nor dead.
I'm just stuck.
I'm confined in a time zone
that can't ever be turned back.
Let's go!
No!
You're the one
that led the group, aren't you?
You're the ringleader.
Hey.
You guys are thieves
from Gaori Village, aren't you?
That means you're a nomad from Goguryeo.
You get what I'm saying, don't you?
Hey!
Shut it.
I'm also from the same place.
Hello, brother.
Or should I call you "sister"?
"Sister"?
Sister.
Why don't you let me free now?
I'm just a low-class officer
in charge of escorting his superiors.
So you won't get much money
by holding me hostage.
I know how I'm going to get money.
What?
The noble lady who didn't even care
about losing her silk bundle
seemed to care very dearly
about something else.
I guess guarding the young lady wasn't
the only thing in your job description.
All I did was talk with her a few times
so she wouldn't be bored on her way.
I guess she couldn't help
but fall for me
because of this pretty face.
Then your face must be worth quite a bit.
Can I persuade you to let me go?
If my hands and feet were free,
I'm sure I would be even more persuasive.
If I cut off your tongue
for talking nonsense,
will the price for your face fall?
How can you say such a scary thing?
Darn.
Pull me up.
What are you doing? Can't you hear me?
How can I help you when I'm like this?
If my hands and feet were free,
I could help you better.
Throw me your sword.
Don't move. If you move,
you'll be sucked in faster.
Throw me your sword.
Where are you going?
Come back!
Grab it.
Quickly!
You're my hostage now.
The price on my head would be much higher
than the price
on a low-class warrior's face.
Actually, I'm not a low-class warrior.
The lady I was escorting
is the princess of Yeongju Castle.
And I'm the captain of her guards.
Are you looking at the moon
that has come up today?
Or the moon that came up
a thousand years ago?
They are all one and the same.
The flowers in the garden
have blossomed brightly.
You must have taken good care
of your guests so far
at the Guest House of the Moon.
I told you I changed
the name of this place.
It's not a guest house.
It's Hotel del Luna.
Stop calling me a landlady.
I'm the president.
They are the same thing.
I saw that the human
who had served you for a while left you.
Well, from death comes a new life.
I also died.
Why don't they take me?
You didn't die.
You are tied to the Moon Tree,
and the flow of life and death
has stopped for you. I told you that.
How long will you keep me tied up?
It's you who is not budging.
I shriveled up and died.
If you cut it up and burn it,
I will be on my way.
The leaves sprout,
and the flowers bloom and wither.
The time of life and death
will flow once again.
Don't you think you should leave something
pretty like this behind before you go?
I have nothing pretty and colorful
like that to leave behind.
Why don't you pick the bright flowers
and give them to pitiful spirits
when you see them off?
That child is still
filled to the brim...
I can't leave you like this forever.
Thank you for saving me earlier.
Consider yourself lucky.
I wouldn't have saved you
if you had been wearing other shoes.
They are so much better
than the tacky poop colored shoes.
You waited for me,
wearing the shoes that I chose for you.
I never waited for you.
Come on.
You sent me a text on the pretext
of that tiger, and waited for me.
I was just curious.
Of course you were curious.
Because you've been
thinking about me all along.
Did you
cast a spell on me or something?
Is that why I dreamed about you?
You dreamed about me?
Seeing ghosts like this
is already too much for me.
I don't want to see you in my dream.
Why? Did I eat you up
in your dream or something?
Forget it.
I don't think it was you in my dream.
If she were you,
she wouldn't have done that.
I forgive you.
You are an adult,
so you can have a dream like that.
What?
It's not that kind of dream!
Koo Chan-sung. I thought you were weak,
but you are actually very healthy.
Yes, I am very healthy.
Okay, you stay healthy.
If you faint like earlier again,
it will be too troublesome for me.
How did you bring me here?
Did you teleport me or something?
It was nothing.
Just like you brought a handcart
the other day,
I brought something to carry you here.
Get in there.
Let's move him.
Ms. Jang, I'm in him.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
Come on, Ms. Jang.
Come out of there.
Now that I'm in a human body,
may I go out and party a little?
Come out.
I really don't want
to get out of this body.
Ms. Jang. Please.
Come out!
That must have hurt.
Go.
Go!
All you need to know is
that I moved you here safely.
Is your neck all right?
Sure.
Why?
As long as you're fine.
Let's go.
Now that you're at my hotel,
I'll give you a tour.
Does this place really exist
in the real world?
Like I said last time,
our hotel is officially registered
at the Jung-gu District Office,
and we pay all the taxes too.
It does exist in the real world,
but its presence is very vague,
so the living do not notice it.
But it can sometimes be seen
when the weather is bad
or if the person has a good sixth sense.
I didn't know there was a hotel here.
You're right.
But it looks kind of scary. Let's just go.
But three to four times a year,
there are people who come in to check.
My goodness.
Our rooms are very expensive.
What do you do with the people
who insist on coming in?
I will check in.
We have a special room
we use for people like them.
Please go inside.
Sure.
A number of people
have checked into this room,
but no one has ever checked out.
What did you do to them?
Do you want to know?
Do you want to go in?
I still have many places to show you.
Okay. Then let's move on to the next one.
Why do you need sunglasses
in the middle of the night?
I don't come out here very often.
The sun is too bright.
It's nighttime in the middle of Seoul.
What is this place?
The inside of the hotel
isn't the real world.
The time and space here
are different from the world you live in.
Maps and watches
are absolutely useless here.
So this isn't the real world as well?
No.
Nothing in this hotel
exists in the real world.
No matter how pretty it is,
it's not in the real world.
You don't exist
in the real world too?
No,
I don't.
Then I wouldn't die if I fell from here?
Be careful. You're still alive.
If a living human falls down, he'll die
because the human body is too weak.
This was what it was like
to have a warm body
with a beating heart.
You need to be alive.
You have many things to do for me.
Stay by my side from now on,
Koo Chan-sung.
If I say no,
are you going to push me over?
It may be a surreal place,
but I demand realistic benefits.
And I am going to wear
whatever shoes I like.
You thought I might push you over?
Is that why you have changed your mind?
I've come this far.
What's the use of running away now?
To be honest, I got curious.
And it looks kind of fun too.
I want to know more
about you and this hotel.
Good.
I was going to let it slide
even if you tried to run away
a few more times.
Like I told you before,
you are my cup of tea.
It was her.
That woman.
May I get a refill on my coffee?
Yes.
-Oh, right. Honey.
-Yes?
Let's stop by the grocery store
on the way.
We'd have to take a detour.
Let's just go next time.
What happened?
-What should we do?
-Hello?
-What do we do? Is she dead?
-Is this 911?
Someone got hit by a car.
No, it wasn't me.
She suddenly fell from an overpass.
Yes, can you please come quickly?
Oh, right. The location?
We're currently at...
911 EMERGENCY SERVICE
That darn loser.
This is driving me crazy.
Whatever!
What's going on?
What happened to me?
Who are you?
This is mine.
We have a new human hotel manager.
I brought him from one of the best hotels
named by Forbes.
So he'll do a good job.
I know he graduated from Harvard,
but the work we do here
isn't based on knowledge.
He needs to have some guts.
But he seems very weak-hearted,
and that worries me.
How about we leave the position
vacant for a while
and hire someone from the two candidates
you had in mind?
There were two other candidates?
Of course.
The top candidate even knows
how to perform an exorcism, right?
What's the point?
He left to catch some useless ghost.
I ask you in the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Why are you here? What is your name?
-That's enough!
-Do not interfere!
I can't go there
before I catch this ghost.
You should leave.
I ask you in the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
What is your name?
Answer me!
-I'm more scared of him.
-Tell me your name!
I gave him the ability to see ghosts
only to see him leave to catch some ghost.
Won't he come back once he catches it?
That'll be impossible.
The ghost is really strong.
Park Il-do, that punk.
Who was the second candidate?
He was a fighter pilot.
She went all the way to the States
to find him.
But he eventually left in that thing.
In what thing?
I don't need the top two candidates.
Koo Chan-sung is here, so we're good.
His office is ready.
Mr. No knew he was going to leave
and had the office cleaned up beforehand.
He worked here for 30 years,
but he didn't leave a single trace behind.
Yes, he did.
That over there.
Mr. No took that photo.
So many humans worked here,
but they're all so vague to me.
How many people were here
including Mr. No?
Ms. Jang is the only one who knows that.
There's been no one special.
What's the point of counting?
What are you doing? Get back to work.
He was nothing more
than the 48th human to work here.
And Koo Chan-sung
will just be the 49th human to work here.
Nothing more.
MANAGER KOO CHAN-SUNG
I caved in way too easily.
That was so not like me.
Why did I do that?
This was what it was like
to have a warm body
with a beating heart.
I got too carried away.
Ms. Jang told us to say hello
to the new manager.
If you all work here,
that means you're all ghosts, right?
I died about 500 years ago.
She died 200 years ago.
And he died 70 years ago.
He's the youngest among us.
I was a scholar who studied very hard
when I was alive.
After a long period of studying,
I passed the National State Exam
with the highest score.
But I suddenly died
right before achieving my lifelong dream.
And while I was wandering around,
I found Man-wol Inn.
I've been here the longest.
You said you used to study.
Then what do you do here?
I used to be very bright
when it came to writing poems.
And now,
I'm a bartender.
So you're the bartender
who's in charge of the food and beverages.
I was the eldest daughter-in-law
of a prestigious family.
But I ended up getting murdered
by my own family.
While staying here,
I'll make sure I see the last member
of that loathful family die
with my own eyes
before I leave for the afterlife.
You must have a deep grudge.
I'm in charge of the rooms.
I see, ma'am.
I died during the Korean War.
This was called Man-wol Hostel
at that time.
It wasn't doing so well back then.
I'm waiting to go with my sister
who's still alive.
All of us have long stories to tell.
As for me--
We all came here
as guests at first. But now
we're working here, extending our stays.
Aside from Ms. Jang,
the three of us have been here
the longest.
Then did Ms. Jang come here
as a guest like you,
and ended up staying for a long term?
No.
Ms. Jang is the owner of Hotel del Luna.
Owner of what?
She's just tied down here
for a punishment from that crone.
She's being tied down?
There's a huge tree in our garden, but--
Do we have a garden?
I think we left the front desk and the bar
unattended for too long.
We better go.
I can't be lazy at work,
or I'll be sent to the other world.
I'll tell you my long story at the bar
while treating you to a martini.
I think you're done for the day.
You can go home now.
Where is the garden with the huge tree?
I didn't get to see it today.
She probably didn't show it to you
because it's unnecessary.
Is there some kind of tie between Ms. Jang
and that tree?
Mr. Koo.
How long do you want to work here?
As short as possible
since I didn't come here out of choice.
Then, it'd be best to keep
your curiosity to a minimum.
You must mean the more I know,
the longer I'll be tied to this place.
The rest of us will take care
of hosting the guests.
All you have to do is do the work
related to the humans.
I'll do that.
Hey, are you going to work already?
No, I just got off work.
Did you have a night shift?
No.
I have to quit the hotel I'm working at.
-Why?
-I'm going to work at a different one.
Which hotel?
Why quit the best hotel in Seoul?
The hotel I'll work at
has a private beach
and a soaring rooftop bar.
Is there such a hotel in Seoul?
I want to go there too.
You can't.
If you come, you'll be in Room 404.
What's in Room 404?
Is it a suite?
I'm so tired.
Hurray!
Yes.
This is the real world.
I have a place to stay,
and I have a friend.
I have lots of other hotels
asking me to come.
Don't get confused.
I'm finally calming down.
This really helps.
Something strange followed me
to the real world.
It's a moon.
It's to show that it's mine.
Man...
Wol.
This is how you write it.
MAN-WOL
I'm paying you back
for giving me good wine.
DEL LUNA
She was in my dream,
and now she's calling me.
It's getting me confused.
What took you so long to pick up?
What is it?
I have your first job for you.
I want to sell
the painting of Baekdu Mountain.
What?
The soul of the mythical creature
made the aura of this painting
even better.
I'll be able to get
twice its original price.
If we sell this,
what about the tiger inside?
The tiger has just left.
This is an empty painting.
The tiger has left?
The tiger lived in a zoo all his life.
He got sick of living in Baekdu Mountain
in a couple of days.
He went to the afterlife
after playing there for a few days.
I'm sure he'll be reborn in blessing.
Is this why you asked me
to get the painting?
To sell it?
Not because you cared about the tiger.
Of course I care about the tiger.
I even wore this for him.
Hey!
Make sure you get a good price for this.
Then as a reward,
I'll get you a tiger print suit like this.
No, thanks. Who would wear such a thing?
Why not? You love the poop color.
I even got the new car
in that color, just for you.
-A new car?
-Make sure to sell this by today.
I have to pick up the new car.
You bought a car?
The car I drove the other day
was also a new one.
You're right. I'm broke now
because I bought another new car.
Make sure you get a good price
for this painting.
At least twice its original price.
Let's go pick up my new car
I must've been crazy.
What more is there to know?
She's nothing but a money chaser.
Is he really gone? Is he not in there?
Roar.
Roar!
KIM YU-NA
That's not who you are.
You died right here!
Give my body back to me!
Yes, Director. Thank you
for introducing me to him.
Yes, I'm heading to the gallery right now.
I'll see you soon.
Give my body back to me!
Seems like Mr. Third Choice brought in
a very annoying guest.
She must have some issues.
She keeps saying she's not dead.
This isn't our first time
seeing the dead saying they're alive.
They always say that they're alive,
they can't die or ask why they died.
We hear that all the time.
Ms. Jang will handle it, right?
I told you to go sell a painting.
Why did you bring in an unwanted guest?
Are you a tout or what?
What did you say?
You said that you comfort souls here.
She seems like she has issues.
Why don't you come up with a solution?
You said you saw her other self
wandering around?
She said she was robbed of her body.
If it's true, we should get it back.
What you've brought is a soul
that came out of her living body.
So you're saying
that her body is out there without a soul?
You said she was robbed of her body.
Her body must be taken over
by another ghost.
What's wrong with Yu-na?
Yu-na bullied her the most.
Maybe she feels guilty
for everything she did to her.
She's acting like she actually feels bad.
Is this the girl's house?
Yes, Yu-na is the only child
of this household.
Their one and only daughter's body is
taken over by a ghost.
Of course we should get it back.
I think I already know the answer,
but are you going to force them pay you?
This isn't just a rich house.
That's the poop colored car
that I'm in love with.
It's very difficult to buy that car now,
but they already bought it before I did.
That means that they're filthy rich.
We need to find out
why this is happening, right?
It's because of a necklace.
It belongs to the dead friend
who took her body.
The ghost's deep grudge followed her,
stuck to the necklace.
Then it took over her body.
I thought they were friends.
Why would she do that?
Stop asking questions.
You said we need to get the body back.
Then that's all we need to do.
Go after her.
Hey!
Let me go!
I'm going to kill her body.
This isn't even your body.
Why are you doing this to a friend?
She's not a friend.
She's the one who killed me.
JEONG SU-JEONG
Give it back to me.
You live on social assistance,
and you waste your money
on something like this?
Do you have no conscience?
The money you get is for your meals.
This is what we call a waste of tax money.
Give it back.
Give it back!
Take it if you can.
-Here you go.
-Give it back to me!
Give it back!
Give it to me.
You little!
Let go of me!
I can't remember anything
after falling off the bridge.
When I came to consciousness,
I realized that I'm in her body...
with my necklace in her hand.
Are you here to give Yu-na her body back?
She killed me!
That's it.
Get me my body back with that now.
The grudge in here...
doesn't disappear that easily.
Just tell my parents.
They'll do anything for me.
Of course they should.
They're the ones who made you after all.
What is it that you wanted
to talk about our daughter?
Yu-na murdered someone.
Did you know
that one of Yu-na's classmates
committed suicide on an overpass?
That's not entirely true.
Your daughter killed her.
This necklace is the evidence.
What is it that you want?
I came to collect the price.
Do you think it's wrong of me
to kill Yu-na?
Let's find another way.
What way?
No matter what I do,
I can't come back to life.
I wanted to live!
Even when they called me a parasite,
I still wanted to live on.
Let go of me!
Please let go of me.
I can't let her return to this body
and live like nothing happened.
Please let go of me.
Wait, just a second.
I'll go get the necklace.
You should just live in this body, okay?
Where is the necklace?
We can't let her return to her body yet!
It'd be too unfair for that girl!
I already returned the necklace.
It's in the hands of her parents.
So this necklace belonged
to that dead girl, right?
That woman told us
this is the only evidence.
There are two ways
to pay for what she did.
One, take this necklace as evidence
to prove your daughter's wrongdoing
and punish her.
She should also apologize
to the dead girl's soul.
Two,
you buy my silence
and get rid of this necklace.
I'll pay as much as you want.
Please...
give it to us and keep it a secret.
So you made your decision.
You'll have to pay a big price.
Everything will go back to normal, right?
Of course.
Once that necklace is gone,
no one will know that you killed her.
No one will know, right?
I told you
that her grudge is very deep, didn't I?
Once that necklace is burned,
your chance to be forgiven for
what you did will be gone for good too.
It doesn't matter.
It does.
You won't ever be able to go back.
Pardon?
I'm saying that your soul
will really die without anyone realizing.
Darn it.
What's done is done, she's already dead.
Our Yu-na should continue
to have a good life.
Yes, she should.
None of this happened.
But what do you think...
that woman meant by the last comment?
Right.
You should know that the choice you made
will kill your daughter's soul.
No!
No! What do I do?
Mom, take it out! Mom! Please!
Please take it out, Mom!
I said, take it out! Take it out!
You should live in that body now.
Although you're parasitic on the body,
try your best to survive again.
DEATH
She has become a true parasite.
However,
she found herself a golden host.
I bet they'll spoil her not knowing
she's only their daughter's shell.
That young girl
will be tortured
while watching her own shell.
I feel bad for her.
She's only paying for what she did.
She's just tied down here
for a punishment from that crone.
Are you also paying for what you did?
I heard you're being punished.
I am.
Someone told me
that I'm arrogant and foolish.
Although I don't agree with it.
Right.
What was that? Did you just say, "Right"?
Are you mocking me?
No, I'm not.
Sometimes. No, very rarely,
I feel bad for you.
TEXT MESSAGE
What is this?
They cancelled the car I pre-ordered.
What kind of bullshit is this?
How is this possible?
Are they looking down on me?
They're dead meat.
Do you take me for a fool?
Forget it.
Give me the one in charge.
I said, the one in charge!
When Ms. Jang gets angry,
she drinks champagne in bulk.
Mr. No always prepared it for her.
I didn't know I'd be required
to serve Ms. Jang alcohol.
You're so unlucky.
You were the third choice,
so we didn't expect
you'd end up as our manager.
I was the third choice?
They told me not to tell you about that.
Are you saying I was the third choice
for the job?
-No.
-This means
there were two other candidates before me.
You're here now, so you're the winner.
It's a feat that I'm not happy about.
Here it is.
What is this?
This sign shows
that it belongs to Ms. Jang.
Anything with this means it's Ms. Jang's.
It's a moon.
It's to show that it's mine.
Come this way.
Ms. Choe.
Do you know what Ms. Jang was like
when she was alive?
What does it mean
that she's tied down for a punishment?
You're just a passer-by here.
Like these people who stopped by
over the many years,
just consider you're only visiting
for a moment,
and leave this place as soon as possible
as you wish.
MAN-WOL HOSTEL
Why are you enduring like that
for such a long time?
MAN-WOL INN
Is this that tree?
There are no leaves.
What are you doing here?
You didn't show me the garden,
so I came by myself.
Guests cannot come here.
So you don't need to see this.
Is this that tree?
The tree that my father touched.
The reason why I was sold here.
You're right.
You're paying the price too.
But it didn't have to be me.
I heard I was the third one on the list.
I really thought it had to be me.
You said I am your cup of tea,
so I made a huge decision to come here.
But I wasn't your first or second choice.
Yes, there were first and second
candidates before you.
Was I really the third choice?
Wasn't I the fourth,
or the fifth one by any chance?
Who said you were the third choice?
-There were more before me?
-You're
the zeroth choice.
The zeroth choice.
You're right. It has to be you
because you are my cup of tea.
Do you want some champagne?
You said you'll sell the Baekdu Mountain
painting for a good price. So have some.
Do you think the tiger saw
what he wanted to see in the painting?
He probably left without complaining
because he did.
He saw the past like a dream,
a time where he could never go back.
He got pretty lucky.
I'm sure you too have
things you miss in the past
that you can never go back to.
I think I saw that.
I told you that I saw you in a dream.
In a dream?
You were smiling
under a huge tree.
When someone said he'd build you a house,
you said mean things just as you do now,
but you were happy.
The moon shined above the wilderness
where you were drinking,
and it was filled
with sounds of instruments,
along with your laughter.
You were full of joy and happiness.
You weren't alone like you are now.
You had someone by your side.
The man who taught you
how to write your name, Man-wol.
Is he the person you miss the most
in your past?
You...
You really...
saw him.
You have been
waiting for that person
over this long period of time.
How do you see...
such things?
I don't know.
Why do I see you?
I'm scared
that I may have to pay the price for it.
Jang Man-wol.
Since I began to see you,
I've been thinking of you...
very much, awfully a lot.
Jang Man-wol, I'm saying...
you are devouring...
all my nights and dreams.
The old memories that shriveled up
crawled out again because of you.
So I need to check this for myself.
Chan-sung. Starting today,
you will deal with ghost guests.
There's someone she really wants to see.
Every single ghost has someone
that they want to see!
You said the owner was a maniac, right?
-Is that so?
-Leaves have sprouted from the dry tree...
I'm trying to take care of you.
I'm sorry.
Chan-sung, come to my hotel if you die.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu
I'm sure you too have
things you miss in the past
that you can never go back to.
I think I saw that.
I told you that I saw you in a dream.
In a dream?
You were smiling
under a huge tree.
When someone said he'd build you a house,
you said mean things just as you do now,
but you were happy.
The man who taught you
how to write your name, Man-wol.
Is he the person you miss the most
in your past?
How do you see...
such things?
Why do I see you?
I'm scared
that I may have to pay the price for it.
What's the sorrow you're still feeling?
Maybe
I'm here by your side...
to help you get over that deep sorrow?
You didn't die.
You are tied to the Moon Tree,
and the flow of life and death
has stopped for you. I told you that.
The leaves sprout,
and the flowers bloom and wither.
Your time will start flowing once again.
The tree just changed.
You're right.
You might turn out to be someone
a lot more special than I thought.
I can't just leave like this.
What about my dog, Sun-dol?
There's nothing you can do
when it comes to death.
Gosh, I can't go!
I can't go!
Sun-dol, bark.
You need to bark to live.
If you don't, you'll die.
My goodness, come on.
Bark! You need to bark!
It's been a week,
and he still won't budge.
It's because he still has something
he's holding onto.
At times like this, it's not
a bad idea to help him out a little.
Sun-dol, you need to leave.
Go outside! Hurry up and go!
Will you please go outside?
Just leave him.
He won't wander for too long.
He'll find his way to Man-wol Inn.
It's called Hotel del Luna now,
not Man-wol Inn.
Yes, I forgot.
Man-wol Inn, Man-wol Hostel,
and then Hotel del Luna.
The name of that place
changes so frequently,
but the owner of the place
hasn't changed at all.
She hasn't changed for over 1,000 years.
She has no hope.
That's why I sent someone there.
Are you going to change the owner?
Man-wol's very stubborn,
so I just sent her some help.
Why did the tree change?
Why do you think? It's because of you.
It's because of me?
The old memories that shriveled up
crawled out again because of you.
What did I do?
All I did was tell you
about the dream I had of you.
I know seeing ghosts is part of my job,
but dreaming is not.
I don't want to be treated unfairly
for something I never even asked for.
You're going to get treated unfairly
because you've already provoked me.
The tree turned ugly because of you.
I get that you're twisted,
but don't distort the truth.
The tree looks alive and healthy.
That is
the problem.
You just saved something
that shouldn't have been saved.
Seeing that you're so angry,
I guess my dream
really was about your past.
Are you embarrassed that I saw your past?
Yes.
I'm extremely embarrassed right now.
So I need to check this for myself.
What are you doing?
This is wrong.
Stay still.
Stop it.
Chan-sung, let's sleep.
Jang Man-won.
You need to sleep
in order to have that dream.
I need to check for myself
if you really saw me in a dream
or if you're deceiving me
using all the rumors
you heard in this hotel.
Chan-sung, go to sleep.
I can't fall asleep like this.
And I can't guarantee
that I'll have that dream again
even if I do fall asleep.
Then sleep next to me
until you do have that dream.
I don't want to sleep next to you.
Be quiet and go to sleep
while I'm being nice.
Fine. I'll sleep.
You can sleep next to me
or watch me sleep.
Do as you want.
I'm going to kill you
if it turns out to be a lie.
You just want it to be a lie
because you don't like
that I saw your past.
I'm not going to tell you
what I see in my dreams
since you hate it so much.
You can kill me or let me live.
Do as you want.
Forget it. I'm not sleeping next to you.
Do the memories that I revived
pain you that much?
Because you can't stop thinking about him?
Shut your mouth unless you want
to turn all green like the tree.
Who is that man?
Why do you ask?
You think it might be you?
Yes, that thought did occur to me.
What I saw could be a memory
from my past life that I don't remember.
There's no way you're him.
Why?
You've been on my mind
ever since I had that dream.
You and I might go back a long way.
You're not him.
I feel nothing.
If you were him,
I definitely wouldn't feel this way.
That's a huge relief.
I kept wondering, "What if I'm the man
she liked in the past?"
It's been bothering me a lot.
You didn't have feelings for him?
You seemed to like him. A lot.
A lot.
Chan-sung.
If you keep spewing useless nonsense,
you'll get treated more unfairly.
More unfairly? How?
What? Are you not going to pay me?
I signed the contract though!
Chan-sung!
Starting today,
you'll deal with ghost guests.
How long has it been since--
I guess you were lost for some time.
I'll help you with your check-in.
I'll make sure you can use
our beauty and hair services first.
This way, please. Let's take the elevator.
What's going on? Is Ms. Jang still angry
even after drinking a case of champagne?
I must've upset her somehow.
I think she's livid now.
Well, what kind of sin
did Ms. Jang commit in the past?
Does it have something to do
with a love affair?
I'm not sure.
Have you heard anything about a man
she's perhaps waiting for?
No, nothing.
Really?
Is she not waiting for him?
Mr. Koo.
Are you concerned
about what she's thinking?
No, not at all.
She's not waiting
for the first and second choices.
Who cares if you were the third one?
You're here now.
Mr. Ji.
I don't care at all
about what Ms. Jang thinks.
Besides, I wasn't the third choice.
I was the zeroth choice.
I beat everyone else.
The zeroth choice? Sure.
-I'm serious.
-Okay, you were the zeroth choice.
It's all useless though.
She said she felt nothing.
What's this spooky feeling?
I think quite a number of guests
are coming.
Will you be all right?
No, I won't.
When our guests first arrive,
they're often broken and ripped.
Sometimes,
they have something tagging along.
But all the guests here are groomed,
so you'll be fine.
I'm now experienced enough
to handle this much.
Can I get a refill on my coffee?
We've run out of coffee beans.
Please give us a moment.
We'll bring it to your table.
How do you procure
the things that the guests
eat and drink here?
You can't get things delivered
from a store.
We get them from the afterlife.
When we treat our guests well
and help them go to the afterlife,
we get compensated for our work.
You mean, the ghosts pay you?
They leave good energy behind.
And that energy makes
the flowers in our garden bloom.
The less regrets they take with them,
the more beautiful the flowers are.
When our garden is filled with flowers,
Mago takes them
and sends us the supplies
that we need in return.
Then why does Ms. Jang
need to earn money through the ghosts?
It's all for her lavish lifestyle.
She spends all the money
on her expensive champagnes,
clothes, jewelry, and cars.
How could someone who's being punished
have such an attitude?
You said she's being punished.
Someone told me
that I'm arrogant and foolish.
Although I don't agree with it.
I saw you in a dream.
The leaves sprout,
and the flowers bloom and wither.
The time of life and death
will flow once again.
That wicked old hag is
pulling a silly trick on me.
The man who taught you
how to write your name, Man-wol.
Is he the person you miss the most
in your past?
Goodness.
A slave ran away!
Someone must've helped her. Find them.
Who ran away?
She's not here. Search outside.
I heard the market where slaves
from Goguryeo are traded, was attacked.
I had a feeling it might be you guys,
so I came to check.
Thank goodness I'm nimble.
I almost got killed by your dagger.
No, I saved you because I'm nimble.
I'm much obliged,
but what will you do about this?
My face is very precious.
How will you pay for this?
Too bad.
The young lady at the Yeongju Castle
adores your face.
How will you seduce her from now on?
Do you think she only adores my face?
Don't be such a baby.
Let go. Let go of me.
I said, let go!
Shut it! Get him over here at once.
What are you waiting for?
Get up!
You bastards, let go!
Let go.
Yeon-u.
Let go. Yeon-u. It's Yeon-u.
Shut your mouth!
If you get out, you'll get caught too.
I give you my word.
I'll be sure to save him
and bring him to you.
I promise.
Yeon-u.
Easy.
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
You have been waiting for that person
over this long period of time.
It is...
too green and too gaudy.
It looks ridiculous.
Yeon-u.
One of them was Yeon-u.
He was in Man-wol's gang.
Are you selling those flowers?
How much is it? I'd like to buy one.
No, that's fine.
I already gave yours.
Your dad almost died,
trying to pluck a flower for you.
Because of that incident, he stopped
stealing and lived a diligent life.
And he also raised a great son like you.
Flowers! Flowers are the best present
for birthdays.
Flowers.
Weren't you the lady...
So how is it? How's working at the hotel?
Did you set this up?
All I did was open a path.
Are you telling me that it wasn't
a coincidence he went to the hotel?
I planted a tree, you know.
Gosh, that tree has been growing
spiky branches
and unwelcoming to the others.
I want you to take good care of the tree.
Okay? If you have a hard time
looking after the tree,
you can come find me.
TO THE SAMDO RIVER
TO HEAVEN
Excuse me.
Hold on.
Sir.
Sun-dol, you brat.
You shouldn't be here.
I can't take you with me. Okay?
You... Goodness.
Where I'm headed is not a place for you.
He died all alone.
It looks like it's been a few days.
The door was open.
Why didn't the dog come out?
That's strange.
You shouldn't follow me there.
My goodness, you poor thing. Goodness.
Okay. Let's go there together, okay?
We'll go together.
Mago plucks the flowers
and hands them out to the people
who are headed to their afterlife.
And the souls who leave
with Mago's farewells
go to a good place.
That lady earlier...
is Mago?
PHARMACY
11-28 YAKJAE-GOLMOKGIL, GYEONGDONG MARKET
What's that?
Chan-sung, come on out!
Chan-sung!
Chan-sung, here.
I bought the most amazing bread.
Someone saw a ghost
at a bakery I regularly go to.
A ghost kneaded the dough
for this bread, so I waited to buy it.
Sanchez, don't say stuff like that.
I don't want to hear about ghosts
even at my own home.
Hey, what if the ghost who made this
followed me home?
Why are you here?
Why are you here again?
Chan-sung, what are you doing?
You're scaring me.
There's no ghost here. It's just bread.
Did you follow him here?
Did you follow the bread?
Chan-sung, I apologize for my silly story.
Let's just eat the bread. Okay?
I'm good. You eat it.
I think I have to go back to work now.
Hey. How can I eat this bread
after what you said just now?
Seems like Mr. Third Choice
brought back a guest who went out.
She went out of here,
went to a bakery, and made bread.
She shouldn't have done
something like that.
She's the one that was supposed
to leave in a limousine today, right?
Yes, Mr. Koo went to Ms. Jang
to get her signature
for postponing the limousine reservation.
Did she want to have bread
before leaving this world?
She can't even eat bread
from this world anyway.
She should've called for room service.
Why did she go to a bakery?
Hyeon-jung, can't you pay better attention
to the guests coming and leaving?
Do you want to get on the bus
to the afterlife?
I had a big group of guests yesterday,
so I was swamped.
Do your job right.
That was mean.
Wasn't it? How can she tell me
to take the bus?
Yes, that was a harsh thing to say.
Why is she so on edge like that?
Oh, it will be the 25th soon.
It's that day already.
We'll pass through it safely, won't we?
We have to.
If what happened 42 years ago
happens again,
Ms. Choe will be
dragged to the afterlife for sure.
A ghost can't just go around this world
stirring up trouble.
She didn't do anything serious,
so tell her to go
to the other world as planned.
I want to change that reservation.
Please sign here.
RESERVATION CHANGE
There's someone she really wants to see.
Every single ghost has someone
that they want to see!
She wants to see that person
because she never saw him
when she was alive.
She was blind when she was alive.
How can she want to see the person
when she has never seen him?
She doesn't even know the name.
Why is she looking for someone
she doesn't even know?
Forget it and go.
Stop annoying me.
She says her hands remember.
If she holds the hands,
she can feel who it is.
That's some nonsense a ghost is spewing.
Go away!
Is what you said also nonsense then?
You said you can tell by your feelings.
That I'm definitely not that man.
Then you don't know either.
You are...
definitely not him.
I'm right then, so you should sign this.
Darn.
JANG MAN-WOL
I'll find her that person
and then send her off.
She is the first guest I brought,
so I want to send her off nicely.
Don't try to get money off her.
She doesn't have any.
Why are you doing something
that won't get you money?
You're being used by that ghost.
You're so weakhearted.
Such an easy target for ghosts.
You're right.
If I'd been tougher and held out,
I wouldn't have ended up here.
I regret that I'm such a weak human being
that you like so much.
-Are you being sarcastic?
-I'm saying it's my fate.
I don't regret bringing you in
and complicating your life.
Do you really think you did that?
They say, "You complicate your own life."
Maybe it wasn't you who dragged me here.
Maybe I was the one who pushed myself
into the place I felt drawn to.
Drink this.
You should drink as much water as alcohol,
so you won't feel dry.
I'll bring some bread when I come back.
The place we're visiting
is a famous bakery.
It's the place that comedian
Kim Jun-hyun visited.
Try the Eat At Once game.
Why are you being nice?
You're making me nervous.
Are you giving me poison nicely?
I'm trying to take care of you.
If I give you water and bread,
who knows?
Leaves have sprouted from the dry tree.
Maybe flowers might bloom.
Don't.
Do you think I'm some seedling
that sprouts when you give it water?
I'm an old tree that's been dry
for over a thousand years.
The tree has leaves now.
I think it will be worthwhile.
-Stop being weird!
-Am I bothering you?
You said you didn't feel anything.
I guess that's not true.
That stupid...
Hey, Chan-sung.
Don't do this. Don't come here anymore.
Why? I have work to do.
You don't have to come here.
I'll let you go.
I have nowhere to go now.
Because you made me
leave the last hotel like that,
they hate me. I can't go back there.
There are other hotels on the Forbes list.
They liked me when they didn't know
I can see ghosts.
Not anymore.
And you have no one else except for me.
You were the third choice.
There are two other candidates,
and they're better.
Oh, those two.
They're too tough and strong for this job.
You need an easy target for ghosts
like me.
Someone who can resolve their grudges.
Here, I'm the zeroth pick.
Chan-sung.
If you keep doing this,
I really won't like you.
Having you like me
because I'm not bothering you.
Having you not like me
because I'm bothering you.
I prefer the latter.
I'll accompany the guest outside.
He will keep on provoking me?
He thinks I'm a joke
because the tree has leaves now.
What kind of bread are you looking for?
The bread that you're baking now
smells so nice.
It's chestnut bread.
It's warm, right?
And fluffy.
I just baked it.
Every time I went there,
he held my hand warmly.
My heart was thumping so hard,
I was afraid he'd know how I felt.
So I never got to talk to him properly.
You don't know his face or his name.
But you will know for sure
when you hold his hand, right?
If you approach him with those hands,
you will only make him scared
and fail to hold him.
Shall I tell them the situation
and find out?
Okay, I will lend my body to you.
Wow, the bread here is the best.
Thank you.
You made the bread with this hand.
It's a great hand.
It's not him.
Can you recommend a cake?
What about this strawberry cake?
The chocolate cake looks good too.
There's cheesecake too.
They're all delicious.
There's only one left, so it must be him.
Can I save points here?
Yes, do you have our membership card?
I didn't bring it.
Tell me your phone number.
Zero, one, zero...
What's your problem?
-This guy has been acting strange.
-Who are you?
Well, I...
Chan-sung.
What are you doing?
Sanchez.
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
I'm sorry.
Take care.
What did you tell them?
I told them you're not a weirdo
and said sorry.
They said you should
never come here again.
I'm sorry, Sanchez.
Why did you do that?
I thought you went to the hotel.
Why are you here?
A guest asked me
to look for someone there.
Jeez.
You could've just asked for the name
instead of kneading the hands
of all the employees.
I had my reasons.
You should've asked me for help.
I'm a regular customer here.
Do you remember
every employee who worked here?
Of course I do.
Let go.
Am I the only one who sees
these green things?
Leaves have sprouted
on the tree.
It's so beautiful. Let's take a photo.
We shouldn't be marveling but lamenting.
It's a sign
that the hotel will face hardship.
Why is that?
Man-wol is being punished
by being tied to this tree.
Such changes to the tree must mean
that her punishment is coming to an end.
What's so wrong with that?
Think about what will happen
after she leaves.
We're still here thanks to her,
so what will happen to us?
We'll have to take
the bus to the afterlife.
No way.
I can't leave yet.
Same here.
Why did this suddenly happen?
What changed?
We have a new manager.
I guess Mr. Third Choice has something
to do with this.
The person you're looking for is
working here now.
Hello, here's the coffee you ordered.
That's him.
It tastes better
if you stir thoroughly. Enjoy.
Thank you.
Would you like to hold his hand?
Excuse me.
Yes?
Hello, I was a regular customer
of the bakery you worked at.
Oh, I see.
I hope you come by here often too.
It's warm, right?
And fluffy.
I just baked it.
Spend some time here
and come back to the hotel.
Do you feel proud?
It was worth it.
Is this a new car?
Yes, isn't it sweet?
The tacky poop color is not fit for a car.
Bright color like this is better.
So you went ahead and bought one?
No, but I call dibs.
Count me out
if you're off to buy one right now.
I'd rather get some sleep.
Sure, let's go sleep.
Sorry?
Let's sleep together.
I'm going to see how you dream this time.
As my boss, saying you'd like to
sleep with me is inappropriate.
I'll let it slide just this once.
Would you rather get a bite to eat?
I never said I wouldn't sleep.
I'm just not sleeping with you.
That's not what I said.
I only asked you out for a meal.
Do you realize that
you're not making any sense?
You said you'd look after me.
Seeing that I sleep and eat well is
how you do it.
Chan-sung.
Look after me.
What would you like to eat?
This place is quite famous
on social media.
I wanted to try the food.
You knew, right?
You knew that this is my friend's place.
Will you believe me if I say no?
Why ask when you're not going to?
What's good here?
Why ask when you won't even order
what I recommend?
You know me well.
I'll have this.
You'll have this. I want to try them both.
Chan-sung!
Sanchez is my roommate.
He gets scared easily,
so don't mention anything about ghosts.
You must've lied to Sanchez
about where you work.
-Hi, Sanchez.
-Hey.
Did you find the man you were looking for?
Yes, thanks to you.
So this is my colleague.
She must be a hotelier too.
That's so cool.
We'll order number 2 and number 15.
Sure thing. Let's see.
It's a hard place to work at, isn't it?
Chan-sung's been stressed out
ever since he started to work there.
You said the owner was a maniac, right?
That lady...
What was her name again?
-Jang Man-wol.
-Yes, Jang Man-wol.
I remember because the name is so weird.
Anyway, from what I hear,
employees must badmouth their bosses
to relieve stress at work.
So when I serve the pizza,
think of it as that owner's head.
And enjoy your meal
while ripping her apart.
Rip, bite, and chew, all right?
It'll take more than one pizza
to vent all your anger.
Order another one.
I never called you a maniac.
I only said you were hard to reason with.
What's so wrong about it?
Don't we all get a little crazy sometimes?
Anyway, this reminds me
of the loaf of bread
you promised to get me.
How did it go at the bakery?
It all went well.
Her hands guided her to the right place.
Is that so?
But the memories
that ghosts have can get...
all mixed up sometimes.
Floating around so for long
makes them forget what's important.
Sometimes, they only remember
what they want to remember.
You said
that she only remembered his hands.
That's a beautiful memory.
Still, it's missing something.
She lived a decently long life,
but his hand is
the only thing she desperately remembers
just because he kindly picked up
bread for her?
What are you getting at?
The most important memories for a ghost
are mostly the same.
The memories of when they died.
Help me.
Chan-sung.
Come to my hotel if you die.
Darn it. What's your problem?
If you do this,
you'll turn to ashes and disappear.
Don't leave in vain like that.
I'll make sure he gets punished
for what he did.
I promise!
You found the guy who committed
a hit-and-run six months ago?
So you caught him by yourself
and brought him here?
Yes, he hit a blind woman
who was crossing the street
with his motorcycle and ran away,
leaving her for dead.
Oh, really?
Gosh, you're incredible.
"He hit a blind woman
who was crossing the street..."
You're the first guest
I'm sending off at this hotel.
I heard you go to a nice place
if you receive that flower.
Thank you.
The memory I had of his hand
was a horrible one.
But I was a fool to remember it
as a warm and heart-fluttering memory.
That's because you were probably
the kind of person
who always tried to remember
happy memories
regardless of how small they were
over terrible hardships you had.
SAMDO RIVER
Sir.
Would you like some more coffee?
Isn't this place huge?
There's a sandy beach if you go outside.
Your son will love it.
Thank you.
Let's go have fun in the water.
Come on.
Do you want me to carry you?
There we go.
The father and son came together
due to a car accident.
Gi-ung, stop!
Gi-ung, no!
He still hasn't come to his senses
even after what he saw.
Ms. Jang.
We saw the tree in the garden.
Everyone's feeling very nervous.
The tree's been dead for over 1,000 years.
Why did it suddenly come back to life?
Mago told me
that someone will come and help me leave.
I guess that person's here.
Is that person Mr. Koo?
Yes.
What did Mr. Koo say?
He told me that he'll take care of me
and that he'll try to make flowers
bloom along with the leaves.
I guess I'll be gone
once the flowers fall.
Then what about us?
What's going to happen to us?
How would I know?
That's up to you.
We can give up all together
and move onto the afterlife.
Or you can roam around
this world as vengeful ghosts
and turn into ashes.
Suit yourself.
We must stay at the hotel a little longer.
And you can't leave just yet either.
We should let go of Mr. Koo.
Besides, he was our third choice,
and we have the fourth candidate ready.
Hey. Isn't that too harsh?
Don't distract me and go away.
I'm sorry.
We'll go away.
What's gotten into her?
What's her deal?
Let's just go.
She's unbelievable.
A ghost has taken up her body.
And she's bold too. She's the perfect fit.
Right. We have another candidate.
I helped her steal the body,
so I can definitely use that against her.
Besides, her family is loaded too.
Let's let go of Mr. Koo.
He won't leave.
I told him to leave, but he said no.
Koo Chan-sung can see ghosts now.
And he's settling in too.
Even if I kick him out
with his eyes carved out,
he'll see ghosts and the hotel.
Mago will be able to take away
his ability to see the ghosts.
You think that old hag will do me a favor?
She's the one who sent him to me.
We can't kill a human,
but if we let him be,
we'll have to get on the bus.
There's a way to fix this
without killing him.
The guest...
who's staying in Room 13.
The guest in Room 13...
The guest in Room 13 hates
even the sound of a human's breath.
If a human sees the guest in Room 13,
the human will go crazy.
Are you suggesting
that we make him go mad?
Yes.
If he goes crazy
and roams around like a madman,
he won't be able to come here
even though he sees ghosts.
This world would isolate such people
without our involvement.
Mental institution.
Ms. Jang, do you approve of this?
Where is Koo Chan-sung now?
This punk keeps making my garden
look more and more hideous.
No one told you to chase around a ghost
without getting any sleep.
You don't have much time left
as a sane man.
It looks like you're wasting
your precious time sleeping.
What a shame.
But it's all your fault.
You were really my cup of tea,
but I hate that you can look into me.
Why are you smiling?
Did you come here,
so we could sleep together?
Are you happy
now that you watched me sleep?
You saw me in your dream again?
Do you want to know?
Sit down. I'll tell you
what you were like in my dream.
This is what I hate.
I should be saying that I'll rip
your mouth open if you don't shut up.
But for a second, I thought about
sitting down there. And I really hate it.
You haven't budged an inch
for over 1,000 years.
A second means a lot.
Yes, this change means a lot to me,
and you'll have to pay for it.
You agreed that you're the one
who complicated your own life.
Whatever happens to you,
it's all your fault.
If something happens to me,
I'm sure you'll protect me.
You said you were going to protect me
as I'm a weak human.
You were the one
who stopped the motorcycle.
No, I didn't. I couldn't care less.
I know that it was you.
I jumped in because I trusted you.
I said, it wasn't me.
I trust that you will protect me.
So please protect me
if something happens to me.
I will stay right next to you.
I'm going to kick you out.
Did it come from the dream?
That second of Man-wol?
Mr. Koo.
I need your help with a guest.
Okay. Which room is the guest in?
It's Room 13.
She's a long-term stay guest.
Burn this incense stick in Room 13.
Okay, I'll do that.
The guest is very picky.
I'm sorry for troubling you.
I'm getting used to ghost guests now.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm giving up
on my virtue as a scholar.
I'm ashamed.
I liked him. He was like a good friend.
Mr. Koo is
on his way to Room 13 now.
Where is the guest?
Chan-sung!
Don't look.
Don't let her hear your breathing.
But I hear--
Don't listen to it.
What's the matter?
Chan-sung isn't going anywhere.
I'm keeping him by my side.
You sent me to that room
on purpose, didn't you?
I lost one of the earrings.
You'll go bankrupt at this rate.
Be kind and cut down on your spending.
She's being forced into a marriage.
You think this is the front desk?
Ma'am, you can't do this to our employee.
-I am okay with it.
-Gosh.
Please take it.
You'll actually marry her?
Jang Man-wol...
Do you love me too?
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu