Hotel Del Luna Blu-ray Disc 4
Subtitle re-timing by Jharel
Boss, what are you doing out here?
This place has the nicest view
of the moon.
Princess Song-hwa is here to see you.
Why are you leaving?
Didn't you come to the castle to see me?
No.
I came to steal.
A clumsy man is keeping guard,
so I thought it'd be
a great night to steal.
I thought I managed to run into someone
I missed.
But I guess I just ran into a thief.
What did you steal?
This belongs to someone I care for.
I guess you came to see me yourself
because I didn't show up
while you were drinking.
Forget it.
It seemed like you were busy
seducing that lady.
You should get going.
You saw that?
But did it really seem like
I was the one seducing her?
Clearly, she was the one seducing me.
You're one lucky guy.
You even get drinks from someone so noble.
I like this better.
And it's more my style.
I'm going to...
confiscate this.
It seems like you already stole
what you were here for.
So you should go back.
The guards are very alert
due to the rebel forces,
so it's very dangerous.
I'll pay for the bottle
the next time we meet.
At this rate, the tree will soon
be covered with flowers.
Chan-sung will put on airs again
when he sees this.
He's trying to scare me.
Are you enjoying this? I'm hot, aren't I?
Are you enjoying this?
Out of the way!
Hey, what was that guy doing
in the ladies' room?
I don't know. He must be a pervert.
The ladies' room?
I definitely got the chills.
What was it?
Is this possessed or something?
You're a ghost who's living
inside a human's body, aren't you?
Was it your doing?
You should be in the afterlife.
This is the punishment
for corrupting the order of this world.
You must vanish immediately.
It wasn't her doing.
She is just a soul
Man-wol has decided to keep alive.
She is not an evil ghost
that has harmed humans.
Why has a lowly ghost taken over a body
and been going around like this?
The owner of the body
died due to the foolish choice
of her parents.
Man-wol let her soul live
in an empty body.
Strictly speaking,
she has not harmed any human.
Man-wol has done a peculiar thing again.
Hurry up and leave here.
A human was harmed here just now.
It's a ghost I have been looking for.
It has harmed a human,
so it is an evil ghost.
Get rid of it as soon as you catch it.
Another Mago has ordered me
to find it and put it back
where it used to be.
Hotel del Luna again?
It was a guest there.
You should capture all of the ghosts
wandering around
and take them to the other world instantly
instead of letting them have a rest.
Is the path to the other world
an expressway?
Why do they need a rest area?
Why did she have to create such a thing
and entrust it to an evil ghost
like Jang Man-wol?
Strictly speaking,
she is not an evil ghost.
Also,
she will also go to the other world soon.
So I was told.
I heard the one who will guide her
to the other world
has been sent there.
They want to send
Man-wol to the other world that easily?
Her soul can't go
to the other world so easily.
Her ill-fated relationship
of this life will be repeated.
She will hurt humans again,
and she will be sent to the afterlife
as an evil ghost.
I'm glad you're leaving here
after a good rest.
If you found your wife who died with you,
you could have departed together.
I hope you will reunite with her
in the afterlife.
The platform for the afterlife is
that way. I'll take you there.
Honey?
Honey.
What are you doing here?
I'm here because I'm dead.
Do you know how much I looked for you
as soon as I died?
You're dead too?
I thought you were saved.
Who is this guy?
Are you having an affair
with that little brat as soon as you died?
Be careful what you say!
He died young.
He's actually three years older than you!
Sweetheart.
-"Sweetheart"?
-What?
Who are you?
Don't you dare touch him!
He is my first love!
Are you crazy?
You can't do this here, sir.
Yes, I'm crazy.
Don't you dare touch him,
and just go your way.
I'm going to kill you!
She's already dead.
You don't need to kill her.
Let me go. I will kill her!
Mr. Koo!
I'll kill you.
-Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
Just leave him be.
This hotel provides all the services
our guests desire.
You are already dead.
It is not difficult for you to die again.
Kill her as much as you want
until you feel better.
Now...
What do you want to kill her with?
Pick one.
Sir, slash and chop her with this.
Ma'am, you can't just stand still.
Chop him properly.
This way please.
Now, there will be a lot of blood
and flesh everywhere.
Everyone take a step back.
You are all dead.
But you can inflict deadly pain
on the other person's soul.
Please hack up the time you lived
together to your heart's content.
Slash it, tear it,
and destroy it.
We will do our best to help you
vent out your grudges.
What are you doing? When a couple fights,
you should try to stop them
and persuade them to live happily.
What do you think you're doing?
How can you live happily?
You are already dead.
You don't even have one second to live.
Just vent out your grudges.
Whether you hack each other,
or bathe in blood,
enjoy to your hearts' content. Bye.
-That's enough.
-Stop fighting.
Stop now.
You shouldn't fight.
That's good.
They were lovebirds
when they were alive. Such a pity.
Her first love, who she truly loved, died.
She married some random guy
out of despair.
An untimely encounter took place
in front of the door to the afterlife.
Remember the last time
when the guests who had debt problems
met here and caused a great commotion?
They have no need for money after death.
But they fought like cats and dogs.
Whether it's big or small,
they had their grudges.
Fighting can be a way
of resolving grudges.
Here is patbingsu.
I'll be going to resolve
the wife's grudges.
She wants to have the patbingsu
that she had with her first love
on their first date.
What is it?
They're soju and roasted seaweed
you enjoyed when you were alive.
I heard from your wife
that she always prepared them for you.
She's so mean.
It's a mean question to ask
in this situation,
but don't you have anyone else
in your heart?
I don't.
For me, my wife was my first love.
It feels so unfair that I'm going to die.
You are already dead.
I'm glad the guests have calmed down.
You were hit, weren't you?
You have to be careful of angry ghosts.
It didn't hurt that much.
That's not important.
You were hit by an evil grudge.
-An evil grudge?
-The grudge of that guest
has hit you.
It could have been dangerous.
But Ms. Jang was watching it,
so you'll be fine.
Ms. Jang?
She probably came because it was too loud.
Whether our guests fight
or have a bloody battle,
she hardly ever cares about it.
But she stepped up today.
I think she did that because she was
worried you'd be hit again.
Well...
I don't usually get beaten up by others.
Since you were hit by a ghost,
you should sprinkle some salt
to ward off evil influence.
Like this.
She told me she would protect me.
She really did protect me.
But it's a little...
embarrassing.
It's the sea.
The sea looks really beautiful.
I'm a little sad.
Because the sea
looks more beautiful now...
than it did earlier.
Jang Man-wol.
I came to check something.
If you're going to nag, do it later.
I'm doing my nails now,
and it's going great.
If these get ruined, I'll kill you.
Goodness.
I can't believe you got beaten up
by a ghost like a loser.
That's the color of the blue sea.
Yes, they're pretty, aren't they?
They are. Very sadly.
The reason you were sad on the beach...
was this?
Because there was no yacht?
Goodness, it got here?
It was sent from Norway,
so I thought it would take a while.
But it got here quickly. Give it to me.
Are you going to buy that?
I sold all of my cars.
I could use a yacht.
You don't have any place to go
on that yacht.
Of course, I have places to go.
What's that thing called?
Right, The Fishermen and the City.
They go around the country on a boat
catching fish.
Don't worry.
I have many places to go on a yacht.
What about the money? Can you afford it?
That's the problem.
That painting of the tiger.
Is no one willing to buy that?
Try to sell it for a quarter of the price.
You can't get a yacht.
If you want to go fishing,
I'll take you
to a fishing hole in Wolmi Island.
We can get there by car.
You sold all of my cars.
We have two left.
What? You said I still have three.
Right, three of them. I got confused.
Gosh, you scared me.
I'm so relieved.
That's a relief, right?
Then let's drive to Wolmi Island.
I'll find a great restaurant too.
I will
cancel this request myself.
Everything got ruined
in the perfect timing.
The color blue and Wolmi Island
don't really go well together.
Wolmi Island is famous for the ride,
Ghost Pang Pang.
I'll switch to a color
that stands out a bit more.
Wolmi Island
TO MS. JANG MAN-WOL, I LOVE YOU
He told me to sprinkle salt,
so seasoned salt should be fine, right?
Chan-sung, what are you doing?
Hey.
You didn't go to work yet?
I'm about to leave. What's that?
Oh, salt.
What are you doing with that?
Did something awful happen?
I heard it's great to sprinkle salt
to prevent evil influence.
"Evil influence"?
You aren't talking about Mi-ra, are you?
Did Mi-ra steal your credit card again?
Did she borrow money under your name?
Yes, Mi-ra did that to me long ago.
I just remembered how angry I was.
Hey, forget the seasoned salt.
There's Himalayan pink salt.
Do you want it?
I don't need to use
such good salt for this.
Seasoned salt should be enough.
Give it to me.
I'll cover every single inch.
Okay.
Hey, Sanchez.
You're seasoning me a bit too much.
You aren't making kimchi right now.
It's stuck. It won't come out.
Really?
Will Man-wol buy the yacht?
You set her up
with the yacht company in Norway?
I uploaded a picture of my yacht
on my social media.
She saw that and asked me
where I got it, so I told her.
She was going to get
something that expensive?
She's the owner of your hotel.
She can afford that much.
I was going to let her join
our yacht club too.
Your yacht club?
The wealthy people's social club?
It's going to help her
with her business too.
She's not dating anyone, is she?
Why do you ask?
I want to set her up
with one of our members.
If it's a yacht club,
you should go ride on a yacht.
Why are you setting people up?
People meet partners for their businesses
and their lives in such clubs.
That's where I met Veronica.
What do you think about him?
Don't you think he's a good match for her?
He's way too thin.
He is?
Jang Man-wol likes
someone like Kim Jun-hyun.
A type like Kim Jun-hyun.
People who can eat five dumplings
in one bite.
Really? In that case,
what about him? He's okay, right?
He looks way too young.
He's well over 30.
Jang Man-wol is older than you think.
No matter what you expect,
she's older than that.
He's way too young.
In that case, who could be the best?
Sanchez, she has no money to buy a yacht.
She doesn't qualify
to be a part of the club.
So don't set her up with any of them.
Don't do it.
In that case, she can join
our tennis club or golf club
-instead of the yacht club, or--
-Sanchez.
Since when were you into sports?
You're such a sportsman.
But she isn't interested in sports.
Leave her alone.
Where's the Himalayan pink salt?
Over there.
He must like her.
Goodness, he made a mess here.
Gosh, this is sweet. Hey, this is sugar.
Did you sprinkle sugar on yourself?
Man, you'll get cockroaches in here.
This is the punishment
for corrupting the order of this world.
You must vanish immediately.
She has grown really weak.
I'm going to take over her body.
Hey. Hey!
No! Stop!
No!
Hey.
Come here.
Is she okay?
-Did she go insane?
-Did she go crazy?
What are we going to do?
Should we call the teacher?
Hey, we should call 911.
Hey, report this.
Should we talk to her?
Maybe she really sees ghosts.
-Can you please step aside?
-Oh, no.
Stop it.
No. No way.
Yu-na, it's me.
You can come out now.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Is there a place
where she can lie down and rest?
The infirmary is
at the end of the hallway.
Thanks.
Something must've happened to her.
It was the fourth Mago
that hurt my intern, wasn't it?
The number four in the black dress.
Don't dare to number the deities.
Though they look different,
they're one with greater plans.
Don't you think it's lame to say
that they have greater plans
when they don't even appear
in the way humans want them to?
Mago wanted
the vengeful ghost that stayed
at the hotel as a guest.
If Mago finds it, will she get rid of it?
Another Mago wants
to bring it back to the hotel.
The greater plans of the deities are
always so darn confusing.
They can be generous and cruel.
That's how the deities are.
The first one wants me
to go to the afterlife,
and the fourth one wants to destroy me
once I become an evil ghost.
You're right, they're all deities.
But who do you think is stronger?
The first one, or the fourth one?
Don't you dare...
to number the deities.
You're just avoiding to answer that.
Whoever is stronger,
they only have one goal.
Anyway, I will have to leave here.
-What's that?
-This is my answer.
Yu-na felt something odd
from the cellphone.
I think the guest of Room 13
harmed a human
by spreading a video through the network.
We'll only know
when we open the video link.
But to make the ghost appear,
we'll need to use a human as bait.
Who should open the link?
No one comes to my mind.
There's only one human at this hotel
who can be the bait.
Get Chan-sung.
No.
Based on what's being said
in the group chat,
I'm sure it's a sex tape
filmed without consent.
Filming such a thing
is a criminal offense,
so is watching it.
I'll never watch anything like this, ever.
What a great man.
What a smart man you are.
But you have to be brave.
We have to find a ghost.
With this?
It's the guest that stayed in Room 13.
We have to open it to find the ghost.
You're saying
that the guest became vengeful
because of some accident
involving this video?
The video might be unpleasant,
or it might be terrifying.
Are you up for it?
IT'S THE FAMOUS VIDEO? I DIDN'T WATCH IT.
I see an empty room.
There's no one.
Yu-na said that she felt something
when the phone rang.
This is where the ghost was.
Here.
I can still feel the grudge of her here.
She created this room.
So you're saying this wasn't
an illegally filmed video?
No,
this is just a room that's built
with the grudge of a ghost.
There must be a few more like this.
Yu-na said that she felt something eerie
even before the man played the video.
She sent the video only to her targets.
Then there must be a next one.
Where could she be right now?
She's probably sent a video
of a room that looks just like this
to the next target,
ready to kill him when he plays the video.
Get off the phone when you're with her.
It's for work. I have to send
something to a client.
Honey.
Honey!
It has been five years
since my sister died,
but the video is still found online.
You must be quite familiar
with cases like this.
There's no way we can get
the videos off the Internet.
That's true.
Were those who distributed
the video punished?
Punished?
All they had to do was pay
some fines when Ga-yeong died.
Is this man related to the incident?
He and Ga-yeong went to the same college.
The video was shared
in the group chat for male students.
That's where the video was leaked.
Her classmates laughed at her
watching the video together.
-Look at that.
-Amazing.
Do you remember who watched the video?
How can I forget?
I still remember all their names.
Had just one of them told us
about the video,
we would've prevented it from spreading.
Then maybe my sister...
wouldn't have died.
My sister locked herself in her room
like a lunatic
and looked all over online to see
if there were more videos of herself.
She was slowly dying.
THE QUEEN OF MECHANICAL ENGINEERING
Now that she's dead,
she must be in peace
free from pain. Right?
I truly...
hope so as well.
The man who filmed the video and sold it
was also a member of the group chat.
What's funny is
that the man now owns
a video-sharing platform,
getting rich and having a nice life.
He really is living a nice life.
So nice that I want to kill him.
Don't get so mad. It'll drain your energy.
This is delicious. Try it.
No, thanks.
The last one is always the best one.
See? The vengeful ghost left
the best one for the last too.
That's why I'm sure she'll come for him.
All we need to do is just to take
his phone to our hotel
before the video is sent to it.
Really?
Do you think she will really leave
the last target here and follow us?
I can't believe somebody like him is
so well off.
The deities are so unfair.
That's why I don't like them.
As I said, the last one is
always the best one.
You're Mr. Koo Chan-sung,
the manager of Hotel del Luna?
Del Luna.
It must be new.
No, it's been around for a very long time.
Are you here to post
an advertisement on our website?
No.
We're here on behalf of our guest.
She desperately wishes
to meet you.
Me?
Who is she? Why does she want to meet me?
She's someone
who holds a lot of grudges against you.
Against me?
I've never done anything for anyone
to feel that way against me.
What are you doing?
You have a really nice yacht.
I'm also planning to buy one like yours.
She's the hotel owner.
My gosh, you've traveled
to so many incredible places.
I should go to these places before I die.
That's enough.
It's rude to take photos
of someone's private space
without their permission.
Really?
What was that?
You have a wedgie.
Hey.
How much do I get paid if I upload
an illicit photo like this
on your website?
One hundred won? Two hundred?
I wonder how many of these photos
need to get uploaded
for you to be able to buy a yacht
and travel to all those places?
-About a million?
-Are you digging into something?
Are you guys reporters? Or cops?
The hotel was just a lie, wasn't it?
No wonder I had never heard of it.
I guess we should invite you over one day
in order to show you that it wasn't a lie.
Get out of here right now
before I call the guards.
Whenever
you see our hotel,
please feel free to visit.
Let's go.
"Always do your best.
The deities will take care of the rest."
Seriously? You believe this kind of stuff?
I'm a very religious man.
If the deities gave you this kind
of life even after what you did,
it just shows how unreasonable
the deities are.
It's his cell phone.
Good job, Chan-sung.
We need to get to the hotel
before the video is sent to the phone.
We should hurry.
Chan-sung did his best
regardless of how weak he is.
I wonder if the deities would do the same.
It's been quite long.
Why isn't the video link here yet?
Is the cell phone out of battery?
The Wi-Fi here works just fine.
The others definitely got the video
through their cell phones.
Cell phones are...
not the only routes to send the video.
Did you check the CCTV footages?
Those people who came in the afternoon
definitely stole my cell phone.
The CCTV footage during that time
all got deleted for some reason.
Are you kidding me?
We have so many CCTVs.
You better find it no matter what.
Yes, sir.
I guess she can send the video
through other routes.
I should go back there.
Chan-sung, your job is done here.
The rest will be taken care of.
What do you mean? By whom?
Mago will show up there.
I'm curious to know
what form she'll appear in.
I wonder if she'll be merciful
or cruel.
CEO, JEONG EUN-SEOK
HERE'S THE VIDEO YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR
What's this?
It's not the CCTV footage of my office.
What is this?
My gosh, what is this?
What?
Was it hacked?
The security system must be a mess.
Look at me.
Who are you?
I'll kill you.
You're an evil ghost
that has harmed humans.
You shall vanish here and now.
Now that she's dead,
she must be in peace
free from pain. Right?
Why won't the deities appear in the way
humans want them to?
This is a glass of a cocktail
to console the soul who has gone.
I think Mr. Koo is heartbroken.
He had his chin up high
after sending off a few customers,
but this incident gave him a burn.
Gosh, that's hot!
It's hot.
He's hurt because he was sincere.
Mr. Koo is a good man.
It's so hard to hate him.
Nothing would have changed
even if you had arrived there earlier.
It's what the deities decided.
Could the same happen
to all of you here too?
Do you mean vanishing?
Yes.
We're all souls after all.
If we stay behind in this world
instead of going to the afterlife,
there's always a chance
the same could happen to us.
If it's dangerous,
why are you still here?
Did you have a sad and painful death
just like her?
Is it the same for all of you?
Mr. Kim and Ms. Choe too?
But
we won't run out there and make trouble.
Don't worry.
YOU'RE INVITED TO HOTEL DEL LUNA
PRESIDENT JANG MAN-WOL
Go mail this out.
What is this?
An invitation.
We promised to invite him, remember?
Are you going to invite him?
But our guest is already gone.
We failed to serve
one of our guests properly.
That's why we should do
what she wanted to do in her stead.
We'll do the best we can.
TO MR. JEONG EUN-SEOK
"Hotel del Luna"?
Whenever you see our hotel,
please feel free to visit.
This is eerie.
YOUR DESTINATION HAS CHANGED
Turn left.
Turn right.
Go straight.
Turn left.
Turn right.
Make a U-turn.
229-7, MYEONG-DONG 8-GIL
Straight.
Is it really this way?
I said, go straight. Straight.
Stop!
What is this?
What is this place?
"Hotel del Luna"?
Did I really come here?
Welcome, sir.
You received an invitation, didn't you?
Ms. Jang is waiting for you.
This way.
What?
It's you.
Welcome. We prepared
a room for you, Mr. Jeong.
So this hotel really exists.
How did you do this?
Did you hack into my car?
You came here with our owner's invitation.
Please follow me.
This is the room.
Like I told you last time,
the guest who looked for you
used to stay in this room.
You said no one has a grudge against you.
Did someone come to your mind?
I'll go in and find out
why you're doing this to me.
This is...
Do you know where this is?
It's my old room.
Do you also remember
the thing you did in this room?
Why is this room here now?
What is this place?
A hotel right between this world
and the other world.
A hotel for souls.
Stop joking around.
There's no such thing.
Was that a dream?
It wasn't.
Who are you?
I invited you to the hotel.
So that wasn't a dream?
It's not a place you can come in a dream.
You can come only when you're dead.
Wait, I'm dead?
No, you aren't dead.
I wanted to ask a question,
so I had to bring your soul here.
You're standing at the boundary
between life and death right now.
What?
Why are you in such a hurry?
I told you that I had a question.
What do you want to know?
You've been to that room.
Do you remember now?
Our guest who made a visit to you.
Do you remember
who that woman is?
That woman...
I will kill you.
Who is that woman?
You killed her.
-I never killed anyone.
-You did.
You stripped her naked
and kicked her outside,
so she was stabbed to death
by everyone's eyes.
You have to remember.
I have no idea. I don't know who she is.
It's what you did. Why don't you know?
Try harder!
Yes, it's something I did.
But I have no idea who she is exactly.
There are so many!
It was a dream.
It was.
Gosh, I thought I really died.
He didn't tell you a good answer.
Why did you send him back?
That's not what I was curious about.
I tried my best to show
that he's the worst.
Now, what will the deities do?
I remember now. Yun Ga-yeong.
Right. I heard she committed suicide.
I remember that now.
The victim of the train accident
at Gyeongbu Line this morning
was identified as CEO Jeong Eun-seok
of World Disk, a file-sharing platform.
Jeong was under investigation
by the police
for distributing illegal pornography
and embezzling company funds.
The circumstances
of the accident are still unknown.
The police have been investigating
the gang members
for a connection with the porn videos,
but the investigation has faced a dead end
since they couldn't find
any feasible connection.
The navigator and event data recorder
in Jeong's car...
I guess the deities really exist.
The investigation will not be easy.
No other human lives were lost
in this accident.
Those who got hurt on the train
at the time of the accident are
being treated at a nearby hospital.
I'm feeling better now.
I'm staying here
because I don't want to go to school.
Tell your friends that it was
because of some bug and go back to school.
If you like school that much,
you should come to my school.
I mean, you can just show yourself
to people like you did the other day.
I can't do that for long.
Especially during the day.
Then how about we get out of here now?
I'll buy you something delicious.
Where's my brother?
Your brother is right here.
That old man is
the founder of this hospital.
He's acquainted with Yu-na's dad,
so I even introduced myself.
Do you know what's uncanny?
He has the same name as you.
His name is Ji Hyeon-jung.
Hyeon-jung.
What is it? Do your legs hurt?
Do you want a piggyback ride? Come here.
How much do you like me?
This much.
That's so little.
That much? As many as your loose teeth?
Ji Hyeon-jung.
I'm sorry. I wasn't calling you.
I'm sorry.
Ji Hyeon...
Jung. What is this?
He always disappears
without saying a thing.
Hyeon-jung's little sister is
quite old now.
I heard that she lost her vision
and that her health deteriorated.
I guess we're going to
see Hyeon-jung off pretty soon.
Will they all get on the bus
to the afterlife today?
You go first. We'll go later.
I'll leave first. You can come later.
I got to live with my first love
all my life.
So you should make your first love
come true here too.
You can leave then without any regrets.
Thank you for everything. Take care.
The platform is this way.
You look upset.
My sister is upset too,
saying it was impudent
of you two to test us.
We would've welcomed you
if you came looking like that
in front of our guest.
If we start showing up
in the way they want,
they'll stop putting
in any efforts themselves.
You must be doing a good job.
I think the flower will bloom.
You should look after it well
so you can send her off.
Isn't it beautiful?
The sea looks really beautiful.
Yes, indeed.
It makes me sad.
It's beautiful.
The funds that Jeong Eun-seok concealed
were found.
It was discovered at a sunflower field
near Jeong's hometown.
About 4 billion won in 50,000-won bills...
He asked us if we were
reporters or police officers
because he was doing
something illegal like that.
By the way, the owner of that field
must be someone stupid like you.
If he finds four billion won in cash,
he should keep it. Why did he report it?
My goodness.
This must be why he had a picture
of a sunflower field in his office.
What?
Don't you remember?
You took a picture of it.
That's why he acted so sensitive
when you took those pictures.
Pictures?
That's enough.
No way.
A field of money was right before my eyes,
and I had no idea.
That's what I should've asked him.
My sunflower field.
POLICE TO INVESTIGATE
CONNECTION TO JEONG'S DEATH
My four billion won!
How is that your money?
That's a ridiculous claim of ownership.
My money.
Chan-sung went out to sail on my yacht
with his boss.
He said he should calm his angry boss.
Chan-sung is sailing on a yacht
with his boss?
Is he entertaining his boss?
I wouldn't call it entertaining.
It's more like a date.
I lost four billion won
right in front of my eyes.
I'm in no mood to ride
someone else's yacht.
Like I said, that money isn't yours.
How can you say that
just because you have a picture of it?
Forget it.
Can't you just console me
even if you don't mean it?
"Would you like me to buy you a yacht?"
You could say something like this.
Why are you getting on my nerves?
I'll buy you a yacht then.
Here. Now that you have a picture,
it's yours.
You are a thief
if you want something that's not yours.
I am a thief.
Didn't you see in your dream?
Your people were all thieves?
The man who married you
looked like he had a higher status.
Married? Me?
I saw you wearing a red bridal dress.
Since it looked fancy,
I assumed you married someone
with some nobleman.
I was...
wearing someone else's dress.
Chan-sung.
I was a bad person.
I'm still bad now,
but I was a lot worse before.
Since you can see my past,
you'll gradually find out
how much of a horrible person I was.
What is it?
Where?
Chan-sung.
Hey, Mi-ra.
Are there more secrets
in this hotel I'm not aware of?
Ms. Jang can never leave this hotel.
Let's do nice things together.
It's better to see
and eat good things together.
What I have is hell.
It's not that wonderful
to be in hell together.
Just let her pass by.
How could I just let her pass by?
Don't do it.
Run away from me, Chan-sung.
I don't care if this is
your prison or your fence.
I will stay here with you.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu
Cheong-myeong, is that you?
You look happy,
Princess Song-hwa.
FULL MOON
Why are you here?
Why do you think?
Do you think I came here
to congratulate your wedding?
I shouldn't have shown you
mercy back then.
The big smile you had on your face earlier
was very beautiful.
What a pity.
The groom is never going to see it.
I'll greet him in your stead.
My smile might not look beautiful, though.
Chan-sung.
Hey, Mi-ra.
She's my friend.
I wonder how she knew I'd be here.
Chan-sung.
You brought her here.
I'm sorry for making you uncomfortable.
This is why you came.
They had no intention of letting me go...
from the beginning.
Jang Man-wol.
Is there something wrong?
She's smiling again...
right in front of me.
Gosh, Mi-ra!
Go look after her.
That is your job.
Here.
-Hey, Chan-sung.
-Oh, sorry.
-Hold my hand.
-Okay.
Here.
Thanks.
Well...
I did come to bother you,
but I didn't know
I'd end up doing it this way.
Drink this.
You drank seawater earlier.
It'll refresh you.
Was her name Jang Man-wol?
Your boss. Did she leave because of me?
Do you know her by any chance?
No, I've never seen her before.
Why do you ask? Did she say she knows me?
Did I see her at the hospital?
Anyway, I'm being such a nuisance.
By the way,
that was not intentional at all.
The wind blew suddenly
as if someone was pushing me.
My gosh, that was so scary.
Was it she who did that?
Nothing's been going my way.
I must be cursed or something.
Should I go see a shaman?
You need to sprinkle salt.
You must purify yourself
when evil ghosts are bugging you.
Don't stay out until late at night
just in case, and try not to be alone.
You sound just like my grandma right now.
She always used to say
that I must be careful at all times
because of my bad karma
from my past lives.
She gave me this.
She said it'll protect me.
You still wear that bracelet?
You remember it.
Chan-sung, I think bad ghosts are
following me around.
-Stay with me at night.
-I have to work at night.
I called a cab for you,
so just go home when it comes.
I lost my purse though.
I've already paid for the cab ride.
I'll put it on your tab, so pay me back.
Don't forget that you're in debt,
which is even scarier than ghosts.
Gosh.
My gosh.
Chan-sung.
You brought her here.
This is why you came.
I wonder if she's okay.
LEE MI-RA
"Lee Mi-ra."
She's the girl he used to date
back when he was in the States.
What a cruel twist of fate.
Enough is enough, please.
DELETE ONE IMAGE
Gosh, how much longer
will you folks keep that up?
Let's go!
I have a lot on my mind right now.
Those ridiculous dance moves are
really getting on my nerves.
Enough, okay?
This is nice!
My gosh, so nice!
Next news.
Ms. Park Heung-ja,
the oldest living person in the country...
You folks can
take a break and start dancing away again
after I get off.
She was the only living person
in the country born in the 19th century.
Ms. Park lived to be 120
and led a happy life
with her children and grandchildren,
always offering positive words of wisdom
with a smile on her face.
She led a great life
and passed away with no regrets.
IN MOURNING
You've enjoyed a fortunate life
for over a century,
so you can leave with no regrets.
You're going to leave like this?
Your great-grandson's wife is due
quite soon.
Wait a couple of months, and you can meet
your great-great-grandchild.
She lived for 120 years.
She has 8 children and 24 grandchildren.
It'd be foolishly greedy of her
to stay just to meet
her great-great-grandchild.
Your great-great-grandchild will be
so adorable.
You'll be incredibly sad
if you don't get to meet this baby.
I said, she lived for 120 years.
You have nothing to be sad about.
Why stop a soul
who is ready to rest in peace?
I stopped her?
No, her great-great-grandkid did.
She has witnessed three centuries
and experienced everything
humans could possibly experience
in one lifetime.
And because of you, that special soul will
wander around the realm of the living now.
They won't let such a special soul
wander around.
Look, that nosy woman is already here.
Her children are great cooks.
This funeral food is really delicious.
Hey, try some.
I can tell right away
it came out of frozen ready meals.
If you have to cook yourself
for the funeral,
your family will never be at peace.
That's how it is these days.
I guess her family's motto is
to take the easy way.
This is why her family was so happy.
Did you interrupt
that soul's journey
to the afterlife just to see me?
I'm kind of regretting it.
It's too much of a hassle.
I should have gone to her right away.
To that woman, Song-hwa.
No, in this life, she's Lee Mi-ra.
While you were shriveled up
and your time stopped,
she came back to this life
as a human after living many lives.
You have met due to the connection
in your previous life.
Just let her pass by.
How could I just let her pass by?
To you, she may be an object
of an unresolved grudge.
To her,
you're a piece of her previous lives
that she doesn't even remember.
You wanted me to let her pass by.
That's why you made me meet her
through Chan-sung.
You cannot harm that girl.
Only if I let her pass by,
I could leave this world peacefully.
Just like the warmhearted Mago wants.
To give you some relief,
I'll go back to the hotel
without causing trouble and stay there.
Drop me off on your way.
Or you can take me to the Samdo River.
Will...
he come too?
For a flower to blossom,
she needs to feel the wind
and face the rain too.
Do you know where Ms. Jang is?
She hasn't come back yet.
Did anything happen on your outing?
She got mad all of a sudden
and disappeared.
Ms. Jang's sudden change of mood
isn't special.
It happens all the time.
When she gets mad, she usually
goes shopping or to a restaurant.
She's probably at a department store
or at a famous restaurant now.
She probably can't do that
because her credit card's maxed out.
Then, she must be livid.
I should stay away from her today.
When she gets livid,
does she vanish into thin air
and not come back to the hotel?
That never happens.
Ms. Jang has to come back to the hotel.
No matter how far she runs away,
the hotel will chase after her.
The hotel will chase after her?
Are there more secrets
in this hotel I'm not aware of?
If Ms. Jang didn't tell you,
-you don't--
-I don't have to know?
I'm not here to stay
just temporarily anymore.
If all the hotel staff knows what it is,
I must know too.
You said that she was tied down
to this hotel for a punishment.
Does her punishment follow after her
when she runs away from it?
That's right.
Ms. Jang can never leave this hotel.
She can't go to the afterlife.
And she can't live in this world either.
It looks like she tried several times
to run away at first.
But it never worked.
Ms. Jang is the Moon Tree.
And the energy of the Moon Tree
is creating this space.
Wherever she goes,
the Moon Tree will put down roots there.
And there stands
the Guest House of the Moon.
When she stays away from the hotel
for more than a day,
the Moon Tree follows her to where she is.
That's why she must return.
It's impossible for her to escape from it.
That means
she's been locked up in this hotel.
But why was she tied down here?
I heard
that she almost became an evil ghost,
but Mago brought her here
and tied her down to this place.
You've seen what happened
to the vengeful ghost
who harmed humans in this life.
To Ms. Jang, this may be her prison,
but it's also a fence.
It's safe for her to stay here.
Here.
Thank you.
You were lucky. No one took your bag.
Thank you so much.
How did this end up on the bus?
Wait.
My photo is missing.
Amusement park.
It looks like Lee Mi-ra was happy.
Chan-sung?
Mr. Koo told me to prepare this for you.
He was quite worried
when you didn't come back
after you disappeared without a word.
I met someone,
and I needed some time to think alone.
As he was worried,
I told him why you had no choice
but to come back to the hotel.
You did?
Where's Chan-sung now?
Is she okay?
Your friend.
I made her fall into the water.
Did she drown?
She's fine.
Too bad.
Why aren't you asking me
why I made her fall into the water
and what I saw in her face?
You should ask me millions of questions,
scold me, and stop me.
If I try to stop you, will that work?
I really don't know.
You call yourself a really bad person.
And seeing how you've been stuck here
for 1,000 years,
I guess you did something very serious.
When I saw you in my dream,
you were just in love.
So what did you do earlier?
What?
Where did you go after ditching me?
There's nothing much for you to do
with a maxed-out credit card.
I don't need you or my credit card
to have fun, you know.
I attended a dance party
and ate nice food at a feast.
A dance party?
Yes, the dance moves were
really mysterious.
And you went there alone?
You could've invited me. Unbelievable.
If you were there,
it would've been a sight.
Let's do nice things together.
It's better to see
and eat good things together.
The view is much better
now that I'm with you.
Whatever it is you're going to do,
just don't forget this.
I don't care if this is
your prison or your fence.
I will...
stay here with you.
Doctor.
Sir, it's raining.
I'm always happy whenever it rains
because I'll be with you.
I'm not your doctor, miss.
Please stay with me until the song ends.
Honey?
Hey.
What's that?
You're the one who said
she should stay with us.
Me? To whom?
Me.
What are you doing here?
I was scared to be alone.
You have no idea what happened to me.
-What happened?
-I found the purse I had lost
on an express bus
when I never got on one.
Hold on. Does this mean
that it got on the bus itself?
My gosh!
Stop it, both of you.
When I'm home, I'd like a rest
from the supernatural.
But this can't be explained
scientifically.
Someone must've taken your purse
and left it on the bus.
Yes, that's possible. You're right.
Didn't you lose anything?
Money or credit cards?
I never carried around any.
That being said, can I borrow some money?
Sanchez!
I'll let her stay here for now,
just in case.
You're opening
the hotel's amusement park again?
Yes, someone seems to have had
some fond memories of an amusement park.
Whoever it is,
the guest will have fun here.
So when will that guest arrive?
I'll invite her soon.
Escort her with care.
Yes, ma'am.
By the way, where did you send
Mr. Kim and Ms. Choe?
To seek out some land.
It's eerie and full of negative energy.
There aren't any buildings
in the way either.
I like this place.
There aren't
any shopping malls or restaurants
within a 15-minute drive.
Ms. Jang won't like it.
Let's leave
and head over to the next candidate,
a sauna building.
Why is she suddenly looking to buy land?
It seems she can barely
pay off her credit card bills.
You're right.
Unless she sells the land she has.
No way. Ms. Jang loves that land.
It's very close to a department store
and naengmyeon restaurants.
But then again, Chan-sung is being
too tight with money.
So it might be possible.
She chose that land
after much consideration.
There's no way she'd sell it. Let's go.
Eunseong Sauna.
EUNSEONG SAUNA
You're very quick
to master new features on devices.
You get the hang of it
after clicking here and there.
I can't, since I'm from
the Joseon Dynasty.
I am from that era, too.
You should correct how you speak first.
Until when will you use archaic phrases?
I'll try my best.
Wait for me.
Hold up.
Thank you for the tour!
Thanks, man.
We'll totally contact you
after talking to our boss.
The hotel opened up an amusement park?
Yes, you should check it out.
It'll be fun to go there
with my boyfriend.
Did you get a boyfriend?
Rumors about me having one are
all over the school.
Is that so? Good for you.
You have a boyfriend now,
so keep up with your studies
and go to classes on time. Okay?
Whatever!
You really liked to go to school.
How could you become a total idiot?
What's wrong with telling you
to study hard at school?
It would be nice to study hard
and become a cool doctor
just like Mr. Koo's girlfriend.
Ms. Jang told me to keep an eye on her
and find out what people think of her.
Can I eat a lot of onion?
-Sure.
-Let's have it together.
-Okay.
-Add a lot of onion please.
She likes onions.
Onion starts with an "o."
Stop showing off, rich boy.
ONION
Ms. Jang is kinder than I thought.
She is taking care of humans
around Mr. Koo as well.
Do you really think she is being kind?
Can you be kind to my boyfriend?
Why? Is your boyfriend mean?
Right.
My boyfriend is so mean and a total idiot.
Is Dr. Han all right?
-He isn't.
-I see.
He scares me to death every night.
He sang in his study last night.
What?
-You want to go in?
-Yes.
I need to find something
to report to Ms. Jang.
Listen to this.
Shall I pretend to be
a cute next-door neighbor
who's come to borrow a screwdriver?
No, don't you have other ideas?
There's something strange in this house.
What is it?
That's not a human, right?
Mi-ra borrowed my Qing Dynasty ceramic.
Well, she already took it
before I agreed to lend it, though.
Anyway, I let her borrow it.
She'll sell it and use all the money.
You won't get it back.
I'll get it back for you.
It's okay. If she doesn't return it,
I'll seize her salary.
You can't do it, but I can.
I should have seized her salary
or something
for all the money she took from me.
You said you won't stay for long
at that hotel, right?
Veronica's father recently
took over a hotel in Sydney.
Two of my father's restaurants will open
there.
It's a five-star hotel.
Would you like to work there?
I don't plan to leave this hotel.
Is there a special reason
why you have to stay at Man-wol's hotel?
You have a good career background,
and you enjoy showing off.
But it's a nameless hotel
without even a proper name card.
You are always working overtime there.
I find it very strange.
Sanchez, do you think I'd work
at an average hotel?
My hotel has world-class facilities.
You can't even imagine
how special the guests are.
There is only one shortcoming.
And that is I can't boast about it.
I see.
I thought you were working
for that crappy hotel
because you have feelings for Man-wol.
What?
I got you right on the spot.
You look like a pushover,
but you are cold.
-You seem slow, but you are sharp.
-Yes.
Right. It's just like how I look
like a pizza place owner,
but I'm a millionaire, right?
Veronica is now fully in love
with that side of me.
I'll get you more soda.
Okay.
LEE MI-RA
Did you sell Sanchez's ceramic?
Chan-sung.
Is there an available room
in your hotel right now?
I can't take a photo of a ghost
with my phone.
I can't take a picture of you either.
You can, if I let myself be seen
like I did at your school.
Although I can't do it for long.
Do it now.
Come on, let yourself be seen.
There you are.
I'm taking the picture now.
What are you guys doing here?
Mr. Koo?
What are you doing here?
We followed your doctor girlfriend.
Mi-ra?
Why?
I told them to.
Did you come to attach a ghost
to Mi-ra to torment her?
I thought you didn't care.
But you seem worried
I might do something to her.
Are you here to stand guard
over your girlfriend's house?
This is not her house.
It's her friend's house.
Mi-ra is staying with me.
At Sanchez's?
So you're living together.
Are you going to keep following her?
Do I have to keep guard?
I just wanted to know
what a good life she has.
Where are you going?
You have to take the ghost.
I didn't put it there.
I didn't even know
you were living with her.
If I had known,
I would've released 108 ghosts.
Either way, it means
there is a ghost in this house.
Let's take her to the hotel.
Ms. Jang.
You only call me that
when you want something from me.
I heard from Mi-ra
that you keep hearing strange noises
and see strange things.
You want to stay at a hotel
for a while, right?
I got this house from my parents.
It's quite old,
so it's not properly soundproofed.
Maybe that's the reason.
I told him everything.
You can't even sleep after you moved in.
We could have just gone to your hotel.
You didn't have to come.
I came to see who the guest is.
We don't accept average guests.
Is that why your boss is with you?
Yes.
You can only come to our hotel
when you have Ms. Jang's invitation.
You have many doctors in your family.
Your hotel must run
on some sort of membership.
We just need an ordinary hotel.
Then you do that.
Excuse me.
Ms. Jang.
We have to take the guest to the hotel.
Forget it.
Why should I take care
of this house's ghost?
It's the house of my friend's friend.
I don't like your friend, and I don't
like you since you're her friend.
Is this the sound?
Do you hear it too?
We are not crazy, right?
We have a special service in our hotel.
You should get the service.
Her name is Gyeong-a
and she is dressed in retro style.
She is waiting for a doctor.
Could she be looking for
the dead father of this house?
Maybe.
If she sees you, she might run away.
I will go in first.
Aren't you scared?
No, I have you.
Gyeong-a?
Min?
Min.
I'm all right.
Min, you came back.
Min.
Who is Min?
I'm sorry I hurt you.
But my heart
already belongs to the doctor.
So, Min and the doctor are
different people.
Are you sick?
Min, I don't have a lot of time.
I can't share that time with you.
But I'll let you give me a goodbye kiss.
Gyeong-a, is this your diary?
Suk-hui, stop it!
Don't touch my things!
I must be Suk-hui.
It's not my fault
you couldn't win Min's heart.
Stop your mean jealousy.
What are all these postcards and letters?
Min, you ask her.
Gyeong-a, what are all these postcards?
I'm very weak, so I can't go outside.
And I don't have any friends.
So I sent my story to a radio station,
and all these people
sent me postcards wishing me well.
"I hope you recover soon.
I also wish you good luck
with your romance.
From Hui, an avid listener
from Ssangmun-dong
who's also lovestruck just like you."
This is actually real.
Hyeok must be here.
There must be someone named Hyeok.
Judging from the look on her face,
Hyeok must like her as well.
So that means Hyeok, Min,
and the doctor all like Gyeong-a
except for Suk-hui.
I guess Suk-hui is the only villain here.
I'll keep pretending I'm Min.
And we should take her to the hotel.
Gyeong-a can't be a guest at our hotel...
because she isn't a soul of a human being.
She's not a ghost then?
Didn't you feel something weird
when she hugged you earlier?
Come to think of it,
I didn't feel cold at all.
I always felt a chill every time
I touched a ghost at our hotel.
But that wasn't the case with Gyeong-a.
That's an imaginary soul
that was created by a human.
"An imaginary soul"?
Yes, it's imaginary.
Gyeong-a was created
in someone's imagination.
Someone created her?
She had an incurable illness,
was loved by Hyeok and Min,
and she even had a love affair
with a doctor.
The diary is real, and someone did send
a story to the radio station.
But the problem is
that it wasn't Gyeong-a.
They were done by the human
who created her.
Who could that be?
If we find that person,
we can get rid of Gyeong-a.
Who is this delusional person
that's so immersed in this sad love story?
What's wrong with you guys?
-Mother, they're here to help us.
-Please leave.
-What's going on?
-Mother, wait.
What are you doing in my study?
Everything here belongs to me.
I see.
May I ask your name, ma'am?
Lee Bok-hui.
You should wait downstairs.
Do you know a lady named Gyeong-a?
I'm Gyeong-a.
I married my husband
when I was 22
through an arranged marriage.
I never got to date anyone.
And that's when...
I created Gyeong-a.
I was so happy to be able to experience
a pure, affectionate,
and passionate love as Gyeong-a,
just like my favorite movie character.
The strong imaginary soul you created
still exists.
It's like an old movie.
I see.
You don't seem startled.
If you live for this long,
you don't get startled that easily.
On top of that,
I was once so delusional
that I created Gyeong-a.
Gyeong-a called me Min.
You look just like him.
She actually liked Min the most.
What about the doctor?
She must've been a huge flirt.
Do I need to get rid of Gyeong-a?
Your son and wife are suffering
because of her.
I see.
I was able to forget about Gyeong-a
thanks to my son.
She got married to a stranger
whom she didn't love.
It must've been hard for her.
Whether it was imaginary or delusional,
I'm sure it still helped her cope
with her situation.
Changing one's reality
by creating an imaginary soul...
That's a good idea.
She asked us to join her for dinner.
What should we do?
She said goodbye to Gyeong-a,
so she must feel lonely.
So you stay as Min
and console her over dinner.
Suk-hui is a villain,
so I'm going to leave.
Okay, then.
It's burning beautifully.
You're right.
It's beautiful.
Ma'am, you don't need to prepare
too many dishes.
Min, just wait here quietly.
Excuse me.
Did Mi-ra leave?
Yes, she probably went back
to the hospital.
By the way, thank you
for inviting us to the hotel.
Pardon?
Your boss gave us invitations
to the hotel.
Invitations?
We'll make sure we visit. I can't wait.
By any chance, did she give
an invitation to Mi-ra as well?
I didn't know there was a hotel here.
Chan-sung is working
at an incredible hotel.
Welcome.
Ms. Jang is waiting for you.
Oh, thank you.
This way.
Please follow me.
Ms. Jang prepared something very special
for you. Let me take you there.
This hotel is amazing.
Welcome.
Welcome to Hotel del Luna.
Thank you for inviting me.
The pleasure's mine.
I just couldn't...
let you pass by.
This place is really nice.
But why is this place empty?
It's not empty.
You just can't see anything
because of that.
This?
You can't see them because of that.
Earlier, you couldn't hear
anything either.
Is this the sound?
We're not crazy, right?
If I take this off,
will I be able to see some other things?
Why don't you let me hold onto it for you?
Do you like it?
Yes, I love amusement parks.
Is that so? I thought so too.
You seem happy in the photo.
You found this.
Thank you.
When I was young,
I went to the amusement park
with my family and took this photo.
That's right.
You from that day are standing over there.
They're my parents and my sister.
I'm happy.
I really hate
that you are
happy.
That's why
I'm going to breathe sadness
into that girl.
And I'll give her to you as a gift.
Hello.
You don't have a happy family.
Your mother said this to you all the time.
"You should have never been born.
I regret giving birth to you."
Your dad got angry whenever he saw you.
"Nothing is working out
all because of you, you witch."
After your annoying sister was born,
your parents loved only her.
Look at this.
The day you came to the amusement park,
your family left you here and went home.
It was the saddest day of your life.
Mom. Dad. Don't abandon me.
All right. Go.
Go to her and fill every day of her life
with sad memories of a girl
who should've never been born.
Thank you, Chan-sung.
Thanks to you, I got to meet her.
And thanks to you, I've found a great way.
So...
I was able to resolve my grudge a bit.
Don't do it.
I already did.
This is...
way stronger than
the imaginary soul Bok-hui created.
Because I created it.
It's a curse.
-Stop it.
-You can't stand it?
Then run away from me, Chan-sung.
I'll let you go.
I won't.
Protect me.
Chan-sung, let her go.
Whatever it is you're going to do,
just don't forget this.
I don't care if this is
your prison or your fence.
I will...
stay here with you.
Aren't you scared?
No, I have you.
You woke up.
Who are you?
Ms. Jang asked me to take you home
because you were too drunk.
I was drunk?
Yes. The hospital is
in Myeongnyun-dong, right?
-Sir, let's get going.
-Sure.
Everything will be okay now.
You ruined everything.
I really don't know.
When I saw you in my dream,
you were just in love.
This is the last time we'll look
at this scenery together.
I'm leaving with my people.
Are you planning to join the rebellion?
They wish to set this country right.
It's much better than living
as a thief here and getting caught
and killed eventually.
Come to the palace.
I can keep you safe.
Are you telling me
to desert my people and go to you?
I can't.
Then shall I go to you?
If you beg me to come,
I will risk my life and go with you.
Don't.
There is no way
we can be together.
Right.
I suppose I won't need
to come here ever again.
You were a great drinking buddy,
so I will miss you.
Everyone's ready. When should we leave?
He was here.
He's probably there now.
Let me go see him for one last time.
Man-wol.
Will you come back?
Yes. Of course, I'll be back.
You don't need to come back.
I'll be fine either way,
so do as you wish.
No, I will come back.
Let me see him just once more.
Wait for me.
All of your people will die
because of you.
Thanks to you,
I made a great contribution.
You were the one who took me there
and bought me enough time.
It's all thanks to you.
Hence, I will spare your life.
I will kill you.
I will kill you...
at all costs.
If you wish to kill me,
you will have to stay alive.
Yeon-u...
Yeon-u.
Yeon-u!
No, Yeon-u.
Let go of me!
Yeon-u.
Yeon-u!
Since you helped the general
make a great contribution,
I will show mercy on you.
FULL MOON
I will kill you
at all costs.
Chan-sung.
Are you all right?
What happened?
Man-wol brought you home.
And you've been sleeping for several days.
"Several days"? What do you mean?
You've been sleeping
for three days straight.
Why is that painting here?
Man-wol left it here.
That...
She said it was taking up space,
so she left it here.
By the way, is she going somewhere?
Wherever she goes,
the Moon Tree will put down roots there.
And there stands
the Guest House of the Moon.
She's gone.
When you see me off, don't feel lonely.
Whether...
this place is a fence
or prison for me...
what I have is hell.
It's not that wonderful...
to be in hell together.
Goodbye.
Chan-sung.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu