Hotel Del Luna Blu-ray Disc 3
Subtitle re-timing by Jharel
Chan-sung!
Don't look.
Don't let her hear your breathing.
But I hear--
Don't listen to it.
What's the matter?
She's the guest staying in this room.
You'll go mad if you see her.
Don't turn around.
Get out of here once the door opens.
Go.
Ma'am.
You won't ever be able
to step out of that door.
I apologize for waking you up.
Why don't you go back inside
and get some sleep?
I guess the smell of incense
made you go crazy.
You've been locked up
in that closet for such a long time.
And you still get angry
when you see a human being?
Do you want to go outside
and vent your anger again?
You're a guest here.
So I won't shove you in the closet.
You should quietly crawl back inside
on your own.
Koo Chan-sung.
Jang Man-wol?
Stop being stupid.
You don't know what a coward he is.
No matter how many times you call him,
he won't come back.
Chan-sung?
Jang Man-wol!
Was that Mr. Third Choice
who ran out at lightning speed?
Even if you look with one eye closed,
it's not Mr. Koo.
I thought so too.
The hair was all loose and wild.
It's the guest in Room 13.
She has left the hotel.
Our plan has failed. This is a disaster.
Chan-sung.
That thing is not here.
You can let me go.
You...
saw it, didn't you?
Just a glimpse.
So have you gone crazy?
I'm not crazy.
I was so frightened
that I can't calm myself down now.
What about you? Are you hurt?
Are you all right, Man-wol?
Chan-sung.
Were you scared?
I'm not hurt.
I'm fine.
Why you...
You've gone a little crazy.
I was just playing around.
Were you really scared?
Then, is it really true that you go mad
if you see that ghost?
I thought you said that just to scare me.
Yes, it's true.
If you had seen it properly,
you would've gone completely mad.
Really?
She's really left, right?
Yes, she ran away.
I thought you'd take care of it.
How could you let her go like that?
Well, I didn't know some coward
would muster up the courage
and come running in opening the door wide.
What a fool.
What...
Wait for me.
A coward?
Are you calling me a coward?
There's no one else here.
You're such a fool.
What... A fool?
Nobody ever called me that
in my whole life.
-I have an MBA from Harvard, and world--
-Shut up!
That's verbal violence.
Please rephrase it.
-Okay. Shut it.
-Are you joking?
-It's a ghost!
-Where?
You are a coward.
God... I thought there was really a ghost.
I must've made a mistake
while burning the incense. I apologize.
I'm glad you are safe.
Yes.
Ms. Choe, you should take
proper care of the rooms.
That dangerous guest could've harmed
our manager.
No, I'm sorry for worrying you.
Do you see how I just improvised that?
Mr. Third Choice has absolutely no idea
that we put him in that room on purpose.
I don't know.
You looked rather guilty.
I think Mr. Koo is a fool
for not noticing that.
Even if he is a fool, he will notice
when Ms. Fourth Choice comes.
I should tell Hyeon-jung to postpone
bringing in Ms. Fourth Choice.
Yu-na, what are you doing?
Get out of the way.
-Did you just see Yu-na?
-Yes.
I heard she's possessed
by Su-jeong's ghost.
I think it's true.
If you call out Su-jeong, she looks back.
-Really?
-Let's go and see.
-Let's go.
-You call her name.
-She really looks back?
That's so weird.
Su-jeong.
It must be true.
-That's so scary.
-It's scary.
-What?
-What is this?
Goodness.
-What?
-What's happening?
-What is that?
What are you doing?
I didn't want you to get hurt,
so I caught you.
It can be painful.
If I got hurt,
they would've looked at me as a human.
Now, they will call me a monster.
Hey.
Wait for me.
She's getting mad at me for helping her.
You. How did you catch me?
Ghosts can't catch humans.
I'm not an average ghost.
There are prayer beads and amulets
in here.
So get lost, you evil ghost.
My friend.
I'm not a ghost that can be
exorcised by power of religion.
I have the right to stay in this world.
I have a place I belong to,
and I also have a job.
Don't make me laugh.
What kind of ghost has a job?
I'm a hotelier. I'm from Hotel del Luna.
Hotel del Luna?
You know
the owner and manager of our hotel, right?
They helped you live in that body.
So what?
You want me to come out of this body?
You are a really precious person.
You're our precious hope.
You are Ms. Fourth Choice.
The fourth choice?
You are the fourth choice
for our hotel's manager.
Something has happened to
Mr. Third Choice,
so I've come to take you,
the fourth choice.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But you are here because you need me.
Yes.
A ghost even has a mobile phone?
Of course.
I have a job, so I also have a phone.
I told you I have a right to stay here.
Your school's Wi-Fi is good.
Mr. Third Choice is unharmed.
Ms. Fourth Choice will be deferred.
Are you saying you don't need me?
For now.
But I might be back to take you soon.
So...
keep studying hard at school.
Hey!
Give me your number.
I want to send texts to a ghost.
I've never shared my number with a human.
So you don't want to?
You can't?
Forget it then.
Okay. We're now friends.
The manager of Hotel del Luna?
Sounds fun.
Right.
Wait...
Mr. Ji?
I'm glad to see you
still in your right mind.
Thank you for being genuinely delighted.
It sounds as if you all expected
me to turn insane in that room.
Gosh.
You didn't, and that's all that matters.
Ms. Fourth Choice is on standby.
We also discussed
a couple of other ways
to get rid of Mr. Third Choice.
HOW TO ELIMINATE MR. THIRD CHOICE
First, we can send him
to the ghost stationed
at the haunted house in Shincheon-gun.
Thirty years is guaranteed
if he stays clear
of the local Grim Reaper.
Next, we can use a strong vengeful ghost
to have him die suddenly.
VENGEFUL GHOST IN UIJEONGBU
He's an experienced killer
operating in Uijeongbu.
Since he's close by, we can easily--
No, just drop it.
Chan-sung isn't going anywhere.
I'm keeping him by my side.
What if the tree keeps transforming?
Mago sent him here on purpose.
You must drive him out.
If he was really sent by a deity,
then just chasing him out
won't solve anything.
What if flowers blossom?
Flowers?
Let them blossom.
Will there be a day
when colorful flowers blossom and
I willingly walk across the Samdo River?
We'll wait and see.
Do you think she's had a change of heart
and is ready to go to the other world?
No, I think she probably doesn't believe
that flowers will really blossom.
If that was the case,
she shouldn't have agreed
to let him in Room 13.
Her and her mood swings.
I'm just glad that Mr. Koo
isn't the perceptive type.
It'll be awkward if he figures out
that we led him there on purpose.
You sent me to that room
on purpose, didn't you?
You wanted me to die or lose my mind.
You're not as dumb as I thought.
You're right.
Everyone's disappointed
that you didn't go crazy.
How can you all do this to me?
I truly thought of you as my colleagues
and started to like you guys.
Isn't this considered as harassment?
So? Are you here to tattle on them?
Should I give them an earful?
What's the point when you were in on it?
You always ask questions
even though you know the answer.
What a weirdo.
Wait.
Where did it go?
Chan-sung,
I lost one of the earrings.
Check the floor for me.
Seriously?
Just let it slide.
They're simply jealous
because you're still alive
when they're not.
How dumb do you think I am?
What was this really about?
The tree changed after you came here.
We're worried
that our time to leave is near.
Why did you save me though?
If you hadn't, I would've gone crazy.
I wasn't going to intervene,
but a leaf changed my mind.
A leaf?
-This one?
-Yes.
That small leaf bothered me.
Are you saying,
I won your heart by this much?
You're doing it again!
Asking questions
when you know the answer...
Do they teach you that at Harvard?
Asking questions to induce an answer
can lead to determining the truth.
It's a known method by Socrates.
That's what the professors
at Harvard taught me.
But this isn't Harvard,
so just get back to finding my earring.
Is finding it worth another leaf?
Why you...
Don't bother looking for it.
If you find it, I'll kill you.
You say you'll kill me,
but you don't mean it.
You say you're not looking for it,
but you want to.
I know you're cynical,
but your words are even more cynical.
Is it because you've been living
as a ghost for too long?
No, I was born this way.
I've always been cynical.
Did you not catch that in your dream?
You were nice and kind.
Me? Seriously?
Yes, you cared for him with affection.
His name was Yeon-u, I think.
So you saw him too.
I did.
Yeon-u!
You called his name with love,
which is why it got stuck in my head.
Why?
Do you think you might be him?
The thought crossed my mind,
but it doesn't seem likely.
Yeon-u was...
the one who loved me the most.
Do you love me too?
I'm certain that I don't.
Leave then.
Yeon-u.
Man-wol.
With this tree you love,
I'll build the biggest house
that anyone has ever seen.
And you can have it.
What?
You'll build a house for me
with this tree?
Forget it.
I don't plan on building a house
and living with you.
We all grow old.
You should think about putting down roots.
I can't let you live under a tarp
when you become an old lady.
I could be captured and killed
at any moment. That's my life.
I don't even expect to live until I'm old.
But you can.
The fortune teller said
that I'll live a long life
just like this tree.
I'm expected to live 100 years,
so I'll give you my extra years.
If you do, you'll die.
You're right.
It's okay, though.
I don't mind dying for you,
so you can have it all.
This will find a human groom
for your dead daughter.
Whoever finds the red pocket
that holds the deceased's desires
shall be her soul's partner.
I hope that pocket will
find us a good man.
Su-min.
We're getting you married
so that you don't get lonely.
No!
I don't want to get married to a stranger.
You're getting off early today.
Yes, I'm a bit tired.
Well, you're the type
who makes more work for yourself.
It is my job to tend to the guests
as a hotelier.
I guess you've changed your mindset.
I thought you hated our hotel.
Because I won...
someone's heart.
I'm actually a bit of a softie,
so I repay favors by ten times the amount.
-Sorry?
-That means if you're nice to me,
I'll treat you really well.
So please be nice to me.
Did he figure anything out?
What did he say?
He used sarcasm to threaten me.
He said he repays favors
by ten times the amount.
I knew Mago wouldn't bring an easy one.
Are you visiting the hotel, ma'am?
Please help me.
Are you all right, ma'am?
You think this is the front desk?
Why do you keep taking the guests
to my office instead of their rooms?
She has her reasons.
Every ghost has their reasons.
And what's wrong with her? Is she drunk?
She's exhausted
from roaming around too much.
Ma'am, you can't do this to our employee.
I am okay with it.
Fine, then. Go ahead and hug her tight.
She's being forced into a marriage.
She doesn't want to get married
to a complete stranger,
and she doesn't want
to get a living person possessed.
Is it a ghost wedding?
It's for those who are still alive.
Why don't you just go along with it?
You can go up to your room
and think it over again.
Our hotel even has a wedding hall.
If you pay the price,
we can even hold a party for you.
Go ahead and think about it.
Why don't you go up to your room?
This won't do. Excuse me.
Gosh.
Chan-sung.
I see you're strong enough to carry her.
And you used a handcart meant for cabbages
to carry me.
A ghost wedding...
That guest was wearing
a Vera Wang wedding dress.
That means she's from a rich family.
-Get ready for the wedding.
-Yes, ma'am.
Then I'll need to get a new dress.
And I'll need new jewelry too.
Shoes, a purse,
and what else will I need?
Gosh, there's so much to prepare.
Chan-sung should
hurry up and get that money
for the Baekdu Mountain painting.
Good morning!
Good morning, Sanchez.
You're up?
I guess you got some sleep last night.
Yes, I slept well.
I didn't even dream this time.
Maybe it was because I was tired.
Did you buy a lottery ticket?
You want to have a lucky dream?
No, I was expecting someone in my dreams.
Your ex-girlfriend?
The ex-boyfriend of a girl I know.
Or her ex-boyfriends.
It's not a dream,
but you missed a call from your friend.
My friend?
Who?
Man-wol.
Man-wol, from your hotel.
Your phone kept ringing,
so I just answered it.
Man-wol
told me to ask you
when you'd get the money for the painting.
Sanchez,
did you really call her by her name,
Man-wol?
Didn't she get mad and yell at you?
She agreed to call me by my name too.
Just Sanchez.
We're even following each other
on our social media.
You know what? She's actually
quite friendly and polite. Right?
Maybe it's because of her job?
It seemed like she's used to being polite.
She must have known
that Sanchez is really rich.
That's why he was unharmed.
"Man-wol"?
-Put it right there.
-Yes, ma'am.
Hyeon-jung, you said
you know how to play the piano, right?
Practice.
Yes, ma'am.
It's been so long since we had a party.
I'm so excited.
It's better to have many guests
for the party,
so should I invite some guests
who are free?
You think it'll look like a wedding
if there are tons of ghosts in here?
It'll seem like a funeral.
As few as possible.
Yes, ma'am.
By the way, have we found the groom yet?
If some unlucky human
finds that red pocket,
he'll be the groom, I suppose.
The bride doesn't seem to want
an arranged marriage like this.
Mr. Koo went to find the red pocket,
so he could return it to her parents
and talk them out of it.
There won't be a wedding
if he finds it first, right?
Chan-sung left to find the red pocket?
Yes, he's very diligent,
so he's probably looking for it already.
If he finds it, it'll cause trouble.
Why?
Will he become the groom
if he finds it first?
He's been caring so much about ghosts.
Now he's going to marry one.
The bride didn't want to get married
to a complete stranger.
But I bet she'll be okay
with marrying Mr. Koo.
That's good news, Ms. Jang.
Ms. Jang, are you going to let him
get married?
Darn you!
I heard the red pocket fell
somewhere near the lake.
Chan-sung, you're still looking for it?
What are you looking for?
I'll help you find it.
No, it's okay.
Don't mind me, and carry on.
You should ride another lap.
It's going to rain soon.
Then I'll go for one more lap.
Let's go home once I'm done.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Can't you see?
I'm on a picnic.
Why are you on a picnic? It's hot outside.
Fine.
Let me answer the question
that you already know the answer to.
I'm here to see you.
I don't want you to look
for that red pocket.
Just leave it.
Are you worried
I might have to marry her if I find it?
Chan-sung, I'm against this marriage.
I can't accept it.
Just let some other guy pick it up.
She doesn't want to marry
someone she doesn't know.
Whoever picks it up
will get startled. If I find it,
you'll take care of it for me.
You think I'll have your back?
Is that why you're being reckless?
Are you using that to find it?
Can you see where it is?
I see it.
What's wrong with the bike?
I found it.
Chan-sung, you'll get to eat
at your friend's wedding.
Sanchez!
What is this?
What the hell?
Sanchez!
Where is he?
Sanchez, are you okay?
I don't know if it's because of the rain,
but it's really cold.
And maybe because of the rain,
I saw something really weird.
Chan-sung, I saw a strange woman
in our house earlier.
And I think she's still here.
I'm so scared.
What should I do?
Sanchez.
You should go inside and get some sleep.
Let me figure this out.
Hello?
Are you Mr. Koo,
the manager at Hotel del Luna?
Yes, that's me.
I got a call from that hotel
saying they'd like to hold a wedding
for Su-min.
Did you say you got a call
from the owner of our hotel?
Yes.
Are you here because of this?
I didn't know
there was a hotel like this in Seoul.
Welcome.
I see that our manager
safely brought you here.
Now, let's start discussing
the wedding in earnest.
Come this way.
This is where the wedding will take place.
We can prepare a banquet
and provide a suite for her
just like any other wedding.
If you can do that, Su-min won't end up
dying a lonely soul.
Please prepare the best of everything.
We're doing this for our child.
We'll pay and give you
anything that's necessary.
By the way, who's the groom?
You're forcing him to marry her
against his will.
Don't you think you'd feel awkward
to meet the groom?
Are you going to congratulate him
or something?
Then I guess it'd be best not to meet him.
We'll entrust you with everything.
We'll do our best to prepare a wedding
that will satisfy everyone.
I knew they'd be rich.
This is a black card that has no limit.
Parents really have no limit
when it comes to loving their kids.
This is my cup of tea.
What are you planning to do?
I'm going to prepare a wedding.
Sanchez got really shocked.
He's practically stupefied.
It's because he's weak-hearted.
That's why we should hold a wedding
and make her leave as soon as possible.
Is Sanchez really going to be okay
once the wedding's over?
Yes.
It's not like they're going
to register their marriage.
Just think of it as a short nightmare.
There's so much to prepare.
We'll get so busy.
Chan-sung, let's hurry.
I wonder if this is
really going to be okay.
God, I want to pee so bad.
I'm about to burst,
but I'm too scared to go to the bathroom.
When is Chan-sung coming home?
Actually, no.
It's okay. I can do it.
So we were hurrying to go shopping?
It's a wedding after all.
It should look sparkly.
Are we here to buy wedding gifts?
Are these necessary for this wedding?
This one looks nice too.
Why do we only have ten fingers?
I wish I could put on more than ten.
Are we here to buy your rings?
You said we should hurry for Sanchez.
This is no time to look at rings.
I got my hands on a credit card
without a limit.
If you're going to nag, go wait outside.
I only have one neck,
so I can only wear one necklace.
Wearing several necklaces
is becoming a thing.
I like that.
Bring me some more.
Her parents didn't give you a credit card
to pay for your jewelry.
It's meant to be used for the wedding.
Exactly. I'm using their money
for the wedding.
The more money I use for this wedding,
the more relieved they will feel.
Did you arrange the wedding
so you could do this?
I'll return the credit card
and burn up the pocket.
Go ahead.
If you do that, your friend
will have to live
the rest of his life with the ghost bride.
The red pocket encompasses
a strong desire.
That desire tied them together
with a red thread,
so that they're forced to be together.
If you burn the pocket,
the bride will never get to go
to the afterlife.
Can't you just cut their tie?
I'm not the almighty.
Do you know how hard that is?
We'll just have them get married,
then send the bride to the afterlife.
That's what our hotel can do.
Ma'am, please come to this side.
PHARMACY
11-28 YAKJAE-GOLMOKGIL, GYEONGDONG MARKET
HERB MEDICINE MARKET
ORIENTAL HERBAL CLINIC
HEALTH CARE CENTER
PHARMACY
Ma'am.
You're really here.
Who are you?
I'm...
I'm Koo Chan-sung from Hotel del Luna.
You told me to come here to look for you
when we met on the subway.
That wasn't me.
That was my eldest sister.
Hey!
The weather outside is amazing!
Who are you?
He came from Hotel del Luna
to find our eldest sister.
Hotel del Luna?
Our sister goes there often
to pick flowers, doesn't she?
Are you twins?
I mean, triplets?
There are more than three of us.
Why are you asking for our sister anyway?
There will be a ghost wedding
at Hotel del Luna?
The bride doesn't want a wedding
she never asked for,
and the groom is shivering in fear.
Is there a way to fix this?
Like what your boss said,
it'd be best to do the wedding
for the sake of those who are alive.
I guess we don't have a choice
but to hold the wedding.
I know! We could switch the groom.
Instead of someone living,
you could find someone dead as her groom.
Where are we going to find a dead groom?
You have a lot of guests at your hotel.
You're right.
Right?
The bride can choose a groom she likes
to give the red pocket.
The two ghosts can get together
and head over to the afterlife,
holding hands.
Yes, I'll try that.
Thank you. I'll get going.
Hey.
You must be tired from working at night.
You probably can't sleep well.
Try this one. I'm sure it'll help.
It's herb tonic tea.
Thank you.
I think she likes you.
That's precious medicine.
You'll feel energetic
even from a short nap.
Really?
Thank you.
Great.
I narrowed it down to guests
who died before getting married.
Okay.
I better visit them one by one
to ask if they're interested.
Let's start with Room 507.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
But are you interested
in going on a blind date?
We'll now start the date
between Ms. Lee Su-min
and her five prospect grooms.
Why are you sitting there?
Because I want to get married too.
Employees can't participate.
Get back here.
What?
Get over here.
I even got changed for this.
This is unfair.
We'll start over again.
Due to the time limit,
we'll make it short.
Please greet each other
while the hourglass is running.
Tell her about what you did
when you were alive.
I hope you'll get to have
sincere conversations.
Gosh, Chan-sung is wasting his time again.
At least,
the bride will get to marry a groom
whom she can connect better with.
I don't know. I doubt there will be
a man the bride likes.
I like this one.
As you might have noticed,
my friend has a weak heart
and won't be able to do the wedding.
You should choose one of them
to leave for the afterlife together.
It's the best I can do for you.
Please make sure to keep time, everyone.
We'll start with the table number one.
Please give the red pocket
to the person you like.
Let's begin.
Please take it.
If I have a wedding with one of them,
I must go with him.
I want to go alone.
I want you, a human, to take it
so I can do that.
But...
If you won't,
I'll just stick to the original plan.
Please bring your friend.
What?
Who did she pick as her husband again?
She said she wants
to have a wedding with Mr. Koo.
Mr. Koo accepted it,
so they are getting ready now.
Will you be the officiant?
Hyeon-jung,
go to Ms. Fourth Choice right now.
Why?
Are you going to send Mr. Koo
to the afterlife together with the bride?
I don't even know what I'm doing now.
Okay.
Let's just think this is a dream.
This is just a meaningless dream.
Everything will be gone once I wake up.
All right.
I'm just going to have a short dream.
Ms. Jang, are you getting married?
What?
Aren't you the one getting married?
GROOM'S ROOM
I guess I had a dream just now.
Chan-sung.
How dare you decide to get married
without my permission?
Why do I need your permission
when I'm the one getting married?
So are you really going to marry her?
This is why you should have helped her
when she came to you,
saying she didn't want to get married.
Do you think she doesn't
want to get married?
No way. She's a ghost
that is mad about getting married.
The strong desires sealed here
belong to that woman who will never leave
before she gets married.
What a beautiful bride.
I heard there's a wedding
at Hotel del Luna, and I came by.
This is my wedding gift for the bride.
You get married to become happy.
Chan-sung.
I'll save you again.
You don't have to have
the unwanted wedding.
Then what do I do with this?
You said this can't be removed.
We should let her
have a wedding as she wishes.
I'm going to bring her real groom
whom she can never...
leave behind.
This lady is your girlfriend, right?
Your girlfriend is marrying
some other guy.
Hey, that's not funny.
I'm not kidding.
If you want to stop the wedding,
you need to go marry her.
The groom that you actually want to marry,
I brought him here.
We have such a great customer service,
don't we?
It looks like you can finally marry
the person you never got over
even after you died.
You must be
very happy.
He should be here any minute now.
Su-min.
When the wedding is over,
the man will die.
The bride will take her man
to the afterlife with her.
I wonder if Chan-sung noticed.
That's why the man's parents
tried to marry her off to anyone
through a ghost wedding.
The man's parents?
They weren't the bride's parents?
It was the man's parents
who requested to hold the wedding.
They were afraid the woman
would take their son with her.
Su-min is dead.
I can't let you go with her.
Why doesn't it come off?
Su-min, please let my son go. Please...
Please let him go!
Ms. Lee, stop. You shouldn't do this.
Let's be together forever.
Ms. Lee, he's still alive.
Stop right now!
Ms. Lee!
No.
We must stop.
Go back.
What's the matter, Su-min?
Go!
Su-min.
It's hard,
but sometimes it's easier
to let go than hold on.
I love you.
Please be happy.
This place looks cooler than I imagined.
I'll start working
as the manager right away.
You can't yet. We have Mr. Koo.
Then I'll be the intern for now.
Let me start training as an intern.
Listen, friend.
It's getting late.
You should go home to sleep
so you can go to school tomorrow.
Hey.
I'm sorry I used you in such a vulgar way.
I'm sure you haven't survived
since the Tang Dynasty
to be used that way.
Mi-ra.
It's been a while.
I'm here to see Chan-sung.
Thank you for helping me
cut the tie before I leave.
I hope your journey will be comfortable.
Those scissors are
from the third crone, right?
Did she come to my hotel
without me knowing?
He's the one who went to see Mago.
Now the crones are all helping
Chan-sung together?
You're the one that Mago is helping.
He'll be the one to see you off.
I felt proud to see my guests off
at my previous hotel,
but I feel lonely here.
That's because you won't ever see them
again.
Chan-sung.
You're doing a good job.
Mago was right about you.
I get why she likes you.
Did you know I met with her?
She told me to take good care of you,
so that leaves will grow
and flowers will bloom.
You...
Do you still see me in your dreams?
Yes.
I hope you keep it up
and take good care of me
and then...
see me off.
That's what Mago wants.
I'll become your last guest
because you are my cup of tea.
Chan-sung.
When you see me off,
don't feel lonely.
He's not answering his phone.
What did you say?
Your Majesty!
He's dressed like a king of Joseon.
Which one is he?
I'm really worried about you.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because I cannot have you reincarnated
as a dog or a pig.
You could get kicked out at this rate--
You're doing a great job.
One, two, three, we can do it!
I hate being poor.
I'm going to keep eating
caviar and champagne.
He has a girlfriend?
-I have her picture.
-Forget it. Don't tell me.
Why are you telling me that?
Is she pretty?
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu
Chan-sung.
When you see me off,
don't feel lonely.
I hope you keep it up
and take good care of me
and then...
see me off.
That's what Mago wants.
What are you doing?
What?
Do you want me to go right now?
Don't rush it. Now isn't the right time.
Do you really think
I'll leave that easily?
I'll make you feel miserable
and get sick and tired of me.
When I leave,
you'll probably put on a big smile
and feel extremely relieved.
Sir.
You shouldn't be here.
I know you can see me.
You can hear me, right?
Damn it!
Please don't spit on me.
Stop it.
How drunk is he?
I don't think he's drunk.
-I think he's just crazy.
-Sir!
-My goodness.
-There are so many weird people.
Calm down and follow me.
-My gosh.
-Poor thing.
Hey, be quiet. Let's not provoke him.
I bought you beer like I promised.
Thank you.
Go to the hotel I told you about
once you're done with the beer.
You'll be able to find it
if you follow the moon.
Okay.
-I can't believe this.
-This is so cool.
-My gosh, look at him.
-Kim Jun-hyun?
It's a sausage.
Welcome.
That's 1,800 won.
-It's really him.
-He's really fat.
I'm a fan of yours.
Are you shooting something nearby?
I really like it when you take
those huge one bites on your show.
-I can't believe it's him.
-Gosh, look.
-He's coming.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-I'm a huge fan.
-Thank you.
Can I please get an autograph?
-Now is not the time to follow...
-This is so cool.
I can't believe
he's even popular among ghosts.
This restaurant was
on The Guys Who Died After Eating.
Kim Jun-hyun...
He ate five balls of sticky rice cake
at once.
That guy. He's not an ordinary man.
Jang Man-wol likes him too.
-I got the leg.
-You need to put that in.
-Yes.
-My goodness.
You're only going to have
the webfoot octopus?
Yes.
Ms. Fourth Choice came by today,
and she's very clever.
She volunteered to intern here.
Why don't we let her do that?
Let her do what she wants.
Then I'll put Hyeon-jung
in charge of training her.
I'll make sure he teaches her well
so she can take over right away
as soon as Mr. Koo quits.
By the way, did Chan-sung leave?
Yes, he took the afternoon off today
and went home early.
One bite!
KIM JUN-HYUN ATTEMPTS TO EAT
EVERYTHING IN ONE BITE
Are you craving that food?
Should I have the intern go buy some?
No.
I don't really crave anything today.
Did you
find this?
No.
I thought I lost it.
Is finding it worth another leaf?
If I want to show him these,
I should start craving
the webfoot octopus.
Hello? Hey, Man-wol.
Chan-sung? He's not home yet.
He's not answering his phone.
Once he comes home, tell him to wait
for me. Tell him I'll be picking him up
in my poop colored car.
Man-wol, Chan-sung
might come home late tonight.
What? Why?
His girlfriend came by today.
What did you just say?
She's the girl he used to date
back when he was in the States.
She came to my house to meet Chan-sung.
But they must be meeting outside.
My gosh, you startled me.
Are you already here?
Chan-sung has a girlfriend?
Who is she? Is she pretty?
-Well--
-Forget it. Don't tell me.
Why are you telling me that?
I never said I was curious.
I'm not interested. At all.
-See you.
-But I haven't said anything yet.
If you want to tell me so badly, go ahead.
I'll hear you out.
Is she pretty?
I just asked if she's pretty.
Yes, she's pretty. She's pretty.
Sanchez.
You really are slow-witted.
You know nothing, do you?
You're so stupid.
Is she...
that pretty?
Yes, she's really pretty. She's smart too.
And she and Chan-sung make a great couple.
I have her picture. You want to see it?
I'll go find it. Wait here.
If she really turns out to be pretty,
I'll kill you, Sanchez.
Man-wol, look.
Man-wol? Did she leave?
I wonder if Chan-sung's late
because he met Mi-ra.
Their connection has lasted
for a very long time.
I hope he takes good care of her,
so that she doesn't end up
getting hurt again.
-Unbelievable.
-This is incredible.
When is Kim Jun-hyun coming?
My gosh, this is cool.
Excuse me.
Are they shooting
The Guys Who Died After Eating here?
Yes, are you also here
to get Kim Jun-hyun's autograph?
A person I know is a fan of his.
-His girlfriend is a fan of his.
-My mom is a huge fan.
My dad is a fan.
My boss is a fan. She likes him a lot.
Hey, you guys.
He's over there giving out his autographs.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Sir, you should come.
Maybe I should've gotten his autograph.
She would've liked it.
Jang Man-wol?
What are you doing here?
Did you know that I was here?
I heard.
Did you meet?
Well, yes. Kind of.
You must've been so happy.
So how was it?
A lot leaner than I thought.
With a small face and great skin.
Why don't you go see for yourself?
I'm sure he's still there. Let's go.
Forget it. Why would I?
I came out to eat webfoot octopus.
Webfoot octopus?
You want to eat webfoot octopus
dressed like that at this late hour?
That's right. Webfoot octopus.
That's the only reason I'm here.
That's the earring I found.
Oh, yes.
I bought these to wear them
when I go out to eat webfoot octopus.
I'm headed to eat webfoot octopus
since I found these earrings.
You must come with me
because you found it.
You're just craving webfoot octopus.
Stop coming up with excuses
that make no sense.
Why? Are you sick and tired of me?
You can't stand me anymore?
If you want to eat webfoot octopus now,
we should go to Noryangjin.
Actually, no.
The west coast is famous for them.
You want to go to the sea?
Well, okay.
And we can see the sunrise too
while we're there.
I'm not sure
if we can see it on the west coast.
But let's go.
Sure.
We'll take that poop colored car you love.
Let's go have some webfoot octopus.
Yes, let's go.
By the way, are you sure
you don't want to see Kim Jun-hyun?
Kim Jun-hyun?
How can I see him?
Didn't you come here to see him?
He's filming something over there.
Darn it. Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Oh, she can run.
Jang Man-wol!
Those are the bowls of hangover soup
he ate here today.
I heard he was chosen again today
for Eat At Once.
I can't believe I missed it.
That's where Kim Jun-hyun sat,
so settle for having
the hangover soup there.
Eat before it gets cold.
Then why don't you show me
how much you can eat in one bite?
With some radish kimchi. Slurp it all in.
Don't overestimate me, please.
I'll enjoy this, in many bites.
This restaurant will do very well
now that Kim Jun-hyun has dined here.
This restaurant would've done fine
even without Kim Jun-hyun.
Because of her.
What about that baby?
She brings a lot of luck to this place.
She was born
with a tremendous amount of luck,
because of all the good karma
she built in her past lives.
Any family with such a child
becomes successful in no time.
You can be born with a lot of luck
when you do many good deeds.
Then in the opposite case...
You're either born dirt poor
or as a dog or a pig.
Then if you're reincarnated...
What? You just thought
I'd totally be reincarnated
as a dog or a pig, didn't you?
I'm not sure, but to be honest,
I am worried
because it's highly likely.
I've already paid for all my sins
by running the hotel
for over a millennium.
But it's not like you've treated
all the guests that well.
How could I have treated them better?
You ignored some of them,
saying they're nuisances.
And you took money
from the rich ones to buy booze
and cars for yourself.
I'm really worried about you.
It's none of your concern.
It is. I should be concerned.
I don't want you to be born
as a dog or a pig.
Gosh, it is none of your business!
Imagine you being reincarnated as a pig.
I don't want to meet you again
as hangover soup.
Be nice.
I don't want this anymore.
I lost my appetite because of you.
I saw a ghost
wandering around the area earlier.
I told him to go to the hotel,
but you should take him
since you're here anyway.
Be nice to him.
Chan-sung.
You always go talk to ghosts
you don't even know.
You really shouldn't.
They could be evil ghosts.
It's dangerous.
Does wandering around for a long time
make them evil ghosts?
Any wandering ghost turns evil
whenever it harms humans.
And such a ghost
can devour all other souls,
let alone living humans.
If it's caught by the Grim Reaper,
it certainly won't be reincarnated
as a lucky child or even as an animal.
Its soul will be perished on the spot.
Why didn't you report to me
that this room's guest left the hotel?
It was due to our human manager's mistake.
What can we do? She left the hotel.
Her soul is filled with hatred
and resentment toward humans.
If she causes any trouble
in the outside world,
I will hold the hotel accountable.
What a headache.
The Grim Reaper will manage to catch her
and bring her back.
If she causes trouble before she's caught
and turns into an evil ghost,
we'll be doomed.
She's a dangerous one,
but I feel so bad for her.
I hope the guest from Room 13
returns safely.
HOT NEW RELEASES. ENJOY.
Shall I take a quick break?
REAL HOT STUFF
What's this?
She's taking her clothes off.
Turn around. Let me see your face.
Are you enjoying this?
You like this?
I'm hot, aren't I?
ARE YOU GOING TO PICK ME UP AGAIN TODAY?
WHEN WILL YOU BE HERE?
I CAN SKIP THE AFTERNOON CLASSES
How dare a ghost ignore my messages?
I'm telling you. Yu-na is possessed.
I got goosebumps all over that day.
-How about I throw this at her?
-Good idea, try it.
Let's see what happens.
-All right, here I go.
-Do it.
Just a second.
-Did you get a text?
-No, it's not me.
-It's not me either.
-Same here.
I didn't get anything either.
-What is this, then?
-What's going on?
Other girls hate her so much.
I'M HERE BEHIND YOU
I got Ms. Jang's permission
that you can come to the hotel.
All right. Let's go there now, then.
Now? But what about your classes?
Didn't you see earlier?
I'm struggling to fit in anyway.
I might as well quit school.
It's because of the friends
that bully you, right?
They're quite annoying, but it's fine.
The real Kim Yu-na was a bad girl.
I'm actually enjoying seeing
how much Yu-na
is hated by others.
It's just that school is boring.
Why do you think school is boring?
I had so much fun
back when I was in school.
I studied and played sports.
I always came home so late from school
that the chief servant
had to come to get me.
"Chief servant"?
Yes, he was the chief servant in my house.
He was in a relationship
with my sister's nanny.
I remember he always fought
with my dad's driver.
They were in a love triangle.
A chief servant, a nanny,
and a driver too?
I guess you were a son of a nobleman
when you were alive.
You were born
with a golden spoon in your mouth.
No, it was a silver spoon.
All of the spoons at my house were silver.
You were born into a rich family
with a silver spoon in your mouth,
but you must've been disappointed
to have lived a short life.
Yes. I am so disappointed
that I can't seem to let it go.
I can't even go to school
even if I wanted to,
so try to have a better time at school.
Schools these days are so nice.
You guys wear nice school uniforms.
And you have a great piano like this one.
This piano is better
than the one at my house.
Well,
it sounds like you learned
how to play piano too.
Play it.
I don't know how to play it,
but I'll listen to it if you play.
I've probably forgotten everything.
Come on, rich boy. Play the piano.
Who are you talking to now?
What are you talking about?
I was playing the piano.
Sure. Play it then.
Go ahead, Yu-na.
You're good at playing the piano.
Play the piano.
-See?
-I was right.
Hey, she can really play.
You're pretty good, rich boy.
See? You didn't forget it.
I guess not.
I can't seem to forget this.
Hyeon-jung!
Will you ride the bicycle with me
even when you're grown up, Hyeon-mi?
Yes!
You have to ride it with me.
You made a promise to me.
Young Master! Over here!
Young Lady!
Don't you think it's better
if I train Ms. Fourth Choice?
Hyeon-jung is too young for this.
I'm sure she'll see more eye to eye
with Hyeon-jung,
who had been educated in the modern times.
You're too old for her.
However, Hyeon-jung is
leaning toward Mr. Third Choice.
Emotionally,
he's bonding more with Mr. Koo.
But he has a reason to stay in this world.
He knows that the hotel might disappear,
so I doubt that he will side with Mr. Koo.
You're right. He has to stay at the hotel
until that day.
I'm glad
that there aren't more changes
after the leaves grew out.
What's going on?
Ms. Jang must be angry.
But she's with Mr. Koo now.
I guess Mr. Third Choice
must have gotten her riled up.
I hope she burns with rage
so the leaves fall off the branches.
We must sell off the cars you don't need.
I need every single car here.
You said you didn't drive seven
of these fourteen cars at all last year.
They are decorating my parking lot.
Look.
I've put these beautiful cars
in the same color.
And these cars are working hard
to make my parking lot look pretty.
This is a huge space.
Imagine there are only three cars
in this big space.
That will look so empty.
That's exactly my point.
There's only one owner.
It makes no sense to have
such a huge parking lot like this.
Select only three cars
and park them near the storage.
And we can utilize this space
for our hotel guests.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why do you want me to sell off my cars?
Because your finances are a mess.
You'll go bankrupt at this rate.
MANAGER KOO CHAN-SUNG
It will be difficult to pay off
your next month's card bills
with the balance we have now.
What about the painting?
No one is buying.
It's not as wanted as I expected.
The gold bars from Kim Yu-na's parents.
You already bought a car with those.
Right. What about the black card?
I sent it back.
You have to pay for the things
you bought for the wedding.
Have you gone mad?
Why would you send that back?
Because I cannot have you reincarnated
as a dog or a pig.
I won't help you extort money
from people anymore.
Be kind and cut down on your spending.
Hey, Chan-sung.
You have nothing to lose.
What if I get reincarnated
as a dog or a pig?
I'm fine if I get reincarnated
as a chicken.
Even if I meet you again
as a bowl of chicken noodles,
I can say, "Hello, I'm tastier
when you eat me with fresh kimchi."
I'll say hello to you like this.
I mean it.
If you don't sell off your cars
and settle your bills,
you won't even have money
to buy chicken noodles next month.
Will I be poor again?
Oh, no. I hate being broke.
Chan-sung, you're lying, right?
You're just trying to scare me, right?
Ms. Jang wasn't always well-off.
When I came to the hotel,
things were rough.
Back then, things were really tough.
As things were chaotic,
we didn't have a human manager.
Ms. Jang went through a lot.
I would kill for a bowl of makgeolli
and radish kimchi.
When the US Army truck passes by later,
I'll try to get some food.
The newbie can speak English
since he was educated recently.
MAN-WOL HOSTEL
You're pretty good.
I'll keep you.
I hate being poor.
I'm going to keep eating
caviar and champagne.
When she didn't have enough money,
she managed to get by
with kimchi and makgeolli.
I should push her even more.
Then, Ms. Jang will hate you.
You could get kicked out at this rate--
You're doing a great job.
You're truly loyal to her.
I can take care of her current finances.
But can the hotel be
in a financial problem?
When there was a war,
a tremendous number of people died.
And none of them died
without regrets and grudges in this world.
But when that happened,
the door to the afterlife opened wide,
so not that many souls came to our hotel.
We managed to get past
that difficult time together.
You did very well too, Mr. Kim.
You were the one
who had the most difficult time.
Let's not be picky with our guests
and protect our hotel the best we can
until the day we resolve
our sorrows and grudges.
Here.
One, two, three.
We can do it.
Your Majesty.
It is well into the night.
Who's there?
Stand back...
Cut!
Mr. Yu, shouldn't the king
sound more solemn?
-I'm sorry.
-We'll take a short break.
You should sound like a king.
Work on it, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
My gosh!
How dare you! How dare...
Who's there?
What a relief.
How dare you!
-Who are you?
-Such insolence! Make way!
-Wasn't it Yu O?
-Yu O!
-My gosh.
-Yu O?
-Yu O!
-Wake up.
-Please wake up.
-Can you hear us?
-Do something.
-Wake up!
-Contact his manager. Hurry!
-Goodness.
-Yu O, wake up.
-Mr. Yu!
Why isn't there anyone who can hear me?
Yu O, come back to us.
Welcome!
A king?
How dare you!
Ms. Choe, what's happening?
A VVIP has come to our hotel.
"A VVIP"?
A king has come to our hotel.
I was never able to see one while I lived,
but now I get the chance.
A big score has entered the hotel.
Gather everyone.
We'll provide the VVIP
with the best service
and have him thoroughly satisfied.
Your Majesty!
It's an honor to accommodate
someone of your status.
I am the owner of this hotel,
Jang Man-wol.
A king?
Tae, Jeong, Tae, Se, Mun, Dan, Se.
Which King could he be?
You must be exhausted.
Allow me to escort you to your room.
Your Majesty,
we have brought you your meal.
This...
It's a chamber pot.
I know he won't need to use it,
but I thought
it'll bring him some comfort.
That is very considerate of you.
Now that I've served the king,
I wouldn't even mind dying...
Well, I'm already dead,
but that's just how delighted I am.
Your Majesty.
I don't want our energy disrupted here,
so don't accept any more new guests.
Tell them to come back
after the king leaves.
Yes, ma'am.
Jang Man-wol.
You shouldn't refuse our guests like this.
Well, I can.
I'm busy here, so go home
if you're going to nag me.
He's dressed like a king of Joseon.
Which one is he?
Some were tyrants, you know.
Nonsense! He didn't seem evil.
Then did he seem generous and wise?
Well...
Why are you nitpicking again?
What's wrong this time?
You must be clueless.
Well, it's understandable. It must be
your first time to serve a king guest.
Have you served one
while working at a hotel then?
Of course.
I've served a few members
of Dubai's royal family.
So?
Are you seriously bragging about it?
-That's not it--
-Enough.
Then you don't know jack.
Dismissed!
Chan-sung,
the painting of Baekdu Mountain...
Sell it at half price.
Don't come to work until you do.
They're just too excited
because of the king.
His Majesty's presence
will make the flowers bloom in the garden.
Making sure he rests well
before leaving for the afterlife
is most important.
Ms. Jang!
I had him sign the hotel register.
HOTEL REGISTER
So his name is Yi Hyeon.
"Yi Hyeon"?
Which King was Yi Hyeon?
It sounds somewhat familiar.
Let me see.
Han Suk-kyu played Yi Do,
Lee Seo-jin played Yi San,
-and Kim Soo-hyun played Yi Hwon.
-Soo-hyun doesn't count.
It was a character
made up for that particular series.
Right, a fusion historical drama.
I'm aware of that.
So who's Yi Hyeon? Did you look it up?
I found him.
Right? I knew he existed.
He's a character from a TV series.
Let me see that.
The Crowned Queen?
Oh, that's right.
The king from this series
goes by the name Yi Hyeon.
He is a king!
Yi Hyeon is just like
Yi Hwon from earlier.
He's a TV character
from a fusion historical drama.
What?
The Crowned Queen is about a queen
who hires a kisaeng who looks similar
to take her place in the palace
in order to stay safe.
Yi Hyeon is the name of the king
who is her husband.
Then who is that king that just came in?
Why does he say he is Yi Hyeon?
The guest who came to the hotel is
the actor Bang Tae-u.
The actor Bang Tae-u has
mostly played minor roles
and supporting roles.
The first leading role he had
was the role of King Yi Hyeon.
However, sadly,
before the filming even started,
he had a cardiac arrest while working out.
He died suddenly.
You mean he is not really a king.
He was an actor who put his soul
into acting to take
the role of a king.
The way he talked and walked
was perfectly like a king.
He died while he was
so immersed in the role.
I believe he thinks he is a real king.
This is so embarrassing.
After we serve him breakfast tomorrow,
send him off
to the afterlife.
I heard he was not a king.
You should have recognized it right away
when I voiced my suspicions.
Good for you.
I didn't send back the guests
who had come, just in case.
You see, I handled it very wisely.
I said, good for you!
When I saw him earlier,
there was a small scar on his face.
You didn't see it, right?
It was impossible for a king
to have a scar on his face
in Joseon Dynasty.
You know Deposed Queen Lady Yun, right?
You should know since you love dramas.
I know her. She was Prince Gwanghae's mom.
It was Prince Yeonsan's.
You should have checked which king he was.
I thought you felt the energy of ghosts.
But you were fooled by an actor.
It looked so real.
Do you know he put his soul
into his acting?
Think about it.
He must have wanted that role so badly
that he thinks he's a king
even after he died.
Why do you look down on a ghost
giving such a performance?
How dare you? Who do you think you are?
I am
just saying I recognized
that he wasn't a king.
If a guest says he is a king,
a hotelier should treat him like one.
Whether he is Mansour
or a king from a drama.
The guests in our hotel are all kings!
Since when did she ever treat
our guests like kings?
YU O IS SUCH A BAD ACTOR.
I'M SICK OF YU'S TERRIBLE ACTING.
A popular star took up the role,
and his acting is terrible.
He is being criticized so much.
If he acted that role,
he would've performed
as if he was possessed.
Performing as if he was possessed...
Would that be possible?
I repented a lot after talking to you.
When you said guests were our kings,
I was also moved.
Then you should work harder in the future.
So I've been thinking.
If the guest wants to act,
we have to help him realize his wishes.
We hoteliers
will help our guests become kings
if that is what they want.
Whether that is Mansour
or a king from a drama.
One more time.
We need to upload it online.
Show how tasty it is.
Okay, one, two, three.
Yu O's fan club hired Sanchez's restaurant
to send a pizza truck to the filming set.
So we were able to get into the set
easily.
What's the use of giving
a "possessed" performance?
It's not like that his face
will be on screen.
I should be able to act
like I'm possessed after eating this...
-I'll do better.
-It's okay. Thanks for the pizza.
Tell him we'll leave
after he looks around the set
and the staff have some pizza.
Ms. Jang.
It's what the guest wants.
He's really looking forward to it.
-Hoteliers should--
-Hey!
Stop. I get it.
Look after the pizza truck.
I'll go get the shooting schedule.
FOOD TRUCK STAFF
THE CROWNED QUEEN
Excuse me. Food Truck lady?
Please take five pizzas
to our costumes staff.
Thank you.
Stop there.
Hey.
This is not a delivery truck.
If they want to eat,
they should come and get it themselves.
Okay.
How impertinent.
ENJOY THE PIZZA
AND ACT LIKE YOU'RE POSSESSED
If he could only act well...
Sir, it's me, Yu O.
Did you talk to the writer
about me not filming those scenes?
I am skipping the last two weeks, right?
I don't care about the plot of the drama.
It's not my concern.
Just tell them my injury is serious.
It's so uncomfortable.
How can the woman
become a queen when there is no king?
The money I'll get paid?
I don't need that few hundred million won.
I just want out.
Few hundred million won?
I don't care if you tell them I'm dead.
You can tell them Yu O is dead.
I can't do this.
Wait a minute.
Even if his face is not seen,
he still can get paid.
The king doesn't appear
as much as I thought.
He only has one scene. Let's help him.
With this one scene,
he will have to show how he can act
like he's possessed.
How did Scene 17 end?
-Then we can go from here.
-Hurry up.
We're starting.
"My queen, you are the only one
I've ever loved." What?
I'm really bad.
What am I going to do?
"You are the only one..."
The Queen?
I must ask her to help me.
Hello, Queen.
Queen, can you do this with me?
Ms. Queen.
Queen.
Can you go over the script with me?
The director gets so annoyed with me.
Please help me.
Scene 42 is an emotional scene.
Oh, my goodness.
Who are you?
Look me in the eye, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty?
What is it, my Queen?
You are the king of all the people
living in this country.
I am.
I am Yi Hyeon, the king of this country.
Your Majesty.
I am a fake.
I am not the queen.
Is that why you wanted to leave my side?
If I stay with you,
you will be in danger.
If you hide in the mountains,
I will cut down all the trees to find you.
If you go to the seas,
I will dry up the sea and stop you.
Your Majesty.
I command you as your king.
Don't leave me alone.
Cut! Okay!
Gosh, that was great!
You were amazing.
My Queen.
That was incredible!
You did great!
-This is great, isn't it?
-You did an amazing job!
-What just happened?
-What?
Are we done?
Great job!
You were amazing, Your Majesty.
His Majesty arrives!
Do not
talk to me about dethroning the Queen.
Your Majesty, Her Majesty is
a woman of lowly status.
She cannot maintain
the dignity of the royal family.
Please consider her dethronement,
Your Majesty!
How dare you?
Our guest agreed to help him act
until the drama ends?
Let's see.
Yes, apparently so.
Why? I thought she wanted to send him off.
His face might not appear on TV
even if he acts,
but she'll gain something else.
My gosh, this is unbelievable.
After I went over my lines with you,
I suddenly acted like I was possessed.
You know what I mean, right?
I felt like I was possessed
by someone else when I acted.
By any chance, are you an acting teacher?
Do you want
to keep this up?
Of course. Please do me a favor
and continue to help me out.
Then...
let's start negotiating your pay.
My pay?
Oh, sure. I guess you already know.
You can take everything.
How much do you get paid for each episode?
I get paid 120 million won,
and there are 4 episodes for 2 weeks.
So, 4 times 120 million won is
480 million won in total.
I guess that will be enough
to rent a house.
Go ahead and take everything.
It's fine with me.
Our guest is getting paid for his acting,
and he's agreed to this.
So I have no objections.
Hey, I didn't know actors
got paid that much money.
Chan-sung,
how about you start a career in acting?
I don't know how to act.
I'm a horrible actor.
I guess you're right.
I can tell that you'll be bad at it.
So, tell me.
You told me that I don't even have
enough money to buy myself
a bowl of chicken noodles.
But that was a lie, wasn't it?
It's true that your loan is overdue.
But I lied about the chicken noodles.
You have enough money for webfoot octopus.
Oh, right. Webfoot octopus.
I couldn't eat that because of you.
Yes, you're right. It's all my fault.
I'll forgive you
since you know you're at fault.
Then let's go to the west coast.
We might get lucky and see the sunrise.
We can also eat webfoot octopus.
What's going on?
Why are you being so nice?
Are you suddenly being nice to me
because I told you
I'm going to be your last guest?
"We'll give you everything you want."
Gosh, what an incredible hotelier.
I'm not that incredible.
Hoteliers aren't supposed to have
personal feelings for their guests.
What?
What kind of personal feelings
do you have for me?
The leaf.
You showed me that I got two leaves.
How do you expect me to ignore that?
Let's not go today.
I had too much champagne.
We can have the webfoot octopus tomorrow.
I need to go to the filming set tomorrow.
You don't need to go there.
I hired an intern for you.
THE CROWNED QUEEN
You're the intern?
Yes.
Feel free to quit whenever you wish.
I'll take your place.
You should be in school.
I'm planning to stay in school.
I'm doing it for someone
who used to love going to school.
School's over today,
so I can go with you, right?
I can't find the hotel on my own
during the day.
Let's go next time.
I have to meet someone here.
Who are you meeting?
A ghost?
No, it's a human being.
I'm meeting a friend.
I'm not interested in humans.
See you later.
I clearly told them to put a space
between "take" and "out."
-Thank you for the food.
-No problem.
I heard you're Man-wol's relative.
You should come often.
Okay.
Hey, Mi-ra.
Chan-sung's waiting for you inside.
Go on in.
I thought he was meeting a friend.
But I guess he meant his girlfriend.
It's been a while.
Yes, it has.
Where are you going, Ms. Jang?
You look like you're in a good mood.
Yes, I'm going to the beach.
The beach? There's a beach in our hotel.
You can't compare that to a real beach.
How is it different?
Our beach is...
Webfoot octopus.
There's no webfoot octopus here.
I'm on my way to eat that.
Should I ask Yu-na to get you some?
No, I want to eat it there.
Gosh, it'll be great
if Mr. Koo can drive you there.
Should I call him?
There's no need. He'll be here.
You're right.
We shouldn't call him to hurry
when he's with his girlfriend.
Yu-na apparently saw her.
I heard she's really pretty.
Mr. Koo's always around ghosts,
so he should meet a lot of humans
when he can.
If he ends up growing old
all by himself just like Mr. No did,
I'd feel so sorry for him.
Ms. Jang, I hope you eat
a lot of delicious food at the beach.
Hyeon-jung.
Tell the guests to empty
the hotel beach within 30 minutes.
I want to take a rest there.
I thought you were going to go
to a beach far away.
Why would I go?
They're all the same anyway.
I'm...
not going.
Should I buy you some webfoot octopus?
You acted like you were never
going to come back to Korea.
But here you are.
Are you nervous to see me here
since it was so unexpected?
I'm just glad to see you.
I found it weird
that you suddenly showed up,
so I asked around.
I heard you took out a loan
and your parents kicked you out.
It was only a small amount.
I'm a doctor.
I'm going to pay it off soon.
Is that so? That's good to hear.
I don't have much time,
so let's cut to the chase.
I want my 5,000 dollars back.
It's been ages since we last met.
Let's not talk about money.
I'm talking about money
because it's been a long time.
Otherwise, I would've sued you.
I don't believe you.
I know how much you loved me.
You'll never sue me.
Yes. When you told me
your family was in a pickle
and asked me to lend you 5,000 dollars,
I liked you so much that I even gave you
money from my tuition.
Chan-sung.
Try to remember
how much you liked me back then.
First, let me calculate
how much you need to pay me back.
Gosh, I'll pay you back.
But I actually called you
because I really missed you.
It's so nice to see you again.
I guess you're still hopeless.
And it's still charming, isn't it?
Okay, fine.
That's enough. You have a bad stomach.
You haven't changed either.
Chan-sung, I heard you're single.
Just a second.
Excuse me!
Wait!
-Yes?
-Mr. Kim Jun-hyun.
Yes?
Can I get an autograph?
Sure.
You must have run here.
Wait. Let me borrow your back.
-My back?
-Yes. It has to be flat.
What's your name?
-It's Jang Man-wol.
-Jang Man-wol.
She's a huge fan.
Thank her for me. What a great name.
Okay.
Bye.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Can we take a photo too?
She doesn't trust people easily.
She doesn't trust people? I see.
Sure, let's take one.
People take photos these days.
How should I pose? All right.
One, two, three.
MS. JANG
I was just about to call you.
-I just met someone.
-Chan-sung.
Take the day off. Don't come.
What about our trip to the sea?
I can go to the sea at the hotel too.
It's all the same, anyway.
I don't have to go. Take the day off.
TO MS. JANG MAN-WOL, I LOVE YOU
You're here.
How did you find me here?
Yeon-u told me.
You should have told me first
if you found a good place like this.
Don't keep it to yourself.
It's a good place to drink alone.
Get lost.
Now do you realize
the view's got better than earlier?
They are just fireflies.
What's got better?
Of course it's better.
Earlier, you were alone.
But now, I'm here with you.
Every sight you see with me
will look different.
From now on, drinking alone here
won't make you happy.
Mark my words.
You'll be waiting for me
to suddenly show up like today.
The tree I'm growing
at Guest House of the Moon
used to be as stiff as a rock.
But it's starting to look pretty now.
I guess the man you sent is taking
good care of the tree.
You sent him there
because you thought he was the remedy,
but he might turn out to be poison.
Love can be one's remedy and poison.
That's how it is.
But it's so hard to weave them together.
Darn it. It's tangled again.
Darn it. What should I do?
Darn it. Goodness.
RICH BOY, DO YOU WANT
TO GRAB A SANDWICH WITH ME?
No. Asking a ghost to have
a sandwich with me sounds weird.
What should I say?
What was that?
That felt really creepy just now.
HEY, ANYTHING FUN THESE DAYS?
SOMEBODY, SEND ME SOME FUN STUFF
HERE
IT'S GOING VIRAL.
BUT IF YOU'RE SCARED, DON'T OPEN IT.
IT'S THE FAMOUS VIDEO? I DIDN'T WATCH IT.
He's trying to scare me.
Are you enjoying this?
You like this?
I'm hot, aren't I?
Ms. Jang is on the beach by herself?
Yes, she told me not to let anyone in.
Is this Weather Control Department?
I'm on the beach now.
The sun is too strong now!
I don't want 12 p.m.
How about around 6 p.m.?
Change the setting to sundown.
Whether the sun is blazing or goes down,
the beach looks the same.
I should ask them
to make the waves stronger.
The beach will still look the same.
Why are you here?
You refused to go to the beach with me.
Because...
I found it silly.
Silly?
You and your capricious mind.
I told you to rest.
What are you doing here?
I did something silly,
but I can't tell you what I did
because you might laugh at me.
What did you do?
-Don't laugh.
-I'm not in the mood. What is it?
TO MS. JANG MAN-WOL, I LOVE YOU.
Doesn't it make you happy?
"To Ms. Jang Man-wol, I love you"?
Are you confessing your love to me?
No! I didn't write this.
This is Kim Jun-hyun's autograph.
Here, "Kim Jun-hyun."
Kim Jun-hyun?
It's true.
I ran after him and asked him
for an autograph on the streets
even though I was so embarrassed.
I thought it'd make you happy.
Are you not happy?
I am.
I love this.
I knew you'd like it.
I felt so shy
about asking for an autograph.
It turns out this beach is as nice
as somewhere far.
Although there's no webfoot octopus here.
That's okay.
Because you're here.
The sea looks really beautiful.
Yes, indeed.
It makes me sad.
I'm...
a little sad.
Because the sea...
looks more beautiful now...
than it did earlier.
Since you can see my past,
you'll gradually find out
how much of a horrible person I was.
You can't do this here, sir.
Just leave him be.
Kill her as much as you want
until you feel better.
Now... Pick one.
Lee Mi-ra.
I invited you to the hotel.
It's not a place you can come in a dream.
You can come only when you're dead.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu