Hotel Del Luna Blu-ray Disc 8
Subtitle re-timing by Jharel
If I knew Ms. Jang was never
going to come back here,
I should've at least said goodbye to her.
It's good that she was able to leave
after she got rid
of her old, deep grudges.
Let's not forget to say goodbye
to each other before we leave.
Don't leave without saying anything.
I'm serious.
Promise me.
You too.
But what do you think is
going to happen to this hotel?
As always, the Grim Reaper
didn't give us a straight answer.
But it seems like Mago is getting ready
to welcome a new owner.
I should let this sit to ferment
until the next full moon.
Now, I just need to add
the most important ingredient,
the Moon Flower.
Oh, dear.
We're out of Moon Flowers.
I heard you asked your sister
at the chemist's shop
to start making a new batch of wine
for the new owner
of the Guest House of the Moon.
The wine is currently being fermented.
It will taste bitter and horrible
to someone who holds a deep grudge.
When Man-wol first drank that wine,
she told me that she'd like
to pluck out my tongue.
Whoever drinks that wine
will be influenced
by the power of the moon
and will no longer be
a part of life or death.
The Moon Tree will suck in
their remaining life
and replace the body.
And the person's soul will be tied
down to the Moon Tree
and become the owner
of the Guest House of the Moon.
The wine will be ready
by the next full moon.
But we're out of the most important
ingredient, the Moon Flower.
I'll look for them.
Where can I find them?
They only bloom in the garden
of the Guest House of the Moon.
But there's not a single flower here.
But I do recall seeing a flower bloom
at the garden that existed 200 years ago.
Then I should go to the Guest House
of the Moon that existed 200 years ago.
You don't need to go.
I'll send someone else there.
You came to work early again.
I just wanted to check
if she came back.
I have something for you, Mr. Koo.
I heard this medicine will get rid
of your ability to see ghosts.
Ms. Jang
once asked me for a favor.
If you think
Chan-sung should no longer come here
anymore,
I want you to give him this.
Why are you giving that to me?
I'm giving it to you just in case
because I trust you the most.
Up until now,
I trusted that she would come back.
But now,
I think...
it's time to give you this.
I guess you think
that she isn't going to return.
Ms. Jang has left this medicine for you
because she wanted you
to start living in reality,
instead of staying here
where she no longer exists.
Chan-sung.
Ta-da.
Guess what I'm about to go eat.
God, you have no clue at all.
It's obviously rice with thistle.
This is thistle,
the white part is rice, the sauce,
and the spoon.
Okay?
Let's go.
Oh, wait. My phone.
I have to take pictures.
Why are you staring at me like that?
You're way too naughty.
What is this?
Did you bring
those special service requests again?
Okay, fine. Bring those to me.
Give me those.
What will a ghost have to do
in the bedroom all night long?
I can just work
and look into other people's dream calls.
Harvard? What do they teach there?
Do they only make you study?
I don't even want to see you. Leave.
Chan-sung, once you leave our hotel,
you'll become an even greater person
than Hwang Mun-suk.
You'll live long,
and you'll become very rich too.
This hotel guarantees it.
But you can't show off like that already.
Hey.
What are you staring at?
Is Jang Man-wol here?
I have to ask you to do something.
What is it?
You have to stop by Man-wol Inn.
Man-wol Inn?
Isn't that Del Luna's name
in the Joseon Dynasty?
You're right. You need to go there for me.
In the garden of Man-wol Inn,
you'll find medicinal flowers
that shine under the moonlight.
You can bring some of them to me.
It's not a big deal.
You can go there yourself.
Why are you asking me to do it?
Because I thought you might like it.
If you go there,
you can get a good look
at the old Man-wol Inn.
Then will I get to meet
Jang Man-wol of that time?
Probably.
If you don't want to do it,
then forget it.
I'll do it.
I'll go.
Once you go around the tree,
you'll see the entrance to Man-wol Inn.
You can return the opposite way.
Once you get there,
do not eat or drink anything.
If you do, you won't be able to return.
MAN-WOL INN
You're the one
who ratted on me, aren't you?
I just told the truth. What now?
You couldn't just die alone, huh?
-No, I couldn't!
-Kill me again, and see what happens!
-Do you really want to die?
-Yes! Kill me!
-That's Ms. Choe.
-Darn you!
-You little...
-Please don't do this.
Please calm down and come this way.
My goodness.
Excuse me, is this the liquor
for Madam Jang?
Yes.
I cannot believe how much she's drinking.
That's Mr. Kim.
Who goes there?
You are alive. How did you get in here?
Are you here to steal?
You are dressed oddly.
Where are you from?
Jang Man-wol...
How do you know my name?
Are you...
Oh from Dangyong sent you here, right?
You probably came here
after you saw the IOU I gave him.
Go and tell Oh Chung-hwan
that I will be there myself
in a month to pay him back.
I came from a place
much further than that.
You cannot
recognize me at this moment.
You can
see ghosts.
Who gave you that ability?
Man-wol!
-Darn it.
-I came back for you!
-You came again.
-I didn't even die
-and came back.
-Madam Jang isn't here.
-What's wrong?
-I came yesterday,
I'm here today,
and I'll come tomorrow too.
Damn it, that lousy old hag.
She's here again.
Man-wol, I'm here again.
Isn't that Mago?
Bring some rice!
-You know her?
-We don't have any.
Yes.
I've met her five other sisters so far.
But I haven't met her.
Are you close to Mago?
Her sisters treated me nicely.
Is that so?
Do you want a drink?
You've probably just started working here.
Yes, it's been less than two years.
This drink is from this world.
It's been a while
since we had a living guest.
Don't you have a human manager?
"A manager"?
You must mean a human steward.
He died a short while ago
so we don't have any at the moment.
Are you the new steward
brought in by Mago?
No, I'm not.
She mistook me
for someone Oh from Dangyong sent.
Who is that?
Dangyong is the gambling den,
and Oh is the money lender.
Gambling den...
Does Jang Man-wol gamble?
After the death of the human steward
who took care of her for a long time,
we thought she went out at nights
because she was feeling empty.
But it turned out that she was gambling.
What should I do?
I'm all in.
If you are scared, just croak.
-I'm all in.
-Here's my house deed.
Okay, show me.
This is good enough.
Wait!
I'm sorry about this.
How much is all this?
She worked with a ghost gambler.
So she raked in all the money at first.
Then Mago found out about it.
After that,
the Mago who brings in poverty,
comes here every day.
So Man-wol's storeroom is about
to be completely empty.
She is gambling with the help
of a ghost gambler.
The situation here is worse.
We might have to sell
the farmland and this house.
We need a proper human steward.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Jang Man-wol.
Do you gamble?
I was bored,
so I only played it as a game.
A game?
If you lived in my world,
you would have gone to prison.
I am planning to stop.
After I get back all the money I lost.
If you think like that,
you will never be able to stop.
I have to get back the money
to take care of the guests.
You don't need money
to take care of your guests.
Is there anything you don't know?
All right.
It seems you have some relationship
with the Mago sisters.
Go and tell that old beggar woman you saw
to leave this place.
You can't drive deities out
just like that.
That's right.
That's why I can't just kick
that beggar out.
Neither can I refuse her.
She comes here every day
wanting me to gamble with her.
I'll never win.
I'll become a beggar myself at this rate.
I once persuaded a deity to leave a place.
Really?
If I persuade her,
will you never gamble again?
Never.
I will put my hand on the line.
Oh, gosh.
It tastes
horrible.
Did you
enjoy your meal?
Who are you?
I am here for the Moon Flower.
My name is Koo Chan-sung.
Your sister sent me.
My big sister sent you?
You came from a very faraway place.
I know you are punishing Jang Man-wol
for what she did.
But can't you please stop now?
I plan to make her go broke.
Please go easy on her.
I don't like to see her suffer too much.
Why not?
If you don't like it,
will you play a round
with me?
You can choose the game.
How about a game of Go?
A game of Go?
I like that.
What's going on? Is he winning?
It's a very close game.
This young man is doing quite well
against a deity.
He was so sure of himself.
He said something about Harvard.
Do you know Harvard?
He studied there.
He said he had a great brain,
if nothing else.
I guess he wasn't lying.
You are so noisy.
Oh, no.
I lost.
Go away right now.
Don't ever come back.
-I'm going.
-Quickly.
Well done.
I WILL NEVER ENTER A GAMBLING DEN AGAIN
Are you happy now?
Please sign it.
Write your name.
How fastidious.
I noticed you had too many horses
in the stable.
Keep only three, and sell the rest
to pay off your debt.
Just three?
You'll say you want
to make the stable look good.
But that's not acceptable.
Pay off your debt first.
Or I'll call the old beggar again.
All right. I will sell them. Okay?
JANG MAN-WOL
There. We're done with this, right?
Don't go to gambling dens if you're bored.
Find a new hobby.
Look.
Joseon is shaped like a tiger.
A tiger?
Bibimbap is delicious in Jeonju.
And in winter, here.
Pohang is famous for half-dried herrings.
You will love
the Pyongyang naengmyeon up there.
Are you telling me
to go on a gourmet tour?
Have you eaten all of them?
Yes, I have.
With someone.
Will it be more fun than gambling?
You will like it
so much that you'll enjoy it
for the next 200 years.
Do you want to go with me?
Hey.
Would you be interested in working
as a steward here?
I like you.
Stay by my side here.
Once you get there,
do not eat or drink anything.
If you do, you won't be able to return.
If I stay here with you,
I won't have to worry
about you vanishing.
There.
Drink up, Chan-sung.
I have to go back.
There's a woman I must wait for.
Is she your lover?
Yes.
She's someone I love so much.
It's too bad.
I guess I might regret it once I go back.
If you leave,
their memories about you,
who traveled back in time,
will disappear.
Did you come to check up on me
because you were worried I wouldn't leave?
It's your choice whether you go back
or stay.
If you stay here, you'll probably become
Man-wol's 85th human steward
before you die.
Will you go back to being someone
who'll send her off,
or will you remain here
as someone passing by?
That's
for you to decide.
Thank you for bringing these for me.
I can see why you sent me there.
You helped me realize how I should feel
while waiting for her.
For now,
you should be happy.
Man-wol has come back.
She must be here.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It was a short period of time there,
but you must've waited for a long time.
Ms. Jang!
-Ms. Jang!
-Ms. Jang.
Ms. Jang!
Ms. Jang.
I'm glad Ms. Jang is back.
I was upset since we started
talking about a new owner.
Ms. Jang must've taken a while
because she had to see him off
on the bridge to the afterlife.
But because she stepped on the bridge,
Ms. Jang has lost a lot of her memories.
Her memories of the person
she sent off is almost gone.
Do older memories disappear first?
The memories that have bothered us
for the longest time
will disappear first.
It seems so futile,
but it gives me a sense of relief.
Don't worry.
I didn't forget anything about you.
Is that so? Then should I test you?
You're so fastidious.
The red car or me?
You. Happy?
Okay, that's the most important thing.
Do you remember
how many cars you have left?
Three...
Hey! You didn't sell them off
while I was away, did you?
I didn't sell your cars,
although I asked the horse to be sold off.
Do you remember Oh from Dangyong?
How do you know Oh Chung-hwan?
Even your memories
from 200 years ago are safe.
That's good.
Did Mr. Kim tell you?
I'm sure he did.
You guys must have talked behind my back.
What else did he say?
Have a drink.
I refused a drink from a woman
just a while ago.
So I need this now.
"A woman"? Why are you lying?
There's no way
you would have another woman.
Are you upset because I made you wait?
But I do. She's someone really beautiful.
Chan-sung, don't underestimate me.
I don't get jealous at all.
I'd just kill you. Die.
I see your hands are intact.
It looks like you kept your promise.
I went to Man-wol Inn to meet Madam Jang.
-Me?
-Mago sent me there.
And I was the one who saved you
from losing everything on gambling.
I don't have such a memory.
I was told that you wouldn't remember.
I only went there briefly
to find the Moon Flowers.
"Moon Flowers"?
Did she need them?
She told me she was making some wine.
-Do you know about it?
-Yes.
I had a taste of it a long time ago.
It was disgusting.
I guess Mago is making the wine again.
But her brother, Ji Hyeon-jung,
died many years ago.
Hyeon-jung!
Tae-seok!
Hey, give me a ride.
Where's your bike?
I left it at home.
-Hop on.
-Nice.
Just kidding.
My gosh.
So, the old man was
your friend from school.
Then I guess he's not a bad person
who stole your life.
He's a good friend who's been taking care
of your sister for you.
I did some research on Dr. Ji Hyeon-jung.
Look.
He did a lot of good deeds as a doctor.
And it seems
that a lot of people respect him.
He lived a really good life
with your name.
Yes, he lived a very diligent life.
He's taking care of your sister
at the hospital he founded,
so wouldn't your sister
be able to live
for at least ten more years?
Hey, I got a text
from your sister's caregiver.
What?
I got her number that day.
Hyeon-jung.
Fortunately, she's stable again.
Like always, she managed
to overcome the worst.
Thank you for everything.
Bye, then.
Hyeon-mi's okay again.
You must be very disappointed.
Young lady.
Did you take my photo?
What photo?
You once talked to me
about Hyeon-jung last time.
You took the photo of me
and Hyeon-jung, didn't you?
You have a photo of Hyeon-jung?
I guess you really were friends.
You're his friend, so make sure
his sister stays alive for a long time.
Hyeon-jung's always watching you.
He was also watching you
just a while ago.
Wait. Is Hyeon-jung alive?
Did he leave his sister with me
and make me live like this
when he's still alive?
Where is Hyeon-jung? Where's he now?
My goodness, you really used to be
an elite student, Hyeon-jung.
I was also really popular.
I can imagine.
Even the ghosts here told me
their hearts fluttered
every time you smiled at them.
I'm sure you were popular.
Back when I passed
the National State Exam at a young age
and was known as a genius,
all the young ladies in the neighborhood
gathered around my house
so they could hear me read out loud.
I guess it was because
they could hear your voice
but couldn't see your face.
You do have a nice voice, Mr. Kim.
A man should have a nice voice.
Don't you agree, Mr. Koo?
But he has good looks
as well as a nice voice.
The person next to you
must be your school friend.
Yes, he's the person
who's taking care of my sister Hyeon-mi
right now.
And thanks to him,
Hyeon-mi was able to stay alive today.
It seems like
Hyeon-jung will be leaving soon.
So I've been thinking...
How about we hold a special event for him
before he leaves
with his sister once she comes here?
Hyeon-jung never got to spend
much time with his sister.
So how about we open up an amusement park
so they could have fun together
even for a little while?
An amusement park?
And I don't mind
turning the bar into a kid-friendly cafe.
He's been kindly waiting
for his sister for 70 years.
He should at least get to talk
to his sister for a short while.
Do you really think
his sister is the only reason
he's been staying here?
He may be a pure and kind young man,
but do you really think
he's been waiting here
for 70 years just because he was
worried about his sister?
Have you all forgotten?
He came here after he got shot.
If you didn't want to come
to the event for them,
you could've just stayed quiet
instead of ruining the mood.
I once
shot someone with this gun.
I shot the ghost's enemy
with a bullet filled with her grudges...
so that he could live in agony forever.
Are you saying you're going to do the same
to the guy who killed Hyeon-jung?
Hyeon-jung already shot his enemy
with a bullet filled with his own grudges.
What do you think that bullet is?
It's Hyeon-mi.
I'm talking about his sister, Ji Hyeon-mi.
His little sister is almost blind
and mentally ill.
And he kept her beside his enemy
and made him suffer forever.
It's true that Hyeon-jung has been
waiting here for 70 years
for his sister to come.
But it's also true that he's used her
to harass the guy who killed him
for 70 whole years.
The person who killed Hyeon-jung
is his friend
that's taking care of his sister?
Yu-na.
Hyeon-jung.
I brought someone
who really wished to meet you.
Me?
Hyeon-jung.
Ms. Jang, Hyeon-jung's so-called friend
just came.
Yu-na brought him here.
I guess he's here to ask him
for forgiveness.
Hyeon-jung ran away
as soon as he saw the old man.
I guess he doesn't want to meet him.
I didn't bring him here for him.
Hyeon-jung can get his stolen life back,
even if only a little,
only while he's still alive.
That's why I brought him here.
Hyeon-jung needs to decide for himself.
During the war,
a bombing killed both his parents.
And Hyeon-jung barely managed
to save his little sister.
Eat slowly.
Is it good?
Hyeon-mi, once we get
to our uncle's place in Busan,
you can eat a lot of good food
and get treated
so that you aren't in pain anymore.
His sister was badly hurt,
so he was in a rush.
Instead of going with the refugees,
he decided to take shortcuts
through the mountains.
Do not move.
Hyeon-jung?
Tae-seok.
That's where he met a runaway soldier,
who turned out to be his friend.
Eat slowly.
My sister is badly hurt.
Do you know the shortcut?
We're headed to our uncle's place
in Busan.
Come with us, Tae-seok.
Take off your uniform.
Take it off!
I'll get shot and die if I'm wearing this,
so take that off.
Tae-seok.
You can't take this.
Hyeon-mi's medicine is in here,
and she'll die without it.
Let it go before I shoot you.
Hyeon-jung.
Hyeon-jung!
-Hyeon-jung!
-Hyeon-jung.
I didn't do this on purpose.
You know that, right?
-Hyeon-jung!
-Damn it.
-I'm sorry.
JI HYEON-JUNG
-Hyeon-jung!
-Take my sister with you.
Hyeon-jung!
Take my sister with you.
-Hyeon-jung!
-Please.
Hyeon-jung!
His friend took Hyeon-mi
and went to his uncle's house.
JI HYEON-JUNG
They recognized Hyeon-mi,
so they naturally thought
the one who brought her there
was Hyeon-jung.
Ever since that time,
he has lived as Ji Hyeon-jung.
Ms. Jang said Hyeon-mi is the bullet
he shot his enemy with.
Hyeon-jung always talked about his sister
with a smile on his face.
He probably couldn't help
but loathe him as he watched
his friend taking care
of his precious sister.
Hyeon-jung, why are you sulking here?
Goodness, the leaves
and flowers are all gone,
so it looks really shabby.
And it looks even worse
with a guy sitting here
looking like a dog
who got caught in the rain.
This isn't fair.
It was really hard to see
how he got to do everything
that I dreamed of doing.
I'll never forgive him.
How can you forgive someone
who punched a hole in your chest?
Just go and hear him out.
I'm sure he didn't come here to show off
that he had a good life
after he killed you.
He's probably here to tell you that
his life has been tough and harsh too.
But it's not too bad
to hear out someone's excuses.
You feel a little better too.
Did that happen to you too?
Yes.
That's how I could finally see him off
as he turned around and left.
You said you didn't remember
the firefly incident.
Are you nitpicking about my memory now?
If you're going to sit here and sulk,
I'll go send him away.
Goodness, Yu-na did all that for nothing.
It will make him feel relieved
for the rest of his life.
However,
since Yu-na brought him here,
go talk to him.
A girl you like is trying very hard
to do something for you.
I guess bringing you here
made Hyeon-jung feel more tormented.
Please leave.
Well, in that case,
can you give this to him?
JI HYEON-JUNG
Hyeon-jung loved going to school.
Mr. Oh Tae-seok.
Hyeon-jung said he will see you.
He wants to see you in this room.
Please go on in.
You still look the same, Hyeon-jung.
I kept an eye on you as you grew older.
Tae-seok.
OH TAE-SEOK
JI HYEON-JUNG
You left Hyeon-jung with his enemy.
Why aren't you worried?
Because Hyeon-jung is good-natured.
And he's been keeping his eye on him.
I'm sure he's already
forgiven him a little since Mr. Oh has
never given up on Hyeon-mi.
Since the nice Hyeon-jung
has forgiven him a little,
the wicked owner will make him pay
the compensation.
Are you going to take money from him?
Hyeon-jung's friend is filthy rich.
I should throw a party
for our little kid before he leaves.
You donated a lot of money
and even founded a hospital
under Ji Hyeon-jung's name.
I've spent all my life
trying to atone for what I did.
Then do one more thing while you're at it.
Please buy a school
under Ji Hyeon-jung's name.
If you can, the prestigious school
Hyeon-jung used to attend.
Please buy it for us.
DONGSEON HIGH SCHOOL
We're so thankful
Dr. Ji Hyeon-jung donated
such a large sum to the school.
However, are you sure you're okay
with such a small event
in the middle of the night?
All Mr. Ji Hyeon-jung wants is
an honorary high school diploma.
Also, the nighttime is more convenient
for those attending today.
And the person receiving the diploma is
Ji Hyeon-jung.
He has the same name as Dr. Ji?
He's a student
who loved going to this school.
There he is.
CEREMONY FOR JI HYEON-JUNG'S
HONORARY DIPLOMA
They must be his family.
Yes, they are.
Is everyone here?
Yes. So many people came.
Why did you have to bring everyone here?
Hyeon-jung is popular, you know.
The Grim Reaper provided us with a bus,
so you don't have to worry.
Here is your honorary diploma.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming, everyone.
For...
-Hyeon-jung!
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
Chan-sung.
All of them are ghosts?
Yes. The people you can see
have been ghosts for a long time,
so they can show themselves.
Show themselves?
That must be a high-level ability.
Aside from that table,
this whole place is
filled with our employees.
That table is full,
and this table is full too?
Sanchez, if this is too hard for you,
it's okay to stay outside.
No, I'm okay.
When else will I get to see
ghosts having dinner?
I want to thank everyone...
Hey, are you sure Man-wol's cousin
isn't a human?
It's a long story.
She was a ghost,
then she possessed someone else's body--
Forget it. They even possess people.
I'll look after everyone
and work even harder from now on.
-Thank you!
-Good luck!
-Let's go!
-Bravo.
Chan-sung, do you like those ghosts?
It's our first time
having a meal together.
It feels good when you have
a meal with your colleagues, right?
Sanchez, don't drink too much.
Some mischievous ghosts
like to possess drunk people.
Are you serious?
The one sitting at that table
has been looking at you for a while.
Be careful.
Ghosts must like good-looking people
like me. Am I right?
DASHCAM SETTINGS
Goodness. Is that a ghost?
I must be able to see them now.
Here. He was recorded clearly.
It's not a ghost.
You startled me.
I guess he's not a ghost.
There's no need to be so scared.
Ghosts used to be people too.
It's normal to be scared.
You're the one who became strange.
Chan-sung, I think you're going too far.
I'm worried you might completely move on
to the other side.
I understand your concern,
but the people
you saw today are all going to leave.
Man-wol, too?
Yes.
Jang Man-wol, too.
I gave Mr. Koo the medicine
while you were away.
He didn't take it.
I see.
Mr. Koo must have trusted
you'd return.
I guess you didn't.
I was glad you were freed from this place.
But,
you returned.
I didn't return because I'm tied
to the Moon Tree like before.
A new owner will be coming.
Mago is working on it.
Does Mr. Koo know about this?
Yes. He does.
Although neither of us talks about it.
I want to send off Mr. Kim,
Hyeon-jung, and you
while I'm here.
But...
I'm not sure if I will have enough time.
Ms. Jang is inside.
Ms. Choe.
I paid a visit to that woman
we found at the pharmacy,
and she'll be giving birth soon.
If the baby ends up carrying on
the family name,
will you continue to stay behind?
Are you afraid
that I'd wander around
after Ms. Jang is gone
and Hotel del Luna disappears?
So you know.
I just found out.
Ms. Jang is no longer tied down
to the Moon Tree.
She could have gone
to the afterlife if she wanted.
What has her tied down here must be you,
Mr. Koo.
Are you worried that I'd become
another Moon Tree?
I'm reminded of something
Mago said to that bride
who had a ghost wedding here.
She said that
it's hard, but sometimes
it's easier to let go than hold on.
Gosh, it's so heavy. It's so heavy.
What are these?
I take them out from time to time.
There's so much dust.
It's so strong. Open it.
-It's a camera.
-Yes.
I used it to take all these pictures.
It looks quite old.
Did your previous managers
take those pictures for you?
Let's see...
That's the one. The one
who took this photo of Man-wol Hostel
ran away after using up all of my money.
So I chased after him, and it turned out
his wife was close to giving birth.
I just let him go.
You already know Hwang Mun-suk
from Hotel del Luna.
And way before this one...
There it is.
The manager at that time was
really handsome.
They say if a man is handsome,
you should call him honey.
He was more than just a honey.
I don't believe you.
Mr. Kim told me everything.
Of all the managers
he saw in the last 500 years,
I'm the most handsome one.
He told me you fell in love with me
because of my looks.
Why would you talk about such a thing
with Mr. Kim?
When did you two get so close?
That's why you should've taken
these pictures
with the people who were with you
at that time.
Then you'd have a proof.
Back then,
I thought they were just passing me by
and meant nothing to me.
But looking at these with you,
it's too bad I didn't leave
any records behind.
Would you like to leave a record right now
with that camera?
Hyeon-jung got his honorary diploma,
but he didn't get to take any pictures.
We should all get together
to take a picture.
I'll take it for you.
I've never taken a picture before.
I wonder if I'll be visible.
You will. I took a picture
with a phone before.
We should have put on more blush.
We look pale like ghosts.
It's okay.
What's so wrong with looking like ghosts
when we're ghosts?
Hyeon-jung, don't open your mouth
when we take the picture.
Mr. Kim, don't blink.
All right.
I'll take it now.
One, two, three...
Mr. Koo, you should join us.
Yes, hurry over.
Come over, Mr. Koo.
How can I put it away
when you're sitting on it?
Get off now.
Lift me off of it.
Just try it.
I won't move until you lift me.
Forget it. You can put it away then.
To the room.
We took a picture.
Now, let's go eat jajangmyeon.
Darn it.
You took a picture.
It was a lot of fun.
Why didn't you call me?
We took it with Mr. Koo
to remember this moment
before Ms. Jang leaves
and the hotel disappears.
Is the hotel going to disappear? Why?
Mago is preparing to make
a new Guest House of the Moon.
Then Ms. Jang's Hotel del Luna
will disappear.
What about you?
Are you going to leave
if the hotel disappears?
It's fermenting really well.
I heard Mago is preparing
the wine for the next hotel owner.
I'll drink it and become the owner.
It's Mago who decides the next owner.
Then Ms. Jang should drink it
and continue to be the owner.
Do you think Mago would do that?
After everything that's happened?
When is Mago coming?
Where can I find her?
She's not someone you can meet
just because you want to.
Then nobody here can meet with her?
I think Mr. Koo has the permission
to enter Mago's pharmacy.
He said he brought the firefly
from her shop.
PHARMACY
11-28 YAKJAE-GOLMOK, GYEONGDONG MARKET
-Cheers.
Sanchez, thank you for everything.
Let's go out to eat with Chan-sung soon.
It'll be my treat.
Are you moving back
to your parents' house?
She's moving in with me.
Are you going to live together?
It's going to be so tough for you,
Yeong-su.
Mi-ra tries to help around the house,
but she's useless.
I already know.
We had so many fights,
so we decided to see
how much more we can fight.
Luckily, I'm good at cleaning.
And she's better at cooking than me,
if nothing else.
She is?
Yes.
The kimchi and side dishes
she brought me were good.
I didn't make them all by myself.
My parents helped me a little.
I see.
It's not a lie since they make them
at the factory.
"The factory"?
My parents run a kimchi factory.
They're always on the shopping channel.
Haven't you heard of Daeho Kimchi?
"Daeho Kimchi"?
I used to eat it all the time
back in the day.
Is that why Mi-ra's side dishes
were perfect to my taste?
No wonder.
The food that raised you
was made by my parents.
We're meant to be together.
I think so.
Chan-sung and I ate that kimchi too.
It's a kimchi brand
that fed countless people in Korea.
I don't think it's anything special.
Yeong-su says it's perfect to his taste.
-Right?
-Sure.
-Cheers.
-Love shot?
-Love shot.
You read my mind.
They should get along
until they move in together.
She might end up staying here
if they fight.
Is it good?
It's good.
Both of you are writers, aren't you?
This was Li Bai's favorite drink.
He's a famous best-selling author.
He passed away
just before the release of his new book.
It's really unfortunate.
I did a lot of research,
and the story was really interesting.
What is your novel about?
It's about a scholar
from the Joseon Dynasty.
The bartender is a scholar
who won the first place
in the National State Exam.
Really?
What is your name?
My name wasn't recorded anywhere
in history.
The protagonist of the novel
I was writing is also someone
who won the first place
in the National State Exam.
But his appointment got cancelled.
Did that actually happen?
He got caught for writing lewd literature,
so he was beaten up by other scholars,
and his appointment got cancelled.
It's the story of a perverted scholar.
That's interesting.
What's the name of that perverted scholar?
He has a grandiose name.
It's Si-ik, which means
the wings of the era.
His name is Kim Si-ik.
Kim Si-ik!
If you have any shame,
do not ever dare lift up your face again.
I had finished the novel before I died,
so it might be published
as my posthumous work.
I hope it does get published.
I heard the wine is made
with the energy of the moon.
The tree came back
to how it used to look like.
No, it's different from that time.
Back then, it was just on display.
But this time, its leaves sprouted,
and its flowers bloomed and fell
as time passed once again.
The tree has gone through all that.
Do you hope to see it
grow out leaves and bloom flowers again?
This is dead.
If I wish to have such time once again,
I should probably cross the bridge.
Probably.
Yu-na, what's wrong?
Ms. Jang.
I stole this wine from Mago's pharmacy.
I heard it's for the new owner.
Can you drink this
and stay at this hotel?
A girl who has been
coming in and out of your hotel
stole the wine I made.
I'm sure she did this
because she was afraid
the reception guy,
Hyeon-jung, would leave.
She didn't want the hotel to disappear.
Then she probably brought that to Man-wol.
If she drinks that
and regains the power of the Moon Tree,
Hotel del Luna will remain here,
and you two
can be together again.
If Ms. Jang makes such a choice,
will you not stop her?
You wanted to let her go peacefully.
If I do not stop her,
what will you do?
Mr. Koo, Yu-na came with...
I know. Where's Jang Man-wol?
On the first day that I was
tied down to the Moon Tree,
the full moon was
as big and bright as that one.
The wine I drank then
fell into my hands again.
Chan-sung.
Should I drink this again?
When I went back in time
and met you,
I wanted to take the drink you offered me
to stay with you there.
If I had done that,
I would've become
the 85th human who worked for you,
and drawn a portrait of you.
I had this thought as I hung
the picture we took together.
That I will be your last manager,
the 99th one.
I won't let you
spend meaningless time with the 100th one.
So...
don't drink that.
I knew you would say that.
Thank you, Chan-sung.
I love you.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu
It's a little kid.
It seems like her parents
already crossed the Samdo River.
How did this little girl manage
to stay alive for so long?
When I came to take her,
I was also surprised to see
that she was still alive.
This little girl is trying so hard
to stay alive.
Why don't you take a step back?
But she won't last more than a few hours.
You never know
what might happen
in that short amount of time.
Father, I see something over there.
What?
My gosh.
Hey, it's very dirty.
Don't touch anything.
They're dead.
They must be from Goguryeo.
I think they were killed while wandering
around after their country collapsed.
Let me see.
Let's take the wagon.
Thank you for the wagon. My goodness.
She moved.
Can you see me?
You're alive.
Don't be sad.
I'm sure your parents went
to the Guest House of the Moon.
I heard it from a granny
who sells medicine.
There's a place called
the Guest House of the Moon
somewhere in the wilderness.
It's where dead people go to get some rest
before they leave for the afterlife.
What's your name?
Man-wol.
The moon.
Your name means the "full moon."
It's pretty.
Do you think
we already met in our past lives?
I'm 1,300 years old.
I wonder how I got to meet you now.
Sometimes, it takes 1,300 years
for two people to meet each other.
Do you know
that it takes a very long time
for the light from the stars to reach us?
The Orion Nebula is
1,300 lightyears away from Earth.
That means it takes 1,300 years
for us to be able to see it
with our own eyes.
Really?
Where is it right now?
You can only see it during winter,
so you can't see it right now.
Winter?
Starting from the next full moon,
the energy of the moon
will be withdrawn from this place.
From now on, you won't be
getting any new guests.
I guess you're telling me
to close it down.
Your Guest House of the Moon...
will only exist
up until the next full moon.
It's a pity that we can only see it
in winter.
Chan-sung, is there any star
we can see right now
instead of the Orion Nebula?
Well...
I'm not sure.
I'm not very good with astronomy.
So I can't answer that question.
You dumbhead from Harvard.
You could've just pointed
at any one of those stars in the sky.
Do you think I would've corrected you
if you were wrong?
I would've just acted
like I was impressed.
Shall I, then?
Let's see.
I should pick a beautiful, shining one
since you like shiny things.
Forget it. It's too late.
There really is one more.
Another star you can see
after living through 1,300 years.
Me, Koo Chan-sung.
I told you my name means a brilliant star.
All right. You're all I need.
I don't care about the star
that I can only see in winter.
I'll be happy as long as I can see you.
Look at you, Chan-sung.
You shine so brightly.
Twinkle twinkle! I'm so dazzled!
Look at you, Man-wol.
You're looking so bright
like the full moon.
"The full moon"?
Or we could call you my lucky charm.
You deserve the nickname
as you've gotten much nicer.
You said I'd be reincarnated as a pig.
You said you'd happily be
reincarnated as chicken noodles.
What if that actually happens?
It's okay. I'll be the fresh kimchi
that goes with it.
Really?
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-You really mean it, right?
You said you'd be the fresh kimchi.
You promised me.
Yes, I'll really be
the fresh kimchi for you.
Did Mr. Kim go somewhere?
He went out after chatting
with those guests.
Yes.
Where did he go?
My new novel will be released.
It's about a perverted scholar, Kim Si-ik,
who passed the National State Exam
for nothing.
I should just leave before I must face
such humiliation.
I should really leave.
Let's not forget to say goodbye
to each other before we leave.
Don't leave without saying anything.
I'm serious.
Gosh.
Oh, dear.
Ms. Jang, I can't find Mr. Kim anywhere.
-He's probably with Hyeon-jung.
-No, he's not.
I couldn't find him anywhere in the hotel.
Maybe he stepped out.
He rarely goes outside the hotel.
Even when he does, he never leaves alone.
He still sounds like a man
living in the Joseon era, you know.
Apparently, he turned pale
and left the bar
while chatting with some guests
about a scholar
who aced the National State Exam.
A scholar
who aced the National State Exam?
You know about his situation, right?
By any chance, was his name
Kim Si-ik when he was alive?
Who is the guest that spoke ill
of Kim Seon-bi?
I was telling him that I died
before I could publish
the book I wrote
about the scholar, Kim Si-ik.
And the novel mocks Kim Si-ik, doesn't it?
It's a fiction I wrote
based on thorough research.
So that novel will actually be released?
I already sent the manuscript
to my publisher.
They'll publish it as my posthumous work.
Which publisher did you send it to?
And how many people have read this?
I still write a novel in longhand,
so there's only one manuscript.
I'm sure the editor-in-chief is
the only one who's read it.
I must find this publisher.
His handwriting is so bad as always.
Gosh, my eyes hurt.
SALACIOUS SCHOLAR, KIM SI-IK
Is the air conditioner on?
HAEGONG PUBLISHING COMPANY
I am not a salacious scholar.
This isn't fair.
First, try to buy the manuscript from him.
The money from selling the horses
will be enough.
But I'm worried Mr. Kim
might cause trouble before we do that.
If he does anything to harm humans,
the Grim Reaper won't let it slide.
Kim Seon-bi is like a crane.
Have you seen a crane attacking humans?
He won't harm anyone.
Still, he's been holding a grudge
for 500 years.
Cranes make sure their feathers stay
as white as snow
even when they're standing in mud.
Seon-bi has waited for 500 years
to clear his name.
I AM NOT SALACIOUS
I'm Kim Si-ik. I am not salacious.
I scared him too much.
I just want to make sure
the book won't be published.
Should I have gone easy on him?
Sir!
What's wrong?
I saw a ghost.
-Sorry?
-A ghost?
I just saw the ghost of Kim Si-ik.
-Hold on.
-You saw his ghost?
-It means the book will be a hit!
-We will hit the jackpot!
My gosh, sir!
-I was really scared.
-What a lucky dream!
It wasn't a dream.
I really saw him, you fool!
-Are we celebrating tonight?
-A team dinner will be nice!
-Guys, how about sushi?
-My gosh.
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Koo, Ms. Jang. You knew I'd be here?
Look at yourself.
Let's go back to the hotel for now.
I cannot go back to the hotel
for I am too humiliated.
I'll just take the bus here
and head to the afterlife.
Why are you being like this?
You're the ace of our hotel,
and you're like a dignified crane.
Cranes do not hang their heads.
Keep your chin up!
I'll get the manuscript
from the publisher no matter what.
Mr. Koo...
You're refusing to return to the hotel,
so you should stay in Chan-sung's room.
Thank you, Mr. Koo.
Only the editor-in-chief has read this,
and he hasn't even finished it yet.
I went through hoops to persuade him
because the author is very famous.
How did you persuade him?
I told him that Kim Si-ik is my ancestor.
He lied that he's your descendant,
and I spent a fortune to buy it from him.
Thank you so much.
Salacious Scholar, Kim Si-ik?
I suppose I'll never be able
to clear my name.
If it's not true,
explain and prove your innocence.
Could you tell us what happened?
Everyone called me a genius
because I passed
the Local State Exam at a very young age.
However, I failed the National State Exam
every time.
After the age of 40,
I left my hometown
and settled down in Hanyang.
Then I focused solely
on studying for the exam.
While I studied alone,
whenever I felt lonely,
watching how others lived
was the only thing that gave me joy.
I saw a young girl
looking after her blind father,
and I also saw brothers and sisters
argue with each other all the time.
-My gosh.
-Hey.
It was beautiful
to see a young couple fall in love
disregarding their social status.
Whenever I grew bored of reading books,
I came up with stories
based on what I had seen on the street.
Master, this is so sad.
What happens next?
Of course, back then, for scholars,
writing a story in something else
than Chinese characters
was considered unconventional.
However, the stories I wrote
weren't vulgar at all.
Wait, you wrote stories
about a dutiful daughter,
a faithful woman, and siblings...
Are they about Sim Cheong,
Chun-hyang, Heung-bu, and Nol-bu?
You wrote all of those stories?
They're known to be
anonymous works to this day.
If that's true, you're the Shakespeare
of the Joseon Dynasty.
But those stories ruined my life
when my life was at its peak.
Master, congratulations.
You'll make a glorious return.
Your appointment will be canceled.
What do you mean?
It's my understanding
that you wrote these stories.
You call yourself a scholar,
and yet you wrote the so-called stories
about lowly lives of the commoners?
You are a disgrace to fellow scholars!
All the scholars will step in to make sure
that someone as vulgar and nasty as you
is never appointed as an official.
I only wrote stories about people's lives.
How could you call these stories vulgar?
A story of an adulterous couple.
A story where the order
between brothers is broken.
A story that confuses the people
through absurd imaginations.
How can a scholar come up
with such stories?
Master!
Kim Si-ik.
If you have any shame,
do not ever dare lift up your face again.
Due to the petition brought
by other scholars, I was disqualified.
The son of a powerful family
took my position.
My father who was in my hometown
was so humiliated
that he refused to eat and passed away.
I was too ashamed to face my wife
who had been supporting me.
As I could neither go back
to my hometown nor stay there,
I died
all by myself, feeling lost in the world.
I feel so wronged.
At first, he waited for
his so-called humiliating stories
to disappear in this world.
But people puffed up his stories,
and the stories spread even more.
Everyone in this world
knows the stories of Chun-hyang
and Sim Cheong.
I'm sure a part of him was
feeling hopeful.
He could have cleared his name
and felt proud instead.
However, there's no evidence.
Can you truly trust everything he says?
No wonder
someone would write a book about him.
People don't know
about the stories he wrote.
He just became a salacious scholar
who got disqualified in the end
because of his so-called vulgar stories.
I will read every page of this manuscript.
Mr. Kim is okay though, right?
He will stay in my room for now.
Sanchez.
I remember seeing you
at the dinner the other day.
Yes. What brings you here?
I have a situation,
so I'll be staying
in Mr. Koo's room for a while.
I see.
Then does he also work at the hotel?
He's the Grim Reaper.
He's not an easy man to meet
when you're alive.
Say hello.
But he's not here
because he has business with me, right?
No. I'm here to console
an old friend of mine.
The Grim Reaper bought me some beer.
Would you like to join us?
No, I'm good. Please go ahead.
Please allow me to stay for a while.
Sure.
-Hey.
-Yes?
As I didn't have any food for beer,
I picked some jujube in your yard.
If we meet in the future,
I'll repay you for them.
Sure.
I have peanuts. Do you want me
to bring some peanuts?
Excuse me.
I didn't know
that's what had happened to Kim Si-ik.
It's unfortunate,
but I don't want to go
against 500-year-old grudges
to publish the book.
I will get rid of it.
It would be a shame
to destroy it like this.
My manager read every page of the novel.
He told me the story was
quite fascinating.
If I were to overlook
the perverted scholar part,
the scholar character is quite enticing
and fascinating, from what I heard.
He's a noble-minded scholar
who doesn't get involved
in the conflict
between two major factions.
He's also a romantic scholar,
who writes to his wife once a month
while she waits for him at this hometown.
I did my research.
That's what Kim Si-ik did.
I'll tell you what. "Kim Si-ik decided
not to join the social cliques
to gain power.
As an outsider,
he indulged himself
in perverted, erotic stories."
Let's just change this part.
"The existing stories, written
in the Korean alphabet by unknown writers,
were actually written
by the scholar, Kim Si-ik."
You won't be able to write this
in a historical book,
but it would make
a very fascinating theme for a novel.
You're right.
"Shin Yun-bok was a woman."
There's a book with that theme too.
In novels, everything is possible.
Let's go with that then.
The most romantic scholar
and the best storyteller
in the Joseon Dynasty,
who was as noble as a crane.
Kim Si-ik.
"Crane"? This title just crossed my mind.
My masterpiece, The War of Cranes,
is followed by this beautiful novel
called A Song of a Crane.
A Song of a Crane. Let's sing that song.
Sir, write a great story.
What just happened?
A Song of a Crane!
You must start the song.
What are you doing?
This happens all the time to people
who died from overwork.
I forgot to mention
that he passes out within 30 seconds
upon grabbing his pen.
What? If he keeps passing out
every 30 seconds,
when will he finish his novel?
We must get help from another writer.
What? Another writer? Who?
We have a novelist
who wanted to work hard, but couldn't
before he died.
Sir, from what I've observed so far,
your writing is superb.
But you haven't decided
what to write about yet.
We have a great topic
as well as an excellent teacher.
Will you
complete a novel?
Does that mean I'll remain
as a character in a fictional story?
Kim Si-ik is recorded as a scholar
who got disqualified
for writing vulgar stories.
There's only one line.
That will not disappear
even if you wait for 500 years.
Is that so?
But it's not fictional
that you were an affectionate husband
and noble scholar.
Remaining in this world in a novel
seems good enough to me.
Is that so?
Besides, it's a novel.
While we're at it,
let's say that he was tall
and very handsome.
How will they know?
Is there anyone you think you resemble?
There's a guy
who I think resembles me a lot.
Okay. Who is it?
Young people call him Mr. Hip.
So Ji-sub?
Are you telling me
that you resemble So Ji-sub?
Come on, you...
You definitely look like him!
Yes. You look just like him.
I resemble him even more from this side.
Goodness, you're right.
Turn around a bit more.
Keep turning.
Yes, that's it.
The back of your head
is pitch black just like his.
Goodness, Mr. Kim.
You're a hip, handsome guy.
Kim Si-ik can even do martial arts.
He sounds pretty cool.
Gosh, the writer romanticized
the guy too much.
This will be a hit.
Ms. Jang. Mr. Koo.
The last part is complete.
Let's see.
It's good.
Mr. Kim.
There's a draft of a book
I received from a rookie writer.
Check the second shelf
of the bookcase in my writing room.
The story is about a scholar,
Kim Si-ik in the Joseon Dynasty,
and the author's name is Bae Seong-hun.
Yes, of course.
Right.
A SONG OF A CRANE
The book has been published,
and our two writers left
with smiles on their faces.
I made these cocktails
as a token of my gratitude,
so please enjoy them.
I said I'm not a fan of Tears.
Still, it's for a special occasion
this time,
so please drink up.
What's the meaning behind it this time?
They are tears of a sad goodbye.
I, Kim Si-ik, a scholar of Joseon,
have washed away my shame.
With these tears that symbolize
my reluctance to leave,
I will now head to the afterlife.
Mr. Kim...
We will
gulp down our tears with this drink...
and say goodbye.
Thank you for everything.
I thank you for all your hard work
and apologize for leaving first.
Take care, Mr. Kim.
It's been 70 years,
but you're still like a baby.
Goodbye, Mr. Kim.
I'll get going.
THE SAMDO RIVER
THIS LIFE, THE AFTERLIFE
Goodbye.
Ms. Jang.
Thank you for preserving my name
and letting me be remembered
as a scholar as mysterious as a crane.
These are the tears
I give to you as my gratitude.
I hope that the cold and icy moon of yours
will go down
beautifully and warmly.
This tastes awful.
Why don't you come
to the hotel these days?
Why would I when it'll soon be gone?
I came to check if Hyeon-mi had died
because that would mean
you'd soon be leaving too.
Well, Mr. Kim left.
See? You're sad because he left too.
That's how I'll feel if you go.
Please say that you'll stay.
It's sad
that he's no longer with us,
but we sent him off with joy.
Because nothing is sadder
than staying in this world.
What's sad about being with me?
Look at me and my sister.
Is that what you want for us?
Fine, leave then.
But I can't stay and watch you leave.
Kim Yu-na's parents keep telling me
to go and study abroad.
I think I'll just go. It's perfect, right?
You can go to the afterlife,
and I'll go abroad.
Let's just leave our graves behind here...
and say our farewell.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I've seen you
watching from outside the pharmacy.
Are you perhaps a relative
of my baby's father?
I was once
a daughter-in-law of
the Yeongju Yun family.
My baby will never be
of the Yeongju Yun family.
It will take my surname instead.
If it's a son,
he'll be the sole heir
who'll carry on the family line.
And a daughter will equally
be the sole heir too.
They don't carry on
the family line though.
Once she marries, she'll become a member
of her husband's family and--
Are you from Joseon or something?
No one thinks like that
in this day and age.
If the grandparents want to see my baby,
then I'll let them.
But, whether it's a boy or a girl,
this baby will just be
my child.
What's wrong?
Why...
did I never think of that
for my daughter?
I feel so sorry for her.
This child...
I just hope the child inside your womb
will be born healthy,
and live a good life.
THE GUYS WHO DIED AFTER EATING
Look.
This.
And this one. Which one should I post?
This one is good.
This one? Okay.
You take so many photos.
Do you have any followers?
Of course. Hyeon-jung, Yu-na, and Sanchez.
That's all?
Your boiled egg looks much better.
You were taking so many pictures.
I thought you had
about a million followers.
You haven't even pressed "like" once.
You have no right to say that.
I don't do social media.
-Alex Ferguson once said--
-Forget it.
I'm sure he said something great.
But that's what he thinks. I will...
What is it now?
Like...
He pressed "like."
Who? Sanchez?
Kim Jun-hyun...
Kim Jun-hyun did.
Look at this. He pressed "like"
for the picture I posted
about the rice with thistle.
LIKE
KIM JUN-HYUN
He really did.
You only have three followers.
How did he find your post
and press "like"?
I don't wish for anything more.
I have been recognized
by the master gourmet.
Since when did you like
Kim Jun-hyun so much?
What?
From the first time I saw him,
I knew he's my cup of tea.
He looks like someone I know.
I was going through hard times
because of my undesirable hobby.
Suddenly a young guy appeared
and saved me with the game of Go.
He also recommended
I go on a gourmet tour.
He looks exactly like Kim Jun-hyun.
But that's me.
What?
I told you I went
to Man-wol Inn 200 years ago
to get the Moon flowers.
It was me who won the game of Go
and drew you the gourmet map.
It was me.
Don't be ridiculous.
I remember clearly.
He had a big build like Kim Jun-hyun.
He was very nice and kind.
You wouldn't even be one-fourth of
the man he is, no matter how hard you try.
What are you trying to do?
That's the way Mago changed your memories.
Now I realize that we did visit
so many good restaurants.
They were all good.
Lastly, there is something
you have to eat.
You have to
eat that later.
You have to.
Let's eat. Naengmyeon is getting cold.
Okay. Let's eat before it gets cold.
Do you want mustard?
Kim Jun-hyun said you need vinegar
when you have Pyongyang naengmyeon.
Wasn't that Baek Jong-won?
It could be.
You're 1,300 years old for sure.
You are confused about
what your favorite guy said.
-How much?
-Just a little.
It looks delicious.
Aren't you adding any?
With Pyongyang naengmyeon,
you have to taste the broth first.
Of all the room service staff,
you will be the only one left.
Most of the guests are gone too.
Thanks for all your work.
-We will be going.
-Okay.
Ms. Choe.
Yes.
I have to go to get Hyeon-mi.
Tae-seok contacted me.
Bring your sister here.
I'll let Ms. Jang know.
Hyeon-mi, I am here.
Hyeon-jung.
Hyeon-mi.
Do you know how long I've waited for you?
Let's go.
Yu-na.
You must be Hyeon-jung's sister, Hyeon-mi.
Thanks to your kind brother,
you'll leave without losing your way.
What about Yu-na?
Does she know you are leaving?
I saw her at the hospital.
Could you give this to her for me?
And...
Please tell her
that every single second she has left
is all so precious,
so she should be a good student
and be happy.
Ma'am.
I'd be happy to give
all the time I have left.
Please grant me a favor.
Hyeon-jung.
Take them with you.
You left flowers on my grave too.
I got these for you.
I asked Mago
and I put myself in huge debt
to get them for you.
She told me that I have to live
a really good life
in order to repay her
for the favor she's done for me.
So you don't need to worry about me.
Thank you.
I won't worry.
Bye, Hyeon-jung.
Goodbye.
Why are you suddenly meeting Mi-ra's
parents? Are you planning to marry?
We're
going to get married this winter.
Then that's going to be
a really important event.
It's weird that you'd want to meet
her parents at a pizza restaurant.
We chose this place because of you.
You have no idea
how much my parents trust you.
Back when they came
to the States to take me back,
all of my friends helped me hide
from them,
but you told them where I was.
You scored
a lot of brownie points with them.
They think you're a very honest friend.
Well, it's nice to hear
that your parents think I'm trustworthy.
But I still don't get
why you'd want me to be here
when you introduce him to your parents.
If my parents end up not liking Yeong-su,
you should help me convince them.
Why? It's your marriage.
And I'm not even his brother.
I don't have a family to introduce her to,
so she must be really worried.
Sanchez, can you be his older brother?
You should tell them
what a great guy Yeong-su is.
You know what I mean, right?
Actually, just tell them
that I'm pregnant.
I'm not a gynecologist.
I'm just an owner of a pizza restaurant.
You're being really weird.
Mi-ra, you shouldn't lie
to your parents like that.
If they happen to disapprove of me,
I'll do my best to convince them.
I just don't want you to feel lonely.
I can't wait to become your family.
Mi-ra.
I guess they won't have any problems
getting married this winter.
We're so different when it comes
to choosing a refrigerator.
It's better to have a bigger freezer.
There are so many things
to store in the freezer.
You never eat anything
from the freezer anyway.
Let's just buy one
that has a big refrigerating space
so we can eat fresh food.
Honey.
Do you choose me
or the refrigerating space?
Your love for me should be equal
to the size of the freezer.
I love you as much as the size
of the North Pole.
So let's get a fridge
that has a lot of refrigerating space.
Done.
Forget it. I'm going to go
take a look at the furniture.
Stop right there.
Ms. Jang?
You're getting married,
Ms. Lee?
Did Chan-sung tell you?
Where is he? Is he here with you?
He went to get some milk tea,
Ms. Lee.
I asked if you're getting married.
Yes, we're getting married this winter.
I'll give you an invitation
once we finish printing them.
I'd like to give you a gift first.
A gift for me?
I wanted to give you
an unforgettable gift.
Look.
Song-hwa.
You better be good to Yeon-u.
If you ever make him cry,
I'll turn your life upside down
just like that TV.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I'll get you this TV as a wedding gift.
I hope whenever you look at it,
you'll always remember what I just said.
What did you say to Mi-ra?
I just said I hoped
they'll have a happy life
as they watch TV together.
You gave Mi-ra a wedding gift?
Yes.
I heard they're getting married in winter.
I won't be able to buy them
anything in winter
since I won't be here anymore.
Ms. Choe's leaving today.
The full moon will be here soon.
Your Guest House of the Moon
will only exist
up until the next full moon.
Your hands are cold.
Should I get you a warm drink?
No.
It's nice. It feels like winter.
But why did you get her a TV?
I noticed
that the TV could flip upside down.
What about that?
You don't need to know.
You remember
Yeon-u, right?
Who's Yeon-u?
He's no longer the person
who loves you the most.
I know.
It's Ms. Choe now.
The rooms
are all empty now.
Ms. Jang, I'll be off now.
Thank you for letting me stay here
all these years
and protecting me.
Thanks to you,
I was able to learn a big lesson
at a very important moment.
Thank you.
Mr. Koo.
I was the one who suggested
that we should make you enter Room 13.
I've been feeling guilty about that.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
If I didn't enter Room 13 that day,
I wouldn't have been able
to obtain that one second.
Even if you ever get to obtain
an entire lifetime,
don't ever let anyone see you
wearing your tiger print suit.
It'll make you lose everything.
I'll keep that in mind.
Ms. Jang.
Now that we're about to say goodbye,
it suddenly reminds me of the day
I first came to Man-wol Inn.
Where do you think you're doing?
Are you stealing that knife
to kill everyone in that family?
My daughter...
The man who killed his own daughter
just welcomed a new child.
You won't be able to kill anyone
with that knife.
If you take this, you'll be able to kill
at least a few people.
After that, you'll get captured
and disappear into thin air
like you always wanted.
But the person
you actually want to kill is yourself
because you have failed to protect
your precious daughter.
If you stay here to go to the afterlife,
you'll get to live a new life.
But I know you don't want that.
You already hate yourself so much.
So, I'm sure
you'd want to throw it away
even if you have a chance.
In a way,
you may be the most suitable employee
for this guest house of the dead
since you are longing
for a perpetual death.
Do you long for the same thing?
The deity must have chained me here
because that's what they saw in me.
It started that day.
As I leaned on you while holding my grudge
and waited,
I wished
that you wouldn't change.
We were embracing our own hell then.
But now, we are leaving this world
in a decent way.
I'm glad for that.
As it's a happy occasion, let's not cry.
I will go with a smile.
Bye.
Ms. Choe.
Can I...
hug you?
I wasn't going to cry.
Why are you making me cry?
There were many times
when my heart broke for you.
I always wanted
to give you a hug like this.
Ms. Choe,
you have comforted me on many occasions.
Thank you.
How much time
do we have left?
Today,
around the time of a full moon,
all the energy at the hotel
will be collected.
Everything will disappear.
And Jang Man-wol must leave.
I've been wanting to ask you
why...
you chose me.
Why did you choose me?
I guess the flower that dreams of the moon
hasn't shown you the last dream yet.
I'm all alone now
just like how I started.
Ms. Jang, I wasn't dozing off.
I just closed my eyes for a second,
and my legs went weak.
That was a lie. I'm sorry.
We have a guest coming in.
You should go back to your office.
Welcome.
How long has it been
since you passed away?
Let me escort you to your room.
This way, please.
Ms. Jang,
the guest in Room 603 was supposed
to take the bus to the afterlife today
but wants to postpone it until tomorrow.
And these are steamed buns
requested by the guest in Room 1120.
The guest really misses
the steamed buns from childhood.
I'm going to bring these up.
Ms. Jang, I made a new cocktail.
Would you like to taste it?
Why don't you smell it at least?
Isn't the color pretty?
Come on, it does not look
like I washed rags in it.
And let's be honest.
Have you ever washed a rag?
Don't go. Stay there.
I'll go wash the rag and bring the water.
Let's compare them.
Stay right there!
You came to send off one last guest,
Chan-sung.
I feel so sleepy.
I feel like I'm falling asleep.
Maybe they want me to feel like
I'm dreaming when I leave.
I'll stay by your side
even if you fall asleep.
Now I've crossed
the long periods of time
and met you there,
embracing the flower
that is dreaming of the moon.
Your name means the "full moon".
It's pretty.
There's a place called
the Guest House of the Moon.
You're still here.
Because this place still exists.
How can I help you?
A long time ago, I lent a pair of scissors
to a bride who visited the hotel.
Do you remember?
You said you need more courage
to let go than to hold on.
You lent it to help her do that.
That's right.
The thing is,
I forgot to get it back from her.
I have it.
My gosh!
Thank goodness.
I should repay you for finding
this precious pair of scissors.
You deities never show up when I need you,
but you always return all favors.
What can I do for you?
Do you want me to cut the ties
between you and the one
who broke your heart?
Are we still connected?
Can you see it?
Are there still ties left to cut?
Well, that's...
I cannot answer that.
Forget it, then.
There's something I want.
I want to travel back in time.
-That's--
-I know you can do it.
You made me do it before.
That's true, but...
It's fine even if it's for a short moment.
Help me
see winter with her.
It's snowing.
Winter is really here.
Am I still dreaming?
This is the winter we're spending together
that you wanted.
Where did this come from?
Maybe from a time in our shared past,
or from a moment
we'll share in our future.
I'm not sure which one it is.
It's just winter
from one of the moments
we've shared or will spend together.
Chan-sung.
I saw you in my dream.
Man-wol. The moon.
Your name means the "full moon."
It's pretty.
We actually met again
after the long periods of time.
Then did this snow come from some winter
we spent together in our past?
I hope it came from our future
we'll spend together.
Really?
Now, the snow looks even prettier.
Are you going alone
without the Grim Reaper's guidance?
I've been the owner of this place
for all those years.
I will go on my own.
You're brave.
Chan-sung.
I've pondered...
countless times what I should tell you...
if this moment ever comes.
"I'm sorry."
"Thank you."
"Have a good life."
I came up with a lot of cool stuff
to tell you.
Now that it's time,
I don't know what to say.
I just...
I want to stay with you.
I just want to see you.
And I don't want to leave you behind here.
I knew I would be like this.
When I'm the weak one,
I pretended to be strong in front of you.
I even made it impossible for you
to stop me from leaving.
I'm sorry.
It was right here.
You told me not to feel lonely
when I see you off.
Were you pretending to be strong?
Back then, I didn't know
I'd like you this much.
I...
I also didn't know
I would fall in love once again.
Like a fool.
I've never thought
about the future before.
But the only thing I can tell you now
is this.
Let's
meet in our next lives again...
no matter what.
Okay?
Yes?
Chan-sung.
You looked into me,
took care of me,
and protected me.
And I thank you for that.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Man-wol.
THE SAMDO RIVER
My dear moon disappeared
after swallowing up
all my nights and dreams.
Goodbye.
It's natural to feel sad and disappointed
when you let go of someone you love.
Just like a flower dreams of
blooming again while withering away,
you'll live, meet,
and love again.
I hope
that is the answer
you two, an arrogant, foolish,
and self-pitying
yet beautiful lovers, have chosen.
Merry Christmas!
It's cold.
Chan-sung.
Chan-sung. It's so freezing.
Hey, it's gotten really cold.
New York's just as cold as Seoul,
so don't forget your winter clothes.
Can you send me my things
once I settle down there?
Sure. Take what you can
and I'll bring the rest when I visit.
How about lunch tomorrow?
Actually, I have other plans.
-Have you been well, Yu-na?
-Yes.
How did you do on your exam?
Do you have a major in mind?
Hotel management.
I'm going to become a hotelier too.
You must've gotten a good score then.
I probably will next year.
Seeing ghosts and all that,
I couldn't focus on my studying this year.
Thanks to the medicine you gave me though,
I don't see them anymore.
It made me focus on studying.
I'm glad to hear that.
You also took the same medicine, right?
You don't see the ghosts now, right?
Do you think the tiger saw
what he wanted to see in the painting?
He saw the past like a dream,
a time where he could never go back.
He got pretty lucky.
My memory of a secretive world
others don't know about.
It is where you are.
And I...
still remember my promise to you.
EXISTENCE AND TIME
You're early.
I thought you'd be late.
I hurried over
so that you wouldn't wait.
Someday...
If we meet again
in some life far down the road...
When that day ever comes,
I hope to always be with you.
We will dream together
looking each other in the eye,
embrace each other, and laugh together
as we
live happily together for a long time.
I'm about to make
an important announcement.
Where are the rest?
Is the sixth still living in Joseon?
Unbelievable.
Why is it that all 12 of us
are never able to congregate?
It's not like you're that busy.
You can talk to them later.
So what's the announcement?
I have chosen a surprising new owner
for the Guest House of the Moon.
Wandering souls
that have nowhere else to go
must have a place to stay
in order to tell their stories.
Then, what's the name of the new hotel?
Oh, that. Well, it's...
What was it again?
Wait. What's wrong with me?
Why can't I remember?
The moon has risen.
Let's open our doors.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu